
Speaker 1  (00:03)
So we've been back-and-forth with the vendor mix and upstairs by the items there's 4 4 categories of things that can be retained depending on the it depends on the product, so the 4 items are activity metadata, and there's an example of what these things are on the right here, so describing what happened, but not actually the content or a screen, no content or screenshot of that. So John Joe uploaded a file at this time to Dropbox, right? So it's sort of like the it. 

Speaker 1  (00:39)
The description of what was done, but not necessarily like a capture of any information from those files or the content, and that is applicable to dlp, and itf, both products would create that type of data, then you have sniffets, snippets are excerpts of sensitive content, so that could be So if that fire was uploaded, for example, a snippet from that file might be a visa, not a visa card number that was present in Or whatever the sensitive data was that was flagged as being a dlp concern that would be produced for a role 3 products DLP ITM or the dspm, which is data at rest scanning ICM is capable of creating screenshots. 

Speaker 1  (01:30)
So like if a user, there's a policy in place, and a user does unusual. Kind of activity. A screenshot of that activity is captured and stored in itm product. 

Speaker 1  (01:45)
And it finally files so again, going back to that example, where the file is uploaded to a risky place. The entire file is captured. So proof point, as like at the vendor level, we have a license with them to store the first 3 for 90 days. 

Speaker 1  (02:03)
They're capable of storing it for UP to a year. But that would come with a cost, I assume, because right now we have the license for 90 And then the files is a different category, they don't store those at all by default. They just don't want to take the ownership of storing full files. 

Speaker 1  (02:21)
For whatever reason, but right now, they just don't support that So The way that they support like if we did want to retain any of these for a longer period then the maximum of one year or if we wanted to retain files at all their default option is to set up sort of an integration with, like the TD would deploy something in Azure, a blob storage. And then they would interact with that and basically push those like whichever of these 4 to that blockstorage. Unfortunately, that requires us to have like a public facing blob, storage and TD doesn't support that right now like over the internet. 

Speaker 1  (03:00)
So there's kind of a challenge there. It's kind of a nogo so that forced us to look at different options on how to solve those things and the options N. Perfect. 

Speaker 1  (03:09)
There's like some catches with all of them. So I figured, let's have a chat to discuss these 4 items and make sure we're all aligned what we actually need to retain, and not And one thing, I'll say, I don't have a clear Like like a full knowledge on what semantic today is retaining for 7 years and I don't know if anyone can speak to that, but maybe we can use that as a starting point for like 1 to 1 to see. What makes sense? 

Speaker 1  (03:40)
So we'll build on this, okay. I also forwarded this to naraj, and thanks for joining Yeah, because who's B so for these products, in case we need to have more conversations on which of these lineup with regulatory or audit requirements, compliance right. They found that And he, and it sounds like maybe we need to talk to talk to data Stewart, for those things as well. 

Speaker 1  (04:08)
But just to kind of For awareness. 

Speaker 2  (04:13)
I don't start with meal in terms of your attention requirements. 

Speaker 3  (04:18)
I mean, for us, my team, we Don 't use data that's more than the I mean, I would probably say we want to use data that's more than 2 years old. And right now, we're not even using data. We use probably about a year's worth of data to look at. 

Speaker 3  (04:34)
Bonthope, or hunt trend analysis from a metrics perspective But if you know, like, if there's ways in which we can pull that down and essentially leverage that using business intelligence tools. Okay, so be it that I definitely don't use more than 2 years worth of data for any of my processes and my metrics. 

Speaker 2  (04:59)
But is there a requirement to keep Keep it for 7, should something, you know, should be a bare requirement to go. Look back at something that happened, you know, years ago. 

Speaker 3  (05:10)
I mean, that the only thing where that would come into an equation is if something was put on legal hold. For example, yeah, then we would have a whole separate issue of like, how how do you address that capture that evidence and procure it in such a way where it's, you know. Preserved in the legal manner 

Speaker 4  (05:32)
Who is the do we have the data steward in this project? 

Speaker 2  (05:37)
And we haven't assigned, but there is a lot of 

Speaker 4  (05:40)
Okay, we, so Neil is telling you practically how we use the information in ipm, but I don't want to speak on official record retention requirements because the data story would need to speak to that like We don't have a long-term storage need for our day-to-day use. But I don't, I don't want to then later have an issue opened against us because we 're out of alignment with record retention policies like with cds, record retention policies, does that make sense. 

Speaker 5  (06:19)
I think I think there are 2 years or even one year it falls under one of those standards. So as long as we have some, you know, some data retention. One year, 2 years or 5 years, 7 years, we should be fine. 

Speaker 5  (06:33)
It's going to be mainly business side calls by telling how, for how long they need the data. 

Speaker 4  (06:40)
Well, I can tell you my investigative data. I have a 10 year record retention, so that's why you see my problem. So that's why we need like We need A We need to make sure that we're in alignment with the record retention policy. 

Speaker 4  (06:59)
So like my investigative files, they can't perch for 10 years. I recognize this is not investigative file but like I can't perch them for 10 years. Which is much different than what we're talking about? 

Speaker 5  (07:13)
Just case for my own understanding of whom I made it, that Who said you need to keep it for 10 years? 

Speaker 4  (07:21)
That TV record retention policy says I have to keep it for 10 years because every document everything has what's called a record classification code, and then you have the based on the record classification code you have to Story and accordance with whatever the record classification code is it tells you the required thing so like, for example, employee personnel files are like 7 years after the person is terminated account payable records are 7 years because of the various tax laws, things like that like so every document has a record classification code and yes that's what we're looking for okay, that's why and the data stewards are the experts at those. 

Speaker 4  (08:10)
So that's like 

Speaker 2  (08:11)
Yeah, let's try to get cheek. See if she can join. Yeah, but we you know, we screwed up on that one. 

Speaker 2  (08:18)
But if it's not an investigative, I get the investigative part. I'm sorry if something is documented in 10 years. Yeah, but But how far back when they look like, you know, the 7 year is something that he's almost part of every legal framework that could ask for something 6 years after it happened, right? 

Speaker 1  (08:38)
But. 

Speaker 4  (08:41)
I don't know the answer as much because like I'm not the expert at td's record retention, so like that's why I want to be 

Speaker 1  (08:52)
Careful. 

Speaker 2  (08:53)
Mr. Chad's question, or what are we doing today? What's Saturday tomorrow? 

Speaker 1  (08:57)
The problem is 

Speaker 3  (08:59)
Wearing apples and oranges right? Orange frame solution is 7 years, and you're about to go to the cloud, which the Bender tells you we can't store for 7 years. So 

Speaker 5  (09:10)
You know, we can, but we have to sell all our kidneys to buy that 

Speaker 3  (09:15)
Yeah, well. 

Speaker 4  (09:16)
Okay, but in case you do anything you want, what time and buddy Neil? 

Speaker 3  (09:19)
Exactly. Yeah, it'll take long as it's not my, as long as it's not my money, I'm fine with it so yeah. 

Speaker 2  (09:26)
But it was like 7 years to achieve, but let's contract that with Chicago, she's presenting 

Speaker 4  (09:33)
Oh, okay. Yeah, so that's the problem is like I know today we're at 7 years, which tells me there's probably some data stored that said that this is this classification code, which makes it 7 years blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. So I just want to be very careful, and I don't want it to be like Sarah, you know, decided we only need data for 90 days, and that's great. 

Speaker 4  (09:56)
And then I get an issue later, because as the business user, we're the ones who are going to get the issue. 

Speaker 6  (10:04)
That's why I was in my thing. You know, if it's on frame or flour, he did our attention of 7 years should remain, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (10:14)
I would think so. 

Speaker 5  (10:15)
Sarah, your question, I can give you the background there that 7 years is coming from. So this is something that I call them data production governance, and Peter Lincoln is not on the fiscal, but he here to be called the ld governance. So this is what we work with him and they said, hey, we need to stay there probably for 7 years. 

Speaker 5  (10:35)
So it is business call, which they made, and we involve data short, and they said. Yeah, it perfectly aligns with out requirements so that is what I'm saying, if you say 2 years is fine for our business requirements then we have to bring it to our data store and get his or her buy anybody saying yeah, it works or not. So that is where 7 years coming. 

Speaker 5  (10:57)
So there is no really? Other than that, like alignment between us injuring and data protection team. Then getting green light from promises to do it. 

Speaker 1  (11:08)
Or something? 

Speaker 4  (11:10)
Okay, but I'm not willing to say a time period because I don't wanna be outside of the record retention guidelines. 

Speaker 1  (11:17)
I think you're not, I think it's fair to know the business requirement, though, like to accept food processes. So like Neil, you mentioned the 2 years would be reasonable to achieve the expected business processes, and that's outside of any audit or compliance requirement, I think it's fair to To get a sense, right like as a separate op. 

Speaker 3  (11:36)
Operationally, I don't need more than 2 years worth of data, but to Sarah's point, if there is an expectation to say for that record high for the type of work that Nielsen, does you need to hold that those records for 7 years. Great, and that fact is what it is. 

Speaker 2  (11:55)
And that's kind of different too, because then Chad, we'll be talking about archiving, right? But it will need to be accessible on an ongoing basis for 2 years, then probably that's the number we're working with archiving, is afterwards doing it on Brent, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (12:11)
It definitely has to talk to the data store. It seems like but it's a good info point for them, right saying, the business would need at least like, 2 years to do their normal operational processes and then see, whatever the requirements are for it's long-term attention. 

Speaker 2  (12:27)
Let me just get I was documenting it for Shika, because she won't be able to die. 

Speaker 7  (12:32)
So from the perspective of the stewardship, so unless there is like some sort of classification that the data is classified as such and requires so many years of attention, most likely the talking out of experience from some other apps they will send us back to business saying that you know how much business needs, how much data be. 

Speaker 8  (12:58)
Ladies and snaps. 

Speaker 1  (12:59)
Yeah, once we're here, so that's good that we have that up on. So the 2 year would apply for is that ITM. 

Speaker 4  (13:09)
Yeah, 2 years is plenty for ipm for a business purpose, not from a record. I don't know the record retention. I just want to say 

Speaker 2  (13:17)
The cooperation 

Speaker 1  (13:20)
Big asteroid, Esc. And the deal peacife is that, are we pretty much aliens like, I don't know about 2 years or From operational process, perspective 

Speaker 6  (13:31)
All right, set it up. 

Speaker 1  (13:35)
Okay, so even that I mean outside of compliance, like you would actually need to look back, potentially up to 7 years. 

Speaker 2  (13:48)
Access, none, that one sounds clearer. 

Speaker 4  (13:57)
I put the record retention the enterprise retention schedule in the the link to it in the chat. I just don't know what the record retention code is for these. Documents, which is why I don't know which one to tell you. 

Speaker 8  (14:16)
On the end of the season, seven goals and 7 per If the sound worked up and I was saying, all of a sudden, like my date, right? Okay, so I'm redundant. Multiple data centers are again 

Speaker 1  (14:28)
I mean, I think that makes sense for No, what we can get out of this car, right? But this is so we have an understanding of what the business needs. Now we have to double-check. 

Speaker 1  (14:38)
I put that store on any Regulatory requirement, that means that may be equal or longer to that retention time rate. 

Speaker 8  (14:50)
Go out and traffic. Go up. Do the nap date what you can do? 

Speaker 1  (14:53)
You heard it sounds like you have a name there. You're really not going to reach out to 

Speaker 2  (14:58)
Oh, yeah, that's the chica chicagot. Yeah, she's the wind in here, but she's in that cloud she'll represent. 

Speaker 8  (15:12)
And you have pretty much particularly 

Speaker 2  (15:15)
Goodbye, pause a question in theater as well. 

Speaker 8  (15:17)
I never used them. However, the theatric fire, almost example, or the 80s. Third party viral, almost 

Speaker 7  (15:26)
And from the Easter perspective, I think we have the east, the semantic products. I'm not sure if we have daes for the 2 point products so they might ask us the deport da. 

Speaker 8  (15:43)
I wanted to throw out how 

Speaker 1  (15:44)
Whatever could I want be? 

Speaker 7  (15:47)
Data are, in fact, assessment for the broad ones, so look currently, we only have records for the semantic so basically through that exercise and define how How much data is there? How long it's going to be stored? Whether it's like pcipi, and all that It's definitely important to the data. 

Speaker 2  (16:10)
Yeah, I think that was already discussing. 

Speaker 1  (16:13)
Yeah, yeah, this is something 

Speaker 2  (16:17)
Okay, I'd have to consider it. How do you want to set it up tad red as I leave you with? So you still need answers for 

Speaker 1  (16:25)
So I mean, I have the audition, like the solutioning is there we have the options in place we got away them. But really, this should kind of be sorted out before we pull the trigger on building, because yeah, if it turns out we don't need to retain as long or the retainment or certain items don't need to be retained at all. For that time period then better to descope now than happens. 

Speaker 2  (16:48)
Oh, so it's clear with DLP 7 years. Yeah, with the data volumes 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
Which one is that? That's fine? But then you have activity, metadata, snippets and files. 

Speaker 1  (17:00)
So like That, for example, the snippets I I don't know I just I don't. I don't know how that would be used necessarily. And I think that's one of the questions about comparing to semantics. 

Speaker 1  (17:18)
So what gets stored today with semantic and how are those used Vs how would these 4 items be used because it might be apples to oranges with the 2 veterans right? Yeah. 

Speaker 8  (17:30)
I'm okay, so 

Speaker 3  (17:32)
I mean, I can definitely tell you, it's apple's oranges, if you're trying to compare the type of data from my world Vs investigations. World Like against different Datasets, one is looking at events. The other is an actual investigation case, which is not the same. 

Speaker 2  (17:55)
Better chat. 

Speaker 1  (17:56)
But I feel like it feels like to be safe, we'll probably put all of these in the same bucket. I have feeling, but either way, we still need to sort out the 

Speaker 2  (18:03)
Yeah, we've had to set something up, but she can, at least formalize things get more. I mean, as data starts role on this, your proper advice. Take the gusting out of it. 

Speaker 1  (18:19)
For me, I don't have any more questions for now, I think at least we're on the same page, we've chatted it out. So yeah 

Speaker 2  (18:26)
Alright, there are no more questions. Thanks everyone for joining. 

Speaker 1  (18:32)
Getting killed because you do it. Mike's is building your 

Speaker 3  (18:37)
I hope you're ready in 1 minute, okay? 

Speaker 8  (18:42)
I'm never going to join you here. Jesus should be live number one, introduction to Azure virtual network. That works, then you'll see every wife, I've learned half one there as well. 

Speaker 8  (18:55)
Android awarding maps a chapter right Hey I just want to go out and watch this one's wet home. It should just be usually every mass work. It should be part of the key for you. 
