
Speaker 1  (00:02)
I have a meeting with csp, folks, because there's still some confusion, like who's our network resorts, and what are our tickets? I reach out to Robert broon, he's the network guy and he's telling us to go to the Sebastian cinema, so tomorrow we will have a quick call to verify that and if you can join, it's at 9 AM. Please do if you can. 

Speaker 1  (00:26)
That's final try to handle as much leg. 

Speaker 2  (00:29)
Yeah, I believe I had 3 calls already at 9 o'clock tomorrow is right? 

Speaker 1  (00:34)
That's fine, I just need to verify from the csb side that you know we are moving right because we don't have the approvals from network to the reason is because we don't have right approvals from the network. 

Speaker 2  (00:49)
That is correct, but it's not that we don't have approval, and maybe you, maybe you haven't seen the stuff even we already have an integrat. For maybe the second believe Sebastian was working with us right, and he's the gatekeeper, and there was some takeaways from our team or most likely the architect team To complete before Sebastian to have and say on this right, and I believe they admire what part of that conversation right is part of those csp tickets breaks the back and was engaged. It was another person a couple of individuals. 

Speaker 2  (01:33)
I can't remember their name right now right now. 

Speaker 3  (01:34)
Yeah, but 

Speaker 2  (01:36)
It was up to them to actually move forward before Sebastian could actually say, yes, I got everything that I needed, and we need to proceed now. 

Speaker 3  (01:46)
So I followed that meeting that Robert is requesting, so Robert and Sebastian are that worked similar right? So depending on which ticket that I think Robert is assigned to moocs or public. 3 of the 4, at least Sebastian is in there too, so there's network and the tickets. 

Speaker 1  (02:06)
And let us for our attitudes for pride. 

Speaker 3  (02:09)
Anyone, it could be either of them. So they have different domains that are working. They have network data security. 

Speaker 3  (02:20)
Yeah, it was just a general B so once economy looked for it truck or truck or All right. Let me 

Speaker 1  (02:31)
The set of European 

Speaker 2  (02:33)
We all joined late to this call. 

Speaker 3  (02:35)
Yeah, yeah, me and Chad, we're here, we were here until the boat. Well, Papa, about 2 minutes ago I favorite, I saw that you were presenting odd. I figured you guys had something else that kind of spilled over, so it was here working on the purport in the background. 

Speaker 3  (02:50)
Hola, did you see my sheer? Molan, tierone. A lot of what's it done? 

Speaker 3  (03:04)
Okay, here we go. So Let's speak kind of one, maybe second, right? 

Speaker 2  (03:14)
I add those tickets that you have opening for divert the different alcohol. 

Speaker 3  (03:20)
Sleepy second is one of them, please. One is on screen look. So all of them is saying, we're quite structured. 

Speaker 3  (03:27)
We're quiet, so She's Sebastian, is the network security guy for this one. Let me find another one, so inside a Sebastian, or Robert. Let's go for ESPN. 

Speaker 3  (03:45)
EPS PM let's track. It's a Boston has done this one as well. So maybe they're getting transferred to Robert Boone. 

Speaker 1  (04:01)
No, no, there are tickets which were submitted when we submitted the request as the application. So when you application, when you submit the ticket is, the request is the application you're supposed to engage network security in a separate way, and that's why those tickets were created. It's not the cp ticket, it's the one which is specifically for network governance. 

Speaker 1  (04:31)
So if those tickets were sitting in the queue for the long time robbed took a look today, and he said what this ticket's about, so I tried to explain him but there is always the confusion, right? Because first we submitted the tickets as the application business application, then we got that and submitted. There's a technical service. 

Speaker 3  (04:55)
So we're only here's only one ticket. So you see this on the screen, 2228, that is one that's active right now. I just hope. 

Speaker 3  (05:05)
And so those are the ones that are in there, you know, and those are the ones he's asking about, right? 2239 here it is, yes EPS PM. Yeah, that's that one there as well, 2245. 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
And talking about Dave, those tickets, which starts with Gs D 

Speaker 3  (05:23)
Oh, the other ones at the bot. 

Speaker 1  (05:24)
Yeah, those are the tickets specifically, when you submit the 

Speaker 3  (05:30)
Okay, you're surpris. 

Speaker 1  (05:32)
That application, they specifically goes for the network governance. Because the workflow, the workflow will be different from the Geer perspective, whether it's application and technical service, but yeah, so if we don't need those like what Robert wants to know that he can cancel them, right? 

Speaker 3  (05:53)
I thought it was calling us for something more interesting, man. 

Speaker 1  (05:57)
Yeah, that goes. 

Speaker 2  (05:58)
Let me understand what's the difference between applications local service during the definition? What was good change? 

Speaker 1  (06:06)
So it's a very Sato, and it's not, it's basically from the tea Dyer, so we try to get into the application as the From the theater, we try to do it as a technical service because it's obviously match match simpler, but pedar will not did not allow us to go from the technical service. Try that several times for him as msdlp. We try that 4 or 3 ap because when you submitted it as a technical service life is a little bit easier. 

Speaker 1  (06:42)
What is a minute is a business application as ours as submitted? Now life is much harder so whatever we submitted as of the ap and the msdlp as a technical servers, they cancel that and open a finding for us and said that, you know you have to go through the tire again so from technical perspective. From the tire we have business application, whatever we are doing from csp, it's I guess yeah, we are doing service so I cannot, I cannot decide that from if it's easier for us to do the technical service than we are doing the technical service if it's not, you know, in the T. 

Speaker 1  (07:29)
There, it's going to be business application. 

Speaker 3  (07:35)
I'm interested in Robin Scott around peace. 

Speaker 1  (07:42)
So the other thing I wanted to ask is you see the tickets we have to say is beach for bad. Yeah, so if you need me to submit tickets for praud, I can submit them. 

Speaker 3  (07:54)
Let's wait first though, because And once they tell us the lesson finished the part once first, because typically it's csb, all process I'm used to you would once they're finished with the part ones, they themselves would trigger a prod. All right, it's a symbol tree. Now you saw the task would come in the same ticket for like, okay, I don't know what they're doing to them, and it's 

Speaker 1  (08:18)
Their processes change several 

Speaker 3  (08:20)
Yes, yes, so Yeah, not supposed to be asking about that boy, and it suits them. Somebody asks about it and I'm saying, you know, you know, arrows guys, eh? Yeah, but So Howard, I was here. 

Speaker 3  (08:36)
And what I'd started on this Document If you have some time now, we could quickly. Up there. 

Speaker 2  (08:49)
You're not sure. Oh, yes, I mean not necessarily no. Yeah. 

Speaker 3  (08:58)
I was sitting, I wanted to I think my plan was to can do most of the updates and then leave the validation and any additions to you. Want me to do that. Still, I think I still have some idea from the changes that we were doing in progress. 

Speaker 3  (09:13)
Usually I look at those and then move some of them up front. 

Speaker 2  (09:17)
Yeah, I would say, let's with this slide. Let's all have it later, just chair the language. 

Speaker 3  (09:24)
I asked whatever plates I know of and then you just, you just continue, right? 

Speaker 2  (09:29)
Yeah, yeah, I see what's interesting and 

Speaker 3  (09:32)
The singer thing I love, that might be important for you guys to mention the society and I'm satisfied from my notes, right? Okay, anything else guys? Does it start work for you guys? 

Speaker 3  (09:42)
With their conflict with the earlier meeting a meeting at the starting at 3 or we can keep this lot. 

Speaker 2  (09:48)
It's one mayor or not. No, we can get there's this, it's been working fine. The reason why the other cultures is tended because of me. 

Speaker 2  (09:56)
I was the one that 

Speaker 3  (09:58)
No worries, but that's okay. That's okay, it's worked first alright. 

Speaker 2  (10:03)
The thing is I told Abby was going to be part of this call, like since my run is not here. 

Speaker 3  (10:08)
Yeah, so I decided she would help with the GR stuff, but I'm not sure what happened at that time like. 

Speaker 2  (10:15)
Yeah, but we also need at least for now, our team to do on the skull right, like we found out here are the teams last year. We need to make sure that we have our PM or I'll act in PM to come and provide a stage right 

Speaker 3  (10:28)
And then we chose to add it too, because they're getting, we're working on a backfield for my own. I'll know more about that tomorrow. But as soon as I hear, I provide a good to see you guys, I don't know how that comes to you. 

Speaker 3  (10:42)
But they're working on it. 

Speaker 2  (10:46)
Well, I know, it was alright. Alright, I don't know how much I would add. I make sure we track it properly right like my my, when I talk to her, and I was talking to Meyer last week is that my idea of getting added to start, you know, acting as a PM is that she's going to be working with us making sure that she's capturing the updates, and that it's being reflected here, so we don't have to spend this additional time, right? 

Speaker 2  (11:13)
So exactly yeah, maybe there was a disconnection. Maybe it was me that didn't actually communicate the message properly, but I have another chat later today. And I make sure that next one. 

Speaker 3  (11:23)
She's in the she's on this invite. 

Speaker 2  (11:26)
I forward the main thing. Oh, serious as soon as I said, let's see her. 

Speaker 3  (11:30)
Because I was there with her with wait WA' Just getting access, make sure she has access to the proof mind share, and then you know, team confirmed that yeah, she does have sheer so have access to the share so that wasn't really necessary. So And it'll later turn that 

Speaker 2  (11:48)
Yeah, yeah, no worries, we have a calling at 4 o'clock, and I'll bring it up. 

Speaker 3  (11:54)
Okay, cool. Alright, let me just finish the updates here and I'll send you the link on We should look at that guys, okay? 

Speaker 2  (12:02)
All right. Thank you guys bye. 
