
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Phytoky management in general, and how we would actually replace a key, I think we were kind of focusing after our onset in Toronto, we were putting some focus into, like, what are the options, if they lose or break a Fido key? And we were talking about issuance as well and getting into issuance? I haven't documented all of the pieces with issuance yet, and Anthony was showing on the other screen that he had put together some flows and stuff for this, I was more just kind of typing through the process to understand where there were gaps or where there were things that were missing. 

Speaker 1  (00:35)
And so I wanted to kind of run through that, but we had to. We ended up having some questions for you, and I know Jonathan took some questions back to you around like the use of the SDK for the UV and roll app. And some pieces there, and I wanted to kind of press on that a little bit more. 

Speaker 1  (00:55)
Because I'm seeing some challenges right so and I wanted to understand how like another company like Bank of America. America or something like that is handling these types of things. Because Either where, I'm not sure if we're overthinking it, or if there's some other like option or flow that we're kind of missing here. 

Speaker 1  (01:20)
But if we talk about I'm kind of I'm gonna skip new users for a minute, I think new user is a little bit more straight, but what I do have some questions there, but I'm going to skip new user, but I want to talk about like the scenario of I lost my phido key, it's I broke it, it was taken. I forgot it whatever, right? And I wanted to kind of Bring up the speed on what we were kind of discussing for potential options right with you know? 

Speaker 1  (01:59)
Maybe what I should do is kind of describe the option at the top to make it a little bit easier, but essentially We're anticipated that we're going to need a cash of spares in all of our distributed branches. And for context, we have about 3000 distributed branch, you know, bank locations. Not including backup, so just front office, the primary users are going to be using phyto keys. 

Speaker 1  (02:30)
We have both 3000 between Canada and the US and they're spread in the US they're spread all over the eastern seaboard in Canada, they're spread all the way across Canada from you. Know Vancouver to British Columbia, right? So 

Speaker 2  (02:49)
Um. 

Speaker 1  (02:52)
We understand and just the way that our branking banking works, and I'm sure that if you worked with other banks, you understand how this works. We have scenarios where we have people that work in multiple bank locations, right, they work in one location in the morning and they run to another location in the afternoon. Or they work in 11 week, and they work in another week. 

Speaker 1  (03:12)
And there's a surprising number of those right, there are certainly ones that only work in one place. There's a bunch of them that run around. And in Canada, what we have, or in the USI think, as well, we have the concept of what's called a float teller, which is someone who is actually hired to float between locations as well. 

Speaker 1  (03:32)
And that's relevant for this, because we get into scenarios of How we get into a few scenarios there around key issuance, right. Like where do we send a key? If we want to pre-register it, where does it go? 

Speaker 1  (03:51)
And one of the things that we've been kind of talking about is the need to potentially send it to the user's home. In order to make sure that it gets to them, but I have some concerns or reservations around that as well, and that has to do with like where does the users start? And they don't always start at the location that their HR portal says that is the information we have for them, so we might send it to their HR job location, but that may not be where they're starting right, and so we were kind of concerned about that, use case, and we're talking to retail more about that. 

Speaker 1  (04:22)
But when in the case of A If they broke or Lost their pie of key, they're not going to be able to wait for 2 or 3 days to get a new key or even an overnight right? Like they show up for work, they don't have their key, they need to be able to work. Right? 

Speaker 1  (04:40)
And so for that reason alone, my assumption is that we have to have some sort of cash of spare keys in every location. And is that somewhat similar to what you're seeing other banks doing? 

Speaker 3  (04:56)
Yes, yes, so every bank that we're currently working with, not just banks, but telcos. That have, you know, contact centers, for example, are all hosting a spare Their inventory, the keys that are used for recovery purposes 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
Okay. So let's talk about how do you actually use those keys, right? Because we were looking at a few different options, and I'm gonna actually just open the page to edit, and I'm just gonna summarize the option at the top, so we can kind of get a better idea of what we're talking about right? 

Speaker 1  (05:36)
So this particular one is Ah, how do I describe this? Essentially? It is User takes a Fido key from the spare cash. 

Speaker 1  (05:50)
You know, Bia manager right? And so here's one of the challenges, right? It's a bit of a catch-22, if they If they don't have their Fido key, they can't log into a machine. 

Speaker 1  (06:05)
So now they need a way to register their new key. And so we're looking at options of well, they can go under another user, and we can offer like a private browser on the retail desktops that can be clicked, and when you open the private browser allows you to get the mfa registration, and it will force a login, so that way you can log in under your own credentials, because one of the challenges here right? Is that if you go to mfa registration for entra on someone's desktop, it just automatically singles signs you in right and then you're under the other user. 

Speaker 1  (06:41)
And of course, you don't want to register your Fido key underneath. The other user, if they're the one side into the workstation, there's also a bunch of concerns about it. Note using another user's workstation to set up your own key. 

Speaker 1  (06:52)
Because now you have the keyboard to someone else's workstation, including their cash credential. And with all of the stuff, we're moving to single sign on, I sure as hell don't want someone to operate as someone else right. Should a user gets them into their desktop, and then walks away now they have access to everything that that other person has access to and that could be problematic, especially for a bad actor use case, right? 

Speaker 1  (07:15)
And so I really hate this option for a bunch of reasons. But that was one of the options that we discussed. The other option is you be enroll mobile app right? 

Speaker 1  (07:29)
The concern with ub enroll. Mobile app is really with How are we authorizing? The appropriate people to Have access to the ubi roll app, and what does that mean for our larger enterprise, right? 

Speaker 1  (07:45)
We're talking about thousands of managers, right? Because it can't just be the branch manager, because that branch manager may not be in the store that day, or they might be at another, we have some branch managers. That support 3 or 4 branches at the same time, right? 

Speaker 1  (07:59)
So it would have to be assistance and leads and Glover else right? And we'd have to be constantly managing that somehow, right. And not only that, we required them to have a phone and to have UV connector and phone now we're asking them to work on their phone, and now they, you know, we might have to consider compensation for them for their phone because of the fact that we're making the work through their phone for this purpose, right? 

Speaker 1  (08:23)
So like there's a bunch of challenges there that we have to deal with beyond the fact that, from what I understand based on my conversations with Jonathan, it seems like There isn't a great way to limit who they have access to do enrollments for and we wouldn't want them to be able to just enroll a key for anyone in the organization that would be severely overprivileged, right? Jonathan mentioned, after talking to you that there was a scenario where, like we could request a key for the user through a ServiceNow or whatever, and that would actually then show up in the queue on the ubico side that this user needs a key, and they could select their user from the queue and provision the key for them, which is slightly better, but still, they could select for anyone else too, right? 

Speaker 1  (09:17)
So not a huge fan of that, and my assumption is that you don't have some scenario here where we can. And even if you had this, I'm not sure that we could administratively handle this. Anyway, where you could say, well, this user can only provision keys for you know, this set of users. 

Speaker 1  (09:35)
And I don't, I don't think we can do that anyway, I think it's too complicated with people moving around between branches and etc, I think it would be way too much to manage that. Either way, right? But I'm concerned about the scenario of I have, you know, up to 10000 retail staff that our leaves or managers that would need to be able to do this. 

Speaker 1  (09:59)
So we're talking 10000 people, potentially. That would have access to provision a key through you being rolled for another person. 

Speaker 3  (10:12)
Great, yeah, so these are all valid concerns, they have, or they were raised by Jonathan, we actually did have a discussion with our product team here at ubico, and these issues were raised with them, in fact, I have are if he's filed for these specific issues. The roll app is still in limited early access, and so certainly, I mean, I think if this is a direction that td would like to pursue, I think then it may be worthwhile talking to product to see what we can do in terms of building in the capability that's required here. 

Speaker 3  (10:56)
I certainly think that it's a possibility. 

Speaker 1  (10:59)
Yeah, let me talk to the other options as well. And just kind of discuss this a little bit further, yeah. So Option 3 is another option we were talking about. 

Speaker 1  (11:14)
So we know that for self-service We are Creating an onboarding portal that's going to tie into an identity verification service. For new users that are coming into the organization or even for folks that need to reset their credentials. It'll be a publicly available onboarding portal, where they have to prove their identity. 

Speaker 1  (11:41)
And through a third party verifier. If you're familiar with like idb solutions And it would kind of help them to initiate their access into our environment, right? And it works particularly well for remote users and stuff like that right? 

Speaker 1  (11:57)
And so it's a pretty common industry capability that a lot of organizations are enabling now to kind of get through that first front door access. And it ties into like Again, like your Identity verification it kind of gets, it gets us out of the secret 0 problem right, and so we were basically saying, hey, how do we how do we deal with Fido key in relationship to an onboarding portal right? And so if we kind of walk through a scenario of you know, they show up at a branch. 

Speaker 1  (12:38)
Without a useful Fido, key They can launch the onboarding portal from their mobile device, right? And we can offer an option for managing multifactor. Options, and they can actually log in with their authenticator mfa. 

Speaker 1  (12:58)
And you could ignore this. This is a tactical thing before we have, IDV integration. But potentially, we could leverage yambring portal to issue them a tap and get through security registration. 

Speaker 1  (13:13)
And we would allow the ability to get to ms security registration through a temporary tap that we would issue through the onboarding portal after verification, check so that we would direct them to the onboarding portal for a verification check and then we'd provide them with a tap, we would only allow external ms, security registration. With tap. And then we would that would let them register a phytop, you know, obviously they have to have the ability to either tap or insert the phytopie on their phone. 

Speaker 1  (13:41)
In order to do that, so there's some potential issues there. But this Probably. Is the most viable option that we can see at the moment. 

Speaker 1  (13:56)
I have a bunch of concerns with this. As well. Right? 

Speaker 1  (14:03)
So These remain, not a mobile smartphone, they may not be registered for a dedicator their verification may not be current. You know, NFC you know, it could be a problem. So, like there's a there's a bunch of like little challenges here, I think that this potentially could be an option, but I don't think it can be the only option, because if for some reason this fails there needs to be some. 

Speaker 1  (14:26)
Other way to get them working right And one of the challenges with Fido one of the benefits of Fido is also the challenge, which is you have to have physical possession to set it up right? And so it's a it's both A A compliment and also a detriment So we had discussed another option, so Jonathan initially mentioned the SDK to me and I was like, oh well, if we have the SDK, then potentially we could hit the SDK through our onboarding portal and actually set up the phytoke directly through there, and then he went back and talked to you again. 

Speaker 1  (15:05)
And I think you had mentioned that the SDK isn't really available to do phytoke, setup. And so I guess my question would be then what is the stdk used for them? And when you have available through the stdk? 

Speaker 3  (15:19)
Yeah, so maybe maybe there were some confusion with respect to how I understood what he was asking for and what the SDK capability is. So yes, so the SDK capability does allow you to provision a phyto ii security key. The thing there is that the tooling that we've built is integrated with our phyto preranch orchestration component comp. 

Speaker 3  (15:51)
Upon it right? So it's not a self-service type of capability. Right, so the roll app is essentially sitting or being driven through the file pre-registration capability. 

Speaker 3  (16:07)
So the idea there is you log in through the app, you know, you select the user that you want the credential to be registered for that. But if we're having tactics of prerequisite 

Speaker 1  (16:22)
If we change this blow, so we directed the user to go to ServiceNow to request a new key. He essentially, which would get it into the Q through the ub connector right? Yep, now it's in the queue. 

Speaker 1  (16:34)
Now we could use the onboarding portal to go, find that entry in the queue through the SDK, and then do the key issuance, right? Yeah, so I think 

Speaker 3  (16:48)
But. 

Speaker 4  (16:50)
I thought I thought that that The ordering ap right the interconnector and the prerequis APIs are only for provisioning and ordering a key that you is in the possession of ubico, not a random key that's already been deployed to is shipped to a branch right where I confuse that. 

Speaker 3  (17:07)
No, so those are those are 2 Capable flows, so there is the flow, and we're shipping, the key, where the key is credentialed at ubico, but what we're talking about now here with Jeremy, is a flow that supported, where you have possession of the key. Okay, alright, so, in this flow of Jeremy, this is possible. Not to do so, actually 

Speaker 1  (17:32)
I don't even know that we need to put a certain, I think, Jonathan, one of the things we'll talk about is whether or not for this scenario, we would even do a ServiceNow, replacement, we might be able to use the onboarding portal to call the ub connector to get a registration set. Up and then call the SDK to then set up their registration. I don't even know why we want to put a ServiceNow request for that. 

Speaker 1  (17:54)
Because At that point, the manager and the employer are already working together. There's no reason to add a ServiceNow request to the to the mix there. 

Speaker 5  (18:03)
And I mean, one of the aspects we talked about was, how do we automate the stock Replenishment and a branch. 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
Well, yeah, but I think that's a problem. Whether or not you the entry point is ServiceNow or the onboarding portal, it would still end up in the same place that either way either both of them are calling the UV connected, right? Yes, I think the question for Shaquille is in a scenario. 

Speaker 1  (18:29)
Where we put in a request for pre-registration, I'm assuming there's some sort of flag that says, don't send this out, we already have the key. 

Speaker 3  (18:42)
But there's two different. There's two different 

Speaker 5  (18:44)
Different cues, I well, tequila used the proper use the proper language to describe that the pre-registration flow and the kind of self 

Speaker 1  (18:53)
Hello, yeah, yeah, you're right. There are two separate cues, so the prerequisites like that, so we would have to know that we have a key when we're making the request. And that would that would cause it, cause us to request against a different cube. 

Speaker 3  (19:12)
Correct? Yeah. So I think maybe Just based on what I'm seeing here or listening to here today, considering that we have idv, as potentially part of the solution, Germany, and also Jonathan, I know, Jonathan, you've been, we had a discussion around, you know, with product around the enroll app specifically. 

Speaker 3  (19:37)
But you become also working on something called ubid and the ubid platform. And so what we're doing is we're taking the ubid, or we're taking the enroll app capability, and we're integrated into an idv, capable flow. So essentially, what that's gonna look like is the user does idv, and then they can provision or sell provision, a ubiquity of their mobile device, which is going to be essentially like a preradge, a pre enrolled credential flow. 

Speaker 3  (20:14)
So what we can do just to think through how that's going to work. I'm considering the environment that we're in constraints etc, it may be beneficial to bring in the product team to talk about that and what that architecture looks like, and what the user dreaming is going to look like. Because this is in line with what we are currently building right now. 

Speaker 3  (20:43)
So I think there's a potential here building something that is tailored to T d's requirements. 

Speaker 1  (21:00)
Yeah, I'm I'm not sure what your response is to that Jonathan, but I would think that that would be a useful conversation. 

Speaker 5  (21:09)
Yeah, I just wanted to. You know, hear about things and understand timeline timelines. 

Speaker 3  (21:16)
All right, yeah, we are Yeah, so we are currently working with other customers. I will say that this solution that I just described is currently being built for Walmart because Walmart Wanted something very similar to what we're talking about here, and so ubiko started to design this solution around kind of Walmart's requirements. And it ended up becoming a more sort of general offering, and so we have just been told about this as of a few weeks ago, with respect to what product is working on and a major part of pre-registration and enrollment has been the idv integration capability. 

Speaker 3  (22:06)
So we have integrated IDV into the connector orchestration framework to enable 2 types of Onboarding models or journeys, right? One is the enrollment agent, the branch manager etc, ID ving and then credentialing the key on behalf of the user, and then another flow where the user is idving, and then credentialing the key themselves. So I think it would probably be beneficial for TV, to understand what that architecture looks like, and then And understand what your requirements are, what your constraints are and see, whether it fits, you know, into, you know, your current framework. 

Speaker 3  (23:01)
And if there are certain things that need to be customized, I think we have the opportunity to do that. Okay? Hey 

Speaker 4  (23:12)
Oh, and Jerry real Clinton related to ID, but we're that gonna have the official company. I believe the solution in place and time for Mister rod branches her army. Are we talking about? 

Speaker 4  (23:26)
We're interim idv, as like a custom. 

Speaker 1  (23:33)
So we've already been going through vendors selection from an idd perspective, whether or not that aligns with our timelines, remains to be seen. What we're saying is that Where we're looking at escalated, the onboarding portal itself with a with our interim identity verification measures that will swap in the idd verification for when it's available right? 

Speaker 4  (24:04)
So, but I was just saying, well, Shaquille's talking about is, hey, okay? If a ubico initiative Relationship with an ID provider So, would we be tough, would that is that a target state solution, or is that an interim state solution? 

Speaker 1  (24:20)
I don't know that that's a solution at all. I think that I have to talk to their product group, okay. Okay. 

Speaker 4  (24:25)
I was just saying, oh, that sounds like 

Speaker 1  (24:28)
We'll have to discuss that right, I mean, right now, Jonathan, my assumption, I think that we've already got our idb vendor locked in. 

Speaker 5  (24:36)
Yeah, I mean, we've chosen one. Yes. 

Speaker 3  (24:41)
Yeah, and as part of UBI D We are obviously we support bring your own idv vendor and so whatever idv vendor that you have selected can be integrated with the solution. So that capability exists as well. But I think that we have to just looking at these and really, in my mind, there are 2 types of flows at a very high level right? 

Speaker 3  (25:10)
There's a tap centric flow that you can drive through idv, where you're doing substruct registration on mobile and the user is essentially driving all of that, I mean, you can do that today relatively easily. And then there's a you know, the other flow, which is, uh I'd say some more managed flow in terms of how the credential It's being created. But to your point Jeremy, there are 0 secrets. 

Speaker 3  (25:38)
There is no tap in that flow. 

Speaker 1  (25:58)
Yeah, I mean, that's, that's the benefit of looking at this type of option Shaquille is like, I would prefer not to do option 3. Where we have to do odd verification, IDV verification and then point them directly at Emma security registration and have them go through that process. There's There's There's ugliness there. 

Speaker 1  (26:27)
But it also brings up another item that I wanted to kind of understand if you had an option for so let's say that we do a pre-registration option right through whatever method like we discussed, and we get it into your prejudge Q with indication that we already have. The key now we used up one of our spare keys in that location. In a magical world We would be able to just Ship another blank spare to that location to replace the one that was just issued. 

Speaker 1  (27:05)
Is there a scenario that enables that without us all having to, because the other thing that I'm concerned about is that if we're not out of replenishing, but we use a spare, my presumption is that the branch will Use up their spares, and then not have any more and then be up a creek. The first time they don't have a spare because there was no real automated flow to handle replacement. 

Speaker 3  (27:33)
Right? Yeah, this is something that we discussed as well. I think Jonathan, if you recall with our professional services team. 

Speaker 3  (27:43)
Where we would need to design a business process, so you do have that automation for replenishment so I think one of the ideas that was floated, was, you know, anytime there's a recovery that's required that there's a ticket that's submitted. And then that ticket would serve as the as sort of the source of truth with respect to how I'm replenishment. Right? 

Speaker 3  (28:09)
So anytime key has been used. It would be a process that Would be triggered for a key to be shipped to that location? 

Speaker 4  (28:26)
How would that? How would you say in this, that's an area? Does you become know the physical location of the unassociated key that was used, or that rely on the user requested the replacement to provide that. 

Speaker 3  (28:39)
Yeah, the replacement, because when the key is shipped. Obviously you're providing the addressing information to where that key needs to go. So I think we just, we just need to sit down and think through how that replenishment flow would work. 

Speaker 4  (28:59)
It's the other item, whether I'm sure you thought about this Jeremy and John But the other option is just to have, like the branch. Tech Support teams have spares themselves and An act as a fallback. If the branch It maintained a stock, just like they were for any other equipment failure. 

Speaker 1  (29:17)
Yeah, but keep in mind that we use a third party vendor. For that like A I can't remember the name that we leveraged these days, but it's different in Canada and the US but It's not as simple as you think, and they're not getting out there same day. 

Speaker 4  (29:40)
Okay, yeah, I didn't know if they were, because it's our branch equipment failures. I didn't know how they were addressing it. I knew that there was somebody to address them. 

Speaker 4  (29:49)
And the details, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (29:51)
I mean, if you're in small town forever in any state or province. 

Speaker 1  (29:57)
Yeah 

Speaker 3  (30:05)
I 

Speaker 5  (30:06)
I think we need to list this as a requirement. Yeah, we need automated stock replen. 

Speaker 1  (30:14)
And I think I could see ways for us to if there is A 

Speaker 6  (30:17)
Are we talking about this? 

Speaker 1  (30:21)
We can automate anything, as long as you get all the resources, the capability to do it. 

Speaker 6  (30:25)
We talked about that with mark on keeping the shipping costs down Jeremy of a restart process to certain locations naturally. But we need to know numbers and get a little more maturity, before we know exactly what that is. 

Speaker 4  (30:42)
Because how do we I think the question to me, is how do in the event that someone and it pulls out of stock or registers a key out of stock? How do we know where that was located? Because especially considering we don't necessarily I know where I use her is at a given time. 

Speaker 4  (30:57)
We'd have to I don't know, we'd have to have some sort of I don't know if you would call my tanesis, but database that you know, this is this key ID that it's physically was physically part of the branch spares, stock. And I don't know, pickipsy or whatever. Yeah, exactly that that's just like that. 

Speaker 5  (31:14)
Yeah, so just describe it right. So 

Speaker 4  (31:17)
So how does does that 

Speaker 5  (31:18)
Do they send ServiceNow that we somehow But do we need a health serial number? 

Speaker 4  (31:25)
I guess when we, when we order a set of I guess when we order a set of unassociated spares, we've ordered 5 spares for the branch in, you know, Toronto branch, 1234, right. Do we get information that it's, these are the serial numbers, or key. Ids or unique identifiers that the keys that are in the stock at brand 234, so we know when someone associates themselves to that key, that the stock in 1234 is depleted by one. 

Speaker 5  (31:57)
That's exactly 

Speaker 4  (31:59)
Do we know that AI am kind of asking like, is that is that information that's available to us at some point during the ordering process? That's definitely, I don't know how to and do we have to store it and then a database of our own 

Speaker 3  (32:11)
Yeah, I mean this is something that we thought about. I think we have discussed this discussion, Jonathan, and I think that we probably need to go through what the business process would look like. So things get a little tricky with respect to your question, Paul. 

Speaker 3  (32:30)
And it's a good one, because One of the things that you know I was talking to Jonathan about here is in this In particular, scenario with the branches is I'd rather well, I'm not gonna say it unique, but it is. Typical for these types of environments, now that we've introduced pre-registration capability of keys, we're going through this with belt Canada, for example. And that is that You know, the branch will have 2 types of let's say configurations for their keys. 

Speaker 3  (33:09)
You'll have a preregged key, which will be custom configured for OTP for authentication to ZOS right, and then your spare key will not be a pre-registered key that will simply be a blank phyto, key, but it will be customized for OTP for zos. Now that's that's done in the way that it's done is because we initially decided that we don't want to preradge keys at a location because of the flover scenario. And so this is common right where your spare key is not a prerench key, because we talk about that key being I can use for recovery and going to the final recovery. 

Speaker 3  (33:58)
It'll be subservice registration for all intents and purposes, so that will not be a pre-registered key. It will still be a custom program key for OTP, so we also have to think about the recovery flow for OTP here and not just paskeys. So I'll park that for a second. 

Speaker 3  (34:19)
That we register keys have Have serial numbers associated with users? Because when we credential the key, the response payload, we return to the fighter connector contains the serial number. The map to the user along with their firmware version, so you get to decide where you want to store that and how Non prerequisite keys don't have that because we're not sending you any type of data, right? 

Speaker 3  (34:54)
Back because there's no pre-registration. So non prerage keys will have to rely on some other form of user to serial mapping, and because of the way phyto works, right? There's no serial number that' S presented during the registration process, so you don't know what the serial number of the key is. 

Speaker 3  (35:14)
And so that becomes tricky, just from a technical standpoint from a protocol standpoint, and so what we can do is what we normally do is we provide this serial number ranges. Now that becomes a little convoluted and complex right? Because you have a range, now, you have to decide, okay, which range is going to which branch and sure you can do that. 

Speaker 3  (35:39)
But we're going to have to think about what that's going to look like, if we really want to be able to. Say this serial number is associated to this branch. 

Speaker 4  (35:48)
But actually wait, I think you maybe the first point sounds like a fundamental blocker, where if we don't see during the self registration process, if we never see a serial member to correlate against what we know is in a branch, then we don't I actually didn't know that so we can't tell from the idp side when someone's registered at pasky, we don't get the serial number information, I guess. 

Speaker 3  (36:13)
And in the no, that's then like 

Speaker 4  (36:18)
If we can't see it from the idp side, and it's, and it's a self registration process, then we'll never know what key was actually consumed. And so even if we knew what 0 numbers were at 1 frame. I actually wouldn't know that that registration dictated the stock from that branch. 

Speaker 3  (36:33)
No, not not through the registration process. Right, so you would have to have, we would have to have some other way to tell that that key was depleted from that stock, at that particular bridge. So whether that's a ticket that has been submitted as part of the recovery flow that gets tied to the entire process that would be able to allow you to identify that, yes, this key has now been depleted from the stock, and not from this branch, but you will not be able to do that via serial number. 

Speaker 4  (37:09)
So the only way to do that is basically to ask the user, right? Have them submit something. I don't write, there's no, it sounds, I don't nothing, a sort of programmatic automated way to handle this, other than once, they've told you that they've consumed the key from that branch that you've shipwon but no way the same just to observe the association of a particular key with a particular user and say whoop, they'll then branch, too, need to spare Oh, no, anyway, that's that sounds like that's just not there's no technical. 

Speaker 4  (37:38)
There's no way to tie those together technically. 

Speaker 3  (37:43)
Not at this point, when Microsoft introduces support for what's called enterprise at a station, which will allow the idp to request The certificate and parse the serial number from the key. Then we will have that kind of more granular capability, but as of today that does not exist. 

Speaker 4  (38:13)
All right anyway, so that's, I guess we'll have to figure out some other out of band way of handling branch, stock sounds like 

Speaker 3  (38:29)
So I think Jeremy and Jonathan. We did. We did help to schedule a meeting with the product team to talk about. 

Speaker 3  (38:41)
What we're doing with UBI D and Have a discussion around T d's requirements and whether You know, it's something that we can accommodate in time for deployment with respect to the roadmap. 

Speaker 5  (38:57)
Yeah, I was going to say, I think it should be like, just A You know, general roadmap update here because there's obviously multiple things that you have on the go with your ubian, roll app, your ubid, you've got 

Speaker 1  (39:12)
There's quantum quick Cryptography, as well. 

Speaker 5  (39:16)
Brian, who knows what else? 

Speaker 3  (39:37)
At the Caribbean chamber is still with us. 

Speaker 1  (39:40)
I am sorry. I'm just still there, yeah. I agree that a conversation is warranted at the end of the day like, you know. 

Speaker 1  (39:51)
We want to make sure that we're taking advantage of what's already being handled in the industry. And what you're looking at Already with other Partners right? I don't want to have to Provision or set up a really clunky. 

Speaker 1  (40:11)
Flow for this, when you may already have something else available, or you have something that's been tried and true by other large organizations in a similar use case, right? Right now, I have to be honest, that all of the flows that we're looking at for key replacement, in particular, uh U. Have definitely some cons. 

Speaker 1  (40:36)
So And I have concerns about the usability of that and pushback from retail and etc, right? So Obviously the more self-service that we can make things, the better and if there's an idb type option that allows for a self-service registration. That avoids us having to customize our own feature for that, that includes a verification check and then giving them a tap, so then they have to redirect and use in another ms security registration page in order to register the bido key. 

Speaker 1  (41:11)
I just I foresee a lot of problems with that option, even though that one is the least painful of the 4 that we explored so far. 

Speaker 3  (41:20)
Really twice, yeah, like, I mean, I do agree, and I think that because you are leveraging Fido, ubiquito, prerech that does enable possibilities. Right? So it does enable the idv integration possibility, and then it does enable obviously the The pre enrollment capability and extends it from not just ubiko, registering the key, but an enrollment agent potentially registering the key as well as the user registering the key. 

Speaker 3  (41:58)
So there are possibilities. I think we just have to look at What what your current requirements are, and what your constraints are and what we can do to accommodate that, if possible. So a discussion with product on what ubid looks like from an architecture, standpoint, capability, standpoint, and whether, you know, they map whether you're functional and non-functional requirements, and then I think you would be in a better position to, you know, make decisions with respect to what's going to work for you. 

Speaker 3  (42:34)
Yeah, great. So this is all great conversation. I appreciate being invited. 

Speaker 3  (42:43)
Thank you, Jonathan. 

Speaker 5  (42:46)
I just requested a suggestion. 

Speaker 3  (42:48)
Oh, okay. So what I is, would it be possible to share those user journeys with me that you have documented there 

Speaker 1  (42:58)
Yeah, we're working on cleaning those up a little bit and putting them into some flows, so If you don't mind giving us a few to get the cleaned up over the next few days, here we should be able to provide that. I don't think there's an ATD centric data here. So 

Speaker 3  (43:16)
Okay, okay, so I'm not sure what your week looks like Jeremy and team that need to be involved in that conversation with product. Certainly Jonathan, you're going to be there. But I can send out or you know, a few times that work for the product team here and allow you to respond with what works for you and schedule the meeting just to have a discussion. 

Speaker 3  (43:45)
And then see where we can go from. There. 

Speaker 5  (43:50)
Okay, sounds good. 

Speaker 3  (43:57)
It's exciting and I'll tell you, it's exciting for me. Personally, idv is an initiative that I have been working on internally at ubico for 2 years now. So it must do. 

Speaker 3  (44:12)
Yeah. It's taken a while for us to get here, but I'm glad that we're here, you know, we have A new chief of product that started, you know, it's about 6 or 7 months ago. Some things have changed quite a bit. 

Speaker 3  (44:28)
But with respect to these flows, and what we're talking about, I mean this is something that I and I have been building and working with other vendors, including you know, Microsoft with verified ID, Jonathan has seen the demos with hyper and their firm product, and how we actually build these flows, whether or not it's taped, you know, with tap issuance, or with prered etc, I think what we're doing with ubid, is we're taking that in a different direction where we're now going to be leveraging, what I think is our hugest, you know. 

Speaker 3  (45:02)
Our biggest advantage, which is the pre-registration component Because we have that automation, we have the security that backs it, and if you're going to be adopting it, and deploying it to drive your credential pipeline, we can add idv on top of that, then I think it does make for a compelling solution. We just have to figure out what the gaps are, and we've talked about some of those earlier before prior to this conversation during this conversation, we just need to figure out what those are and see if there's a possibility of being able to solve for them. 

Speaker 1  (45:40)
Yeah, great. Yeah, we Joss and I have been trying to get identity verification, working or approved and funded at TV for about 4 years. I think, Jonathan And it wasn't really until this last year that we were able to start getting some traction on it. 

Speaker 1  (46:02)
And it's been a long, it was a hard thing for executives to wrap their heads around. And I think it was, it was kind of hard like I don't know, I didn't feel like it was. I felt like it was a very simple A conversation to have right like we are literally handing credentials to people that were not verifying. 

Speaker 1  (46:28)
Through their managers or just giving them like a one time password And people are calling the service desk and using virtually, we've had Over the last 20 years that I've been at Didi, we've had challenges with how do we verify people calling the help desk to get resets, right, and it's just shocking to me that people haven't been able to put 2 and 2 together and realize that we need something stronger. Even in the face of just significant industry shift in that direction, right? So it's been a long time coming for sure. 

Speaker 3  (47:00)
Yeah, and you know, I recently presented on an idv with hyper. And Yuboko, and we talked about this very problem. We have a bank. 

Speaker 3  (47:14)
It's a medium-sized bank in the US that deployed. Fishing, the wind fishing resists, an authentication for signing it had lots of problems, they decided it became a board level concerned, both said yes, let's do this, they went ahead, they deployed fishing, went down to basically 0. But. 

Speaker 3  (47:35)
The recovery process has no IDV and falls back WDP. Yeah. And so I think we're, this is where we are with a lot of organizations that I'm working with, I'm seeing this time and time again, so we're trying to encourage. 

Speaker 3  (47:54)
And I think this is where td's on the right path right that this is the way we need to be thinking about Being pushed and resistant throughout the identity life cycle Yeah, great, so I know where our time so what I'll do is Jonathan and Jeremy, I'll send you some times I'll check the availability of the product team and then let's get a discussion together to talk about ubid, and then we can do it too. Take the next steps. In the meantime, once you've got your documentation. 

Speaker 3  (48:41)
Fit for for release, just to send it to me so that I have it, and we can go through it here internally as well. With our solution. Architects Just to see what works where and if there are any discussions, we need to have around that, then we can do that as well. 

Speaker 1  (48:57)
It's sound to get 

Speaker 4  (48:58)
Great guy, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (49:04)
Next folks, Anthony, for tomorrow, maybe we can put some focus into 

Speaker 7  (49:08)
Yeah, I got it, I got it. Yeah, mapping the yeah, it looks like an important issue. We need to figure out the best and easiest way to understand it's not going to be one size fits all, but we can't keep everybody happy, but let's try let's do it. 

Speaker 1  (49:25)
All right, yeah, we'll talk tomorrow. Thanks. Bye 

Speaker 8  (50:40)
It's like loop, this little cloop. 

Speaker 8  (52:37)
You need to bring 

Speaker 8  (54:52)
Oh, something. 20. 

Speaker 3  (54:56)
You know, it's bullying. 

Speaker 3  (55:40)
This see, we have to put this 

Speaker 3  (01:01:36)
It's together, yes, got it. You need to 

Speaker 8  (01:03:51)
This flew. 
