
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Now it's the right contact when it comes to like Physical deployment of something in a branch Related to, you know, does soft hardware 

Speaker 2  (00:13)
Yes 

Speaker 3  (00:14)
I already do, we've just heard clarity. What's that I raised this with savario already just for awareness, so he noticed that we're looking at this kind of thing. So I assume you can be involved in some kind of hardware standard. 

Speaker 2  (00:25)
Yeah, I know that that's a hardware standard part of it, and then we gotta figure out number one, so normally for like a regular, just going into the branch that's the desk side team under fassel that owns like the Vendors that go in. But if we're talking about, like, hey, it's going to need to be a project. 

Speaker 4  (00:44)
To actually 

Speaker 2  (00:45)
Put equipment in and coordinate with all the branches in the US and Canada. Yeah, and then ownership of the devices we'd have to probably loop in, or you know, management of equipment would probably have to be with queasy Brown, who homes, the hard asset management team. 

Speaker 5  (01:04)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (01:05)
I'm not sure how accurate it was, Dave, but I know that Mike met with It might have been basil, or whoever that owns the Bender relationships for field services. And they gave, like a general quote of like, this is how much we think it would cost. To go and install something like this in the branches, and then we included that in our financial quote, for the project for the program, which I think is now going through, like hedge for funding or something like that, I know that there's a whole bunch of churn around that, but There was I believe that that is somehow included in there somewhere, but it may With Michael nar. 

Speaker 6  (01:51)
Yeah, we better get that included, because I've been talking to, Michael daybell funding, and he's got to present something to Jim this afternoon at 4:30, and he seemed to be not entirely 100% sure as to what should or shouldn't be included. But that really, that piece really does. Need to be included. 

Speaker 7  (02:16)
Yeah, and I think Jordan, you had a concern about use of fc readers as well, with regards to the design or mainframe. 

Speaker 8  (02:25)
Yeah, we just have to make sure we test it right and fairy like you read the documentary because they say OTD can be passed through the NFC tap. Through some HID protocol, but I don't, we haven't tested that So that's something we need to do, and technically, we don't even need to test it like using the mainframe, the way that it actually theoretically works. You should build open up notepad and tap the can the reader, if it types a string and a notepad, and it bulwark. 

Speaker 7  (03:03)
All right, yeah, I just wanted to quickly ask about Because there was a session around funding this morning, so 

Speaker 4  (03:11)
Jordan changed just brought that up. With me, so I'll think about it a little bit. 

Speaker 9  (03:19)
Yeah, I agree with the test test. 

Speaker 8  (03:21)
Yeah, read up on the docks, because really all it's doing, like the way it works for you. USB, is it acts as virtual keyboard and types the string in its inner right supposedly, when you look at the docks, you can do the same thing over NFC, but it has to be set up in the right slot and some other stuff. So yeah, take that back. 

Speaker 8  (03:37)
Jonathan, let me know what you find it. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (03:41)
Because when I initially just tested the NFC reader, it was basic functionality, but at the same time I did look into configuring configuration settings and options. But I didn't even attempt to test otb, didn't want to get too far down into the weed. But I think I can without too much difficulty. 

Speaker 4  (04:07)
So I let you know 

Speaker 7  (04:12)
Okay, alright, I wanna start from the bottom, because we haven't really been talking about mainframe for a few weeks. So we'll just quickly go through mainframe updates, and then we'll go to the top. So nps server bills, I know, there's been a lot of discussion about this, Paul. 

Speaker 7  (04:34)
Do you want to give the group an update? On these, I don't know you had to rework some of the design there. 

Speaker 5  (04:42)
Yes, so we're, I guess we're yeah, that's BL10 by kind of discussed the eye. And I discussed the That's 5 capabilities with the network team and they Don 't support kind of making, they don't support source network address better. Remember the right terms, I permit source network dress translation, but preserving the source address for traffic. 

Speaker 5  (05:09)
By making the mtm, the gateway for the virtual servers in that's not a pattern that's available for virtual servers and TV, so we have to kind of fall back on either. He was at ltms during pure Deanna, slow balancing. If we want to do Though bouncing out of the anthropom. 

Speaker 5  (05:34)
Patients inside it all, of course Using replacing the ltms with the Microsoft S proxy servers, which basically kind of do our Guilty of the dozen networkload bounce, does load bouncing between ps servers directly or Seeing if we can Dang at the dilution would work in the absence, you know, sort of without the preservation of source H information that's typically I think I thought it was required for the ideas to function but it may just be able to act as if the right the exam is the client directly, but there's a question around kind of the secrets and Authentication vertical, which is because I people can take their face so Because it's no concern, don't see that option will just be divided in it. 

Speaker 5  (06:37)
Except I have prompted, I have favorite requests, I do correct malpoda, correct network zone, now that we define the network zone that's will be in. And we can Are mutations of it? I They also request Locked him because I just had gtm before, and we had to kind of set up a health well and the gtm. 

Speaker 5  (06:59)
Which video is possible? Need to work that outside put in requests for that. 

Speaker 7  (07:14)
Thanks for the update. Any thoughts, questions on that from anybody else? 

Speaker 5  (07:23)
I'm hoping for you. 

Speaker 4  (07:25)
Go ahead. 

Speaker 9  (07:26)
I was going to say when we set up the cast servers for the broadcom AM solution, we worked with the F5 team Paul to define GT M owned. Name resolution that in the background, then checked the ltms. It's not a pattern, the team prefer. 

Speaker 9  (07:52)
Say it that way, but it was the option we tested with in the am environment, and it worked. Properly, so when we queried the G tms, they replied back with the real I ps that were being monitored by the L tms under the covers, and then we were able to connect directly to the servers rather than having to proxy through the ltms themselves. 

Speaker 5  (08:25)
Okay. No, yeah, that's probably what we would need. I know you can't help check. 

Speaker 5  (08:28)
The ability tends to be more constrained. That's so these have been ltm. During the 

Speaker 9  (08:34)
Checks, yeah, we had the ltms doing the health checks and then the gtm monitoring and then just replying back with the available IPS based on that monitor okay? 

Speaker 5  (08:47)
I think that's the most likely bubble do here that's next today. 

Speaker 8  (08:50)
Yeah, it was okay. That sounds, that sounds interesting. 

Speaker 4  (08:54)
Mark, and I'm going to say Paul and I really only got a couple minutes to touch based on this, I said that I guess I'm not a fan of introducing additional servers into the mix here, like the proxies, you know, they have If purpose A And in our case Really? We're not looking for we don't really unload, we don't load constraints, we're really just looking for availability and introducing another layer. With proxies just seems completely unnecessary, so if we can do something at the network like mark just described. 

Speaker 4  (09:32)
I would certainly go that way. Yeah, it makes 

Speaker 5  (09:37)
So yeah, most of them turn, we'll try and match something up-and-down. Make sure that it The work smoothly and have a real depth set up to swap the mainframe test. But sorry, yeah, Tesla's environment. 

Speaker 5  (09:51)
I'll work too. 

Speaker 7  (09:58)
Okay, so Jonathan, this impacts some of your design work right? So you had suffering this into 21 for nps and one for zmfa, right? 

Speaker 4  (10:12)
Yeah, that's right. That's right. Well, the existing yeah, so the existing one just so right now for a high level, it just says generically. 

Speaker 4  (10:23)
You know, talks about high availability and load balancing, but doesn't have the specifics. So once we get this figured out, we decided and I will need that for detailed, so we're good for today. 

Speaker 7  (10:36)
Okay, so this does not impact the high level design. 

Speaker 9  (10:41)
And just so you're on the same page, Jonathan, it's the mainframe itself. Will it can load balance between the 2 targets if there's going to be one at each data center, so we're not reliant on the enterprise level. Design, but obviously if there was one, we would Hitchhar, wagon to it right. 

Speaker 9  (11:05)
But we can go ahead independently of that. Paul's able to stand up the 2 servers, then set him a fake and Life Rodge, the 2 of them in a high availability pattern. In itself, right without the need of additional help from others. 

Speaker 9  (11:22)
That sounds 

Speaker 4  (11:23)
Yeah, and I think I've got that captured. Okay? 

Speaker 7  (11:27)
Yeah, thanks. So, Jonathan is the high level design. A completion of probability on track for tomorrow. 

Speaker 4  (11:35)
Richard, no, no cause I have 2 So no, that won't be completed tomorrow. Be completed next week. 

Speaker 7  (11:50)
Okay, so I'll just need a new timeline on that. Please 

Speaker 4  (11:56)
Okay, put a friend to end it next week. That's like 2324. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 4  (12:08)
So right here, okay. Does not give me the steel option, okay? 

Speaker 7  (12:30)
Can our infrastructure architect continue dependent on these Details. 

Speaker 5  (12:38)
He's been basically consulting at this point, but he came to a finalized design until, you know, finalized. Finalized infrastructure design until the details are sorted out. As is directly down the stream of the the A sort of solution design An architecture, which is currently, you know. 

Speaker 7  (13:14)
I don't think else for MPs. Paul, are you hoping to get this done next week or 

Speaker 5  (13:25)
One have submitted the requests. I'm at the mercy at the The moment I think the vms might have already been created, so I just need to start out access that I haven't had a chance to actually check. Usually credit quick for vms for the F5I have no idea their SLA is 10 days normally. 

Speaker 5  (13:44)
I banned. It could be longer depending on whether this customized health check takes more time. I can't wait for that right now. 

Speaker 6  (13:56)
But aside from homes, you've got everything you need at the moment that you know that you need pop. Is there anything else that you're lacking? That would allow you to perceive? 

Speaker 6  (14:14)
I don't think so I just want to check thanks. 

Speaker 7  (14:21)
Okay, anything else here NPS. 

Speaker 4  (14:24)
Well, just to be just to be clear here, the part that I'm working I'm working on right now, is that it was a greed, but Ken Allen at Dave Roberts that we would establish nps as a standard. I didn't remember that. Okay, so that's that's the only thing that's It's a standing holding up the approval issuing the certificate for high level design for nps. 

Speaker 6  (14:56)
Do we need to have the standard in place to get that bill? 

Speaker 5  (15:01)
No okay. 

Speaker 4  (15:02)
Okay, yeah, so I just I just wanted Make that make that clear, like, I'm good for high level Des. For NPS you know this part here about the what we do for the load, balancing that can wait from my perspective to help detail design, but Nabil needs that information in order to actually do the build. 

Speaker 5  (15:25)
Configuration, I don't think he does the bill. I think he just does the infrastructure design. 

Speaker 4  (15:30)
Yeah, yeah, the design. Yeah, so that you can get the built going. Yes. 

Speaker 5  (15:34)
Yeah 

Speaker 4  (15:40)
Bear as much or 

Speaker 10  (15:45)
He's modeled with Oliver. 

Speaker 7  (15:47)
Produce a lot of work governments. I wanted to approve Jonathan, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (15:54)
Yeah, as if there's only one approval date. Yes, there's several we know about and probably 10 days ago. 

Speaker 7  (16:06)
Yeah, one step. 

Speaker 4  (16:08)
Okay, because every exec has committed to making processes easier around here for the past 20 years. And 

Speaker 8  (16:16)
It's half, it's gonna happen this year. 

Speaker 11  (16:19)
I wouldn't hold my breat. 

Speaker 7  (16:24)
All right, so mainframe, lfa capability, so this is quite outdated. Oh, my gosh. There has been a decision I think mark you were going to check with. 

Speaker 8  (16:38)
Weighing and 

Speaker 7  (16:40)
Others on the US front door. So, do you want to provide any updates on that one? 

Speaker 9  (16:46)
Yeah, sure, we're talking about. Pushing or forcing people who are not using the Kix application. Which is a very small minority of these are population to use Z net like we do in Canada, in order to access those non-business applications. 

Speaker 9  (17:12)
All right, and we're socializing it with the with the US teams and gathering the stakeholders, it's already been explained to them. They don't see an issue initially with it. Within their user communities, but they're reaching out to make sure that we've got everyone included. 

Speaker 9  (17:35)
All right, so a number of folks in the US do use easynet, but it's just not mandatory. Okay, so the intent is for the those logging onto kicksteck. To have no change in the way they do so today. 

Speaker 9  (17:53)
At any level, they'll be mfaid when they log into Kix. But if you're trying to get to any other application, any other vtam application within the US environment, then you're going to be forced again through easynet. Mandatory front door for nonetheless, applications 

Speaker 6  (18:16)
And this was penmark, this was approved by 

Speaker 9  (18:21)
While we're still discussing it right, so that was the that's the proposal. But we're discussing it with the business executives in the US. 

Speaker 6  (18:34)
And who are the business executives in the US? This is 

Speaker 9  (18:38)
Jackie and Manny and the pet plus team, those kind of the people who were accountable for the primary Business Services with t 

Speaker 6  (18:52)
And weighing and branwoods are both aware 

Speaker 9  (18:55)
But they're involved, yeah, they 're actively engaged in the communication themselves. Okay. 

Speaker 6  (19:03)
Okay, now so mark that as a discussion that's going on Andrew. And the decision, so there's a couple of decisions in there, right? 1st decision is to whether or not the host engineering team is going to proceed with that. 

Speaker 6  (19:21)
Second one is when it's going to it's. It has not been included in any scope for this project, right? So we have to get agreement as to terms. 

Speaker 9  (19:48)
I've already built the working prototype to verify that we can redirect logons through that environment. And it's working properly as expected. I've, we've communicated within that initial kickoff. 

Speaker 9  (20:06)
With the stakeholders, we've provided them insight into how the ABC screen will change. Then, the lock on screen that people see when they connect into the US and Add-on a little bit of an insight into what's coming down there, you know, coming their way soon, because I don't think all of them are aware Of the mfa project and its implications to their work groups. 

Speaker 7  (20:46)
Deciding here that this is the pentagon broadcom. 

Speaker 9  (20:51)
Yeah, so broadcom just is a quick update. They're expected to deliver the code to Jay on Monday. 

Speaker 7  (20:59)
Have they committed mark? 

Speaker 9  (21:01)
No, that was their their saying that that would be their forecast as to when they'll deliver A. We'll be on Monday of next week upon his return. 

Speaker 10  (21:12)
Mark mark, did they have the security access fixed? 

Speaker 9  (21:15)
No, they're still working on that, I okay. So I'm okay, so that's right. It'll be sometime early next week, right? 

Speaker 9  (21:22)
So there is a concern that it would be weeks out or months out, but It sounds like they're going to be able to deliver that in early part of next week. When Jack gets back And then it should only take us a couple of days to shake it down and make sure it works, and then we'll be able to check off that box. Yeah, you have to 

Speaker 7  (21:55)
I know there was some back-and-forth and continuous updates when we were looking in France, but maybe this one will be simple. So what's left for a test flex? You then 

Speaker 9  (22:09)
Nothing. 

Speaker 7  (22:14)
So you've done your POC mark, and then now we're Ready to go to Netflix. You And we're not gonna test om. 

Speaker 9  (22:24)
And we put plaque seve in yesterday Tim and Hassan worked on that, and got it stood up and deview. We weren't planning to test the msoth, because Paul's going to be building new servers for that purpose. But Tim played with the UB key capability, since that's native. 

Speaker 9  (22:48)
Within the environment. 

Speaker 7  (22:50)
That's not working yet. 

Speaker 9  (22:51)
Okay, we haven't got it working yet, but But we'll import the keys and be able to do and confirm that's working properly. There's no errors coming up in the product startup, so It looks all clean. We'll just complete some testing there and we'll let you know when that's done, yeah. 

Speaker 9  (23:18)
I do not want to sleeve the promotion eventually up into production in both Canada and the USA. 

Speaker 7  (23:26)
Beth, a mark we discussed a couple days ago like some timelines. Do you have an E Tl when those will be provided? 

Speaker 9  (23:34)
We've always said we need to start the activity a month before, we're looking to complete all right, so if we're looking to complete before the end of fiscal year fiscal year end say, maybe the weekend of if we arbitrarily pick the weekend, I think it's 17th or the 15th. Then, we would need to start that promotion up to production on September 15th. 

Speaker 6  (24:03)
Why don't we work on trying to get ahead of it? 

Speaker 9  (24:06)
Well, we can't I'm saying, these would be the deadlines. Right? We were saying, if usually like to work backwards to say, what's the latest date that we could start something and be confident of completion, so that was kind of the way I was envisioning it, but certainly, we'll go ahead and do the setup before then. 

Speaker 9  (24:26)
Just that's, I'm saying the latest that we can start it and still be confident. 

Speaker 7  (24:33)
Yeah, but I think mark you were going to send an email right? 

Speaker 9  (24:37)
I was just going to describe that that we what remains is really the nps testing. From our perspective and the And then just enough time to promote the code app 2000 will be the only timelines I can really provide, right? And the idea would be, of course, to go as strange as described right not to wait until the that date arrives to go ahead. 

Speaker 9  (25:11)
And And initiate those activities now that can be done without any dependencies. 

Speaker 7  (25:26)
And are you saying that we We'll be going to production with or without NPS or NPS is a hard dependency. 

Speaker 9  (25:34)
Well, nps is a dependency for Microsoft authenticator. All right, so if we don't have that working or tested, then we wouldn't be able to deploy that capability in production right, it would become a ub only mental. Such time is that testing was completed and then we could enable it. 

Speaker 9  (26:04)
So we know we can do UP independently if the NP SMS off, so That would be kind of the minimum threshold to say it was deployed from my perspective. 

Speaker 7  (26:27)
And then Jordan, we're still working through some of this R and R. For day, 2. I just needed a writing basically. 

Speaker 8  (26:38)
Yeah, one of the things that has been done right as you know, from yesterday is I got the ticket open to Ahmed's team and gave them some sample data for the reports we need from amh that will have the Iraq F2 to upn mapping. 

Speaker 9  (26:55)
Yeah, and did that sound promising, Jordan that they may be able to provide 

Speaker 8  (27:00)
Yet, they reached out to me within 5 minutes, opening it and got a priority, isn't everything that was needed, so they're going to be working on it. 

Speaker 7  (27:27)
For traffic manager, traffic manager, although anything else for me. 

Speaker 11  (27:44)
So just a question Andrew, were we able to get the a simple of the report? For the power BI for main 

Speaker 7  (27:55)
Yeah, Jordan and I were just briefly discussing that yesterday think we're going to be leveraging one of the reports that's required, I think the one that you just mentioned Jordan, and that should list out all the main users, right? 

Speaker 8  (28:17)
Yes, no, right. So for that, I think I'd have to add some extra data if we want to, like, identify all active manframe users from that port from amh. I mean, there's other 

Speaker 5  (28:32)
The requirement isn't just active mainframe users, right? It's what they've got, what they have configured in mainframe for MF. A. 

Speaker 8  (28:39)
Yeah, that's A 

Speaker 5  (28:41)
That certain thing 

Speaker 8  (28:42)
Yeah, that's a separate report, and actually that would capture that. 

Speaker 5  (28:46)
Yeah, it's a much more detailed requirement than just who's an 8 frame user, though I'm sure that's relevant, but if you're going to ask for a much more detail, you might as well. 

Speaker 8  (28:55)
Yeah, I get acquired when I present the report and I give requirements for that right like I wanted to report from both days 15 rackf that had all the users their status, what factors that were enrolled in? Because you want to be able to report on that. 

Speaker 7  (29:15)
Yeah, Jordan, I think I sent an email on the exact ask. 

Speaker 1  (29:27)
I was just blowing it up now. 

Speaker 7  (29:30)
Okay, it's really the metrics basically for the entire project team here, we're trying to build out dashboarding for the enterprise rollout, similar to when those local business, and so we just need an ongoing report to list of the All the main prime users, so you can figure out what methods they have etc. 

Speaker 5  (29:57)
Right today, I also say that, and maybe I didn't respond to green enough detail, but it's like we don't just need to know all mainframe users right, and they specifically know about their mfa status. In addition to whether their mainframe user is the mfa status and mainframe, you won't be able to get from the ID reports. Oh, right, whether they're configured to use msaws. 

Speaker 5  (30:19)
In mainframe would mean that you had bed, then you would want to look up the ant ID information whether the user has fs off and figured entreaty, but if they're The fairies you have a king and on the mainframe, then it has nothing to do with that ubiquitous setup and a trid, though you'd expect them to be correlated. But it's technically independent that you can and then mainstream has an internal variable that says Denotes, whether someone has configured to use nsf or ubiquit. I would have had it, and I don't A little more involved, but you should have all those data points if you want to do analysis. 

Speaker 9  (31:02)
And does that Paul provide you with the upn value that you're looking for on your end? 

Speaker 5  (31:09)
My requirement is that I get that in the in coming transaction for rockets, so that's not a reporting requirement. 

Speaker 8  (31:15)
Yeah, like I said those are two separate process, let's not mix them up right? That's giving VPN is so we can assign that when users profile, and we set them up for set of a second requirement is for us to go everybody. We have an accept tune rackf, are the, you know? 

Speaker 8  (31:30)
What's their mfa, status? What factor are they using? Are the active etc? 

Speaker 8  (31:34)
I did write a user story with requirements for that. 

Speaker 9  (31:40)
Because I thought that was something that Brian was and Tim were working on to build reporting around the status of mfa users on the platform. 

Speaker 8  (31:50)
Yeah, I believe they are yeah. 

Speaker 10  (31:53)
That's one of the 6 

Speaker 5  (31:57)
Development efforts. 

Speaker 9  (32:00)
All right, so yeah, to show that right to say these are the mainframe users and here is their mfa status. 

Speaker 10  (32:08)
Yeah, so there's a few you know, things that you know will come up. You know, like like what all users are going to be eligible to be emethate you know, we're going to have users that are in Suspense suspense dates, canceled states. Don't are they going to be, you know, mf? 

Speaker 10  (32:30)
8 as part of the big Bang. 

Speaker 8  (32:34)
I've seen the fall back in my career well. We are doing some cleanup, right? So I mean, ideally we should have, you know, active users right would be, it would be Emma Fang, but yeah, man I don't want to redo derail the skull. 

Speaker 8  (32:47)
A bunch of that would fall into our enterprise rollout plan. 

Speaker 9  (32:53)
As you're hoping, this team is able to somehow extract Insight, from the mainframe acf, 2 and rockf database is part of their reporting. 

Speaker 8  (33:04)
Yes 

Speaker 10  (33:05)
So we'll definitely be able to report on On huall is enrolled The blood factor is active. 

Speaker 7  (33:19)
Okay, anything else to remain firm? I just want to move on quickly. 

Speaker 10  (33:24)
So you have If you don't have a caption somewhere else you've got all the development efforts going on. You know, the panel's been corrected the ingestion processes. 

Speaker 7  (33:38)
I mean, we can add a bullet point here. 

Speaker 10  (33:41)
I don't have to I just want to, you know, highlight, you know, that that's At least six different development efforts. And then Fiscal activity You need to go or cleanup in the ongoing cleanup. 

Speaker 7  (34:07)
All the time. Cleanup anything else, Brian. 

Speaker 10  (34:19)
Mine, that's not a we've got further breakdown, you know, if it's record 

Speaker 7  (34:24)
Okay, sounds good. All right, Jane, you mentioned that the msa is moving along. Here we go. 

Speaker 6  (34:40)
Yes, yes, it's moving along. Mom, they are looking at Other quadrant. Gardner, quadrant. 

Speaker 6  (34:55)
Entities, to see if they can validate the prices that came back, they're also working with You would go to downgrade the to get a 2 year quote, which is something ubico, said that they couldn't do, but SSG and vm has somehow managed to get that out of or at least get in ubico, working on that, so we are making progress, and I think I saw mic on the phone, we do have to look into Mike, how to start the spid process, if your side is similar to ours, so we just want to get ahead of that, to make sure that's a place when we finally do get confirmation from venture management. 

Speaker 12  (35:44)
Yeah, so I was wondering, I think that that stuff's coming up soon once we get contracts on. 

Speaker 6  (35:53)
Yes, yes, and they were the ones who suggested we'd get ahead of it and start working on it. 

Speaker 12  (36:00)
I'm just seeing, I need to go and put a pnt in for the 1.15, then 

Speaker 6  (36:08)
Yeah, well you have to, you have to start the, I don't know. I think there may be precursor events that have to start in. That's that. 

Speaker 12  (36:17)
Tnt submission, I'll go. It's like dizzy, bad out and start the dance. 

Speaker 5  (36:24)
Yeah 

Speaker 6  (36:26)
But that is that is moving. 

Speaker 7  (36:31)
Got great. Thank you. Was Jeremy still here? 

Speaker 7  (36:39)
Okay, yes? Great, okay. So 502 I guess the discussion around use cases working with Anthony S that gone? 

Speaker 1  (36:54)
Slower than I'd like it to go, but it's going It's going right now, we've been working through several things, we've actually been working with Shaquille from ubico, as well on what the Bible options are, we've generated a bunch of questions for retail, I know that you just provide a vaccine information about setting up a dedicated call, we've been working with Anthony yesterday and today we've been having sessions pretty much every day with Anthony and have been working through kind of formatting the functional use cases to review with retail, so we can, you know, finish Or we can account for those properly in the in the design flows for those use cases right? 

Speaker 1  (37:37)
And so we've put a lot of focus more recently into lost stolen broken keys because that seemed to be one of the biggest pain points where we have the most gaps. And I've been formuling options for that. So the couple of the key takeaways is that for the moment, we are going to be meeting with retail, I think, that you have something set app with Canadian retail, but we need to also do this with US retail, mostly to validate our assumptions and ask some additional questions about the functional use cases that we're working with that helps very much inform how we're going to or what decisions we're going to make from a design perspective on how we ship keys to new users, where they go and how they get instantiated. 

Speaker 1  (38:24)
So I believe that you've already set up one of those calls. And then we also have a call with ubico, based on the lost stolen key recovery with their product group that Shaquille is hoping to facilitate because we do see some specific gaps around how we register a key for a user or register a spare key for a user. And ubico has some capabilities that they're working on, that might address that scenario for us in a better way than the options that we were looking at. 

Speaker 1  (38:59)
So We, I believe we have that meeting getting scheduled as well. 

Speaker 7  (39:05)
Okay, do you mind just including Jane and I and those as well. 

Speaker 1  (39:10)
In the meeting with ubico 

Speaker 7  (39:12)
I like Janie wanted to be On some of those items 

Speaker 6  (39:21)
Yeah, but if I can go, I'll go if I can't go well. 

Speaker 1  (39:26)
Yeah, that's that's fine. You know, that's definitely more exploratory, Jane. But yes, we are eventually going to have to go through kind of the flows that we've been documenting with you and talk about some of the pain points, and there definitely, you know, some of the options are more painful than others. 

Speaker 1  (39:48)
We definitely want to sync up on these things. We're going to have to get to end a job on what options we have and where we want to take that, because then I'm very positive that retail is going to have some feedback, right if we're asking their managers to do something like, install a ub and roll app on their mobile. Device, which I'm not advocated for by the way. 

Speaker 1  (40:09)
Or you know, handle some sort of Request or delivery process, like it does change the experience, and it does put ownership on the managers and etc, like any way we swing this managing spare keys, is a task that they don't do today that they will be doing in the future, and so we 're gonna have to be kind. Of sensitive to that and determine how we manage that and how we present that and what that looks like, so we need to very much crystallize on what our options are, and my anticipation is that you know, retail will have some input to that. 

Speaker 8  (40:46)
Yeah, I just want to add Jeremy like from a madeframe side too. We want to understand the flow for this because obviously for retail, we need to be exactly in tune, because we have a little bit because with mainframe right. If you lost your key, you then have to be like deenrolled on the zmfa side and then register, and we'll have to figure out how that process works from that end. 

Speaker 1  (41:06)
Yeah, and I want to note Jordan and Jane that we still need to talk about some enterprise, protect control requirements for keys that we don't have today that also informs the design right, and so I think I don't know who's taking primary on that again. Jane, I don't know. I don't know if we've engaged control Partners yet, but like there are definitely things like, for example, if somebody loses their key, we should be clearing the opt method so that way somebody else couldn't, because when you have physical position of the key, that's a bad thing, right? 

Speaker 1  (41:39)
So we need to likely, you know, have a control standard that dictates that as part of registering a Fido key, we're killing the old key, for example, right or that we have a process to kill the old key, is kooky is possible, because identified as lost or stolen right, and there's other controls around you. Know pain length and a whole bunch of other stuff that we absolutely should should dictate that we don't have well documented from a control standard for today. 

Speaker 8  (42:09)
If I recall correctly, I think our penlet says 4 characters, which I think the EV key minimum is 6 Brett, so I may Dix seat that, but the only reason it's 4 is because of All right, say, and the fact that our auditors don't really know what a pin is. 

Speaker 10  (42:29)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (42:31)
It's starting more to it than that right? Like, yeah, we have to talk about Yeah, there's other things I won't get into it on this call. But there's a bunch of other things that we have to think about, when it comes to pre-registered keys, how we actually communicate the pin to people. 

Speaker 1  (42:47)
And things like that that are going to matter right where we ship the keys to whether or not we can ship it to someone's home, whether or not you know, delivery signature is required by the recipient of the key, you know, like all of those things, right, like there's a there's a bunch of stuff to discuss here. And that will definitely inform the design and the flow right, like if we can't ship it to someone's house, that it's a big difference. That means we have to solution, how the hell we figure out where a retail person is starting, right? 

Speaker 1  (43:19)
You know, and if they're not starting at their HR job location, if they're starting at a training center at a different store or something, then how do they get in their key, right? And part of the definition of that is that, if the controls dictate certain things that limit our ability to ship a key to a person because of the retail use case Then, the answer might be that we cannot pre-register keys right? And we have to register them in person with the person who's there, and we have to manage it through a spare pool, and that completely changes the design right? 

Speaker 1  (43:53)
Yeah. 

Speaker 7  (43:55)
It's made, Jerry. There is also AUS retail. Touch point, it's the same day. 

Speaker 7  (44:02)
It's at like 430 on Tuesdays. I included yourself and Anthony and those 

Speaker 11  (44:09)
Sorry, Andrew. Can you include me as well, please? 

Speaker 7  (44:12)
Yes, yes, I can do that. 

Speaker 1  (44:19)
So yeah, it's gonna be unfortunately Andrew, I know. This has been a bit more of a marathon than a sprint. There's a lot of pieces to it. 

Speaker 1  (44:28)
If you look at Anthony's documentation, there's just a ton of stuff out there because there's there's a lot of moving parts to this one, it's complicated. 

Speaker 7  (44:36)
Yeah And then what about this discussion on the onboarding portal? Because I don't think this is the ID long-term solution, is not It's not likely happening for IDV. 

Speaker 1  (44:49)
What do you mean by not likely happening? 

Speaker 7  (44:53)
Jane's still not in scope right for next year. 

Speaker 6  (44:56)
Hasn't been funded for next year, hasn't been funded yet for next year. 

Speaker 1  (45:01)
Yeah, I think I think that was like, there's. It is amazing how credibly stupid art. 

Speaker 6  (45:08)
I I put that forward And I did not get much of a response 

Speaker 8  (45:16)
It was like literally the day after you said, we absolutely need this Jeremy, they 're like they' re not funding it. 

Speaker 1  (45:24)
Like II you know, like how many times I've been here too long, right? Because how many times in my tenure do I have to stand up and say this is going to be an audit finding where you're going to get a thematic for this, only to be ignored over and over again. And asked for funding and being ignored, and then we get a thematic, and then we have to work a 100 hours a week for a year and a 1 to resolve the thematic, because they wouldn't f****** listen to me. 

Speaker 1  (45:52)
Like, how many times do we have to do this? A 

Speaker 6  (45:57)
Yeah, we can. We can discuss, but they 

Speaker 1  (46:01)
We're giving up high assurance of dedicators to people without verifying them. I told them that it's common freaking sense. 

Speaker 6  (46:08)
I told them that, and the response was just as we've said. We'ren't interested in funding it. 

Speaker 1  (46:24)
Do I have to go like? Do I need an audience with Steve sparks? 

Speaker 6  (46:31)
I There was an audience with Steve sparks, and he did turn it down. 

Speaker 1  (46:40)
That is like 

Speaker 7  (46:43)
So when you watch what 

Speaker 1  (46:44)
Hardly turn that's unbelievable I just don't understand. 

Speaker 6  (46:49)
I ask for an explanation as well. And I got nothing. 

Speaker 12  (46:54)
So he doesn't want an onboarding portal. 

Speaker 1  (46:57)
No, it's not about the opera portal. It's about ID verification. 

Speaker 12  (47:04)
I'm sure you guys don't want to identity proof. 

Speaker 6  (47:09)
I mean, there is Lack of funding. 

Speaker 5  (47:14)
There's lack of 

Speaker 1  (47:16)
There's lack of understanding that is like 

Speaker 7  (47:24)
So, Jeremy, like, what do we do like that? What is that 

Speaker 1  (47:26)
I don't know. I honestly don't know Let's just hand out keys to people and send them f****** pins to their personal emails. I guess we don't need to verify them. 

Speaker 1  (47:36)
It's trust me, bro, that's our approach now. Sure, right. Like what a what do we do? 

Speaker 12  (47:44)
We invented a secret handshake. 

Speaker 1  (47:51)
What do we do if everyone agrees that it's a problem but they don't want to do anything about it? What do we do, Jane? 

Speaker 6  (47:59)
I can't, well, I'm gonna take it back to Theresa yet again. To make sure that she knows what the issue is, she knows what the problem is. 

Speaker 1  (48:07)
But that has means to yourself, and Jordan, is that now, you're going to have to make concessions, we cannot deliver pins to people securely with the upcoming VDI initiatives, and stuff where we need to move people from, trusted to untrusted, we have no way to verify them, we're just gonna have to send them Send them starter passwords and send them pins, and where you have no way to really effectively verify them. And you're, you're dissuading OTP and you're standard, but that's the only option we have In Louisville. 

Speaker 6  (48:42)
I recognize all of that. We can talk about it offline. We can talk about it offline, so don't worry anything up anymore. 

Speaker 7  (48:55)
Okay, and then just quickly the last piece here Jeremy, you were working with Ben, yep, sorry about all 

Speaker 5  (49:03)
I'm not skip over right onboard. So I write long-term ID solution is one thing. But the onboarding point just to right we do that is going to be even if there was a long-term ID solution being implemented. 

Speaker 5  (49:16)
That's made some sort of portal sooner, right? 

Speaker 1  (49:21)
The intent is that we know that for the ID solution, we need an onboarding portal, and the intent would be that we would initially start to implement the onboarding portal early for the purposes of Security registration with the intent that we would plug the IDD piece into that if there is going to be no ID. V then we have to question whether or not we build this at all because now we have to look at what the alternative is okay. Right? 

Speaker 1  (49:50)
So yes, I mean, we can still discuss building the onboarding portal and we can still discuss using, you know, one time password as a as a verification, but then what that becomes our permanent solution right now it already violates our control standards, so you're going to have to adjust your control standard. 

Speaker 6  (50:19)
Yeah I don't know what the we will we? 

Speaker 1  (50:25)
Perhaps we have no path to get people in the front door. 

Speaker 8  (50:29)
Guys. 

Speaker 7  (50:36)
Jeremy were able to work with Ben on some of those test cases. 

Speaker 1  (50:41)
Ben is on, I think I heard from Paul and Jonathan that we were able to test the primary thing that I wanted to test, which was we confirmed that with a pre-registered phyto key for a user logging into a new machine for the first time, they do not need a password, which is a massive massive win, right? It means that you can get issued a pre-registered Fido key, you can plug it into a new machine as a new user, and you can log in with no password. So we don't have to communicate a starter password. 

Speaker 1  (51:17)
We don't have to log you in one time before we set app your fighto key, you're able to do this for the first time. It makes our It makes our first day use case for retail, much simpler. 

Speaker 5  (51:30)
Which is, can I just give a double-check Ben? Is that true, that was my impression from job, and that I just want to make sure that my mistake experi? 

Speaker 3  (51:40)
My test was with my own account and on a brand new machine. So yes, I was able to get to the brand new machine, but I'm an existing user, and I had already set up my pin on my ub and key and everything. 

Speaker 1  (51:53)
Yeah, we want to try the new use case Ben, and we hope there's a few other flavors of that that I wanted to test that I had documented some test cases for 

Speaker 8  (52:01)
Yeah, I have a question too like, I guess it's part of this because it's actually very good point. When I think that's a great user experience, right? And I wear initial password. 

Speaker 8  (52:08)
And you get your key plug it in. It's also means that we're going to have to do a bunch of changes to our existing jointer flow and amh round. Past, yes, to the things like that. 

Speaker 8  (52:16)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (52:17)
Suspect Jordan, we need to talk about first time pin issuance Vs first time password issuance, and then we also have to talk about how you set your password for things that still need a password, which we have a few of you of. 

Speaker 8  (52:30)
And apparently I'm sure people remember your password, because I heard that's A 

Speaker 1  (52:35)
That's a problem as well. Yeah And honestly, like I don't hate that problem though Jordan, right? 

Speaker 8  (52:44)
Well, actually, Kim windows hello store. Have we looked at using windows hello, to just store your password. I mean, that's another thing you can do. 

Speaker 1  (52:51)
But we're not using manisalo, for most of our retail use. 

Speaker 8  (52:55)
I may not retail, but other I'm people. 

Speaker 1  (52:59)
I'm not sure that's how it works, Jordan. I guess allow replaces the password. It doesn't store it. 

Speaker 1  (53:08)
There is a there is a profiles. Yeah, there is a profile 

Speaker 8  (53:14)
Yeah, like sorry, anything like a password, man. 

Speaker 1  (53:16)
Manager or something or yeah, there is a Google Chrome password manager that we've looked at, which is not windows or windows hello. There is a native Google Chrome password manager that we looked at to replace the net IQ one that was in use by US. There was never a decision that was made to move forward with that, but we haven't looked at that. 

Speaker 1  (53:38)
Okay, there's also I know that unmanaged cyberarch solution that's going in, but it doesn't really work as a password storage mechanism. It's more of a reference safe, right? 

Speaker 7  (53:50)
I do want to move on with 5 minutes, but Jeremy band are you guys working on additional test cases on this or 

Speaker 1  (53:59)
There are additional test cases that we do need to do Ben. 

Speaker 3  (54:04)
Yeah, is there a document for that? I don't there is 

Speaker 1  (54:08)
Yeah, I'll pay you. I'll ping you that. 

Speaker 3  (54:12)
Is there a way to provision my ub T that I have, in my hand like as a first time test scenario, like with a 10 pin and stuff. 

Speaker 1  (54:24)
I'll ask a good question, I don't know how to Repin a ubq. Well, actually, you can clear the key in windows. 

Speaker 8  (54:31)
Right industry set up window 

Speaker 1  (54:32)
Yes 

Speaker 3  (54:33)
Install the ubico desktop app and played around with. I don't know if i' 

Speaker 1  (54:37)
You don't, you don't need that you could go to stop app. You can actually do it natively in windows, okay? There's a flow for that Jonathan and I'm on vacation next week. 

Speaker 1  (54:46)
But Jonathan and Paul and manice are aware of that. 

Speaker 13  (54:49)
But that clear is just keeping my clears all the credentials, just mix it as a brand new key. So if you have any other accounts on it, just be careful on 

Speaker 3  (54:58)
Yeah, I'm gonna, he wipes just for the time being I mentioned Jonathan earlier. Yeah, so I'd looked at some of the cases there and I had to remove myself from debaske temporarily, just because we're dealing with some fraud issues, so I'll have to everything's kind. Of cleared right now on my account. 

Speaker 3  (55:13)
I'll get set it up whenever though. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (55:15)
And Ben, you can't set We can set a temporary pit. I'll work with you on that. 

Speaker 3  (55:26)
The man was next week, gets an England or Tuesday, but 

Speaker 4  (55:30)
Let you stay. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 7  (55:35)
I'd very quickly, Jeremy. We're working on Q4 AI planning for custom claims. I think the goal was to do the design and try to get sit completed or debit Dev and sit. 

Speaker 7  (55:49)
I'm not sure that we'll be able to do that in the next two weeks, and then I was curious what the plan is for Q4 is it to promote all the way to Prague? 

Speaker 1  (55:59)
Yeah, so we're, we're essentially there, from a Dev perspective. Actually, we've been able to simulate the traffic. We actually found a way to simulate the request coming from entry ID and simulate the response coming back. 

Speaker 1  (56:15)
We can't do the full end handshake, but we did have that conversation with the ridge one that you were involved in. We're working to get AB so engaged to move forward with that. Do I think we'll be complete by the end of Q3 at this point, just because of the stuff, we have to set up and the exceptions, we have to get and etc. 

Speaker 1  (56:32)
No I think that there's still a little bit of work, but the rest of the PPI itself is good. It's the other pieces like getting the network pieces in place, and the entry ID stuff Paul I did reach out to you earlier, we're kind of at the point where we're ready to engage with the nraid side of stuff, so I did add you to the AZ CP chat and told ash to connect with you. 

Speaker 5  (56:54)
Yep, I saw I did want to confirm. So the custom claims are that also includes the rhone and the database elements right? 

Speaker 1  (57:01)
It does, yeah, so we have simulated data in a database. Now we have not done the rajone integration yet, and that wouldn't happen in Dev. Anyway, that's gonna happen in prad. 

Speaker 5  (57:11)
Oh, there's not going to be anything. 

Speaker 1  (57:14)
No, we can't put, we can't even get the user data that's in rohana is not available in debits, only available in prad, right? And we can't put user data in Deb. So we're lately, data in Dev. 

Speaker 1  (57:30)
There's actually a conversation to be had there about, like, what happens if there's an app that needs custom plays provider. Where do they get their data? And the answer is, is they actually will not be able to get that data in Dev. 

Speaker 1  (57:42)
Those claims they will have to get it in Pat and hire and I actually have to talk to their own team about whether or not we can even get the data in Pat, to be honest. 

Speaker 5  (57:50)
That's definitely a challenge for developers that was going to be my first question. If there's not even a mockup data on that or well yes, we, but we just have a database there that we can, we can throw stuff into that might be representative of what they're in prads. And where we make it 

Speaker 1  (58:08)
And talk about airbustness, where, like, we can let them load We can let them input something that would just load in data for sample data for a test account or something 

Speaker 5  (58:18)
Yeah, okay. Sorry, no, that's we would. I would say, we would need that right. 

Speaker 5  (58:23)
Otherwise, developers are just going to be flying blind. 

Speaker 1  (58:26)
I'm painfully aware of our detriments in Dev, especially as it relates to that and also like SaaS based applications. So Andrew to answer your question, I know we're at a time, the ideal scenario would be to get this done in Q4, the the pain points for this at the moment will mostly be how long it's going to take rajona, to work with us, which I don't have an answer. For yet, but once, I have that settled better, then we'll be able to have a clear answer at this point I think that we're projecting that we should be good by the end of Q4. 

Speaker 7  (59:11)
Sounds good extremely thanks. Everybody. And we'll We appreciate it. 

Speaker 6  (59:19)
But Goodbye, that's 
