
Speaker 1  (00:00)
It's including Jeremy, to discuss kind of the use cases that they've been working on and kind of brought some questions to inform. Or from the business perspective, so we have Anthony on the line. And I know you've been working closely with Jeremy on those use cases. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
I'm wondering if you 

Speaker 2  (00:22)
Who wanted? 

Speaker 1  (00:23)
To share any of the progress that you've been working out of working on otherwise, I think Jeremy and left us with a few questions and items to discuss for today's meeting. 

Speaker 3  (00:34)
Take hi, good morning, good afternoon, Andrew. We have not officially released any stories. As of yet. 

Speaker 3  (00:51)
The crux of the meeting, I guess we'll have to center around the questions that Jeremy sent you. Okay, we do have a lot of written documentation all over the place right now we are hoping to share this not only with you but also with the ubiko vendor as such, hopefully, within the next 2 or 3 days we do have a very structured, this thing outward right now. I'll just give you A A quick review as to what I have been working on. 

Speaker 3  (01:31)
Okay. Our focus has been across two major journeys, new hire and lost broken, and found we do have material that we have to groom right now. Okay, let's put it that way it is not groomed. 

Speaker 3  (01:52)
We do have diagrams, which everybody likes to see, you know, we are drafting this so that we can share it with the general audience soon and come and get your opinions and feedback. But right now, I think at least for today. Let's focus at least on my part of things. 

Speaker 3  (02:14)
It's going to be focus on the questions that Jeremy has sent, because I'm not officially entitled to share this. I'm just giving you a little peek. Mix 

Speaker 1  (02:28)
Yeah, that makes sense. So I guess just an update to our uh U. Colleagues here at the candidate retail side were working through detailed use cases still, so Anthony was just traveling that with Jeremy Bernard and Jeremy couldn't make it for this call, but he left us with a couple more questions, some of which you may have briefly discussed in some of our former conversations. 

Speaker 1  (02:56)
But I'll see if I can bring this up. Maybe I don't know if anybody has any questions before we dive into those. Chris John Eric Bryant. 

Speaker 4  (03:10)
Nothing for me. 

Speaker 5  (03:16)
Nothing at this point. 

Speaker 1  (03:21)
So now, it's good, we'll just pull up those questions. 

Speaker 1  (03:34)
I love something in the uh. 

Speaker 2  (03:40)
On that page. 

Speaker 1  (03:48)
Excuse me, 1 second. 

Speaker 6  (03:56)
Okay, there we go. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
The first question that was provided was around Where does the retail worker start their first day? So what does day one look like? Do they start in the breakup room? 

Speaker 1  (04:20)
Or off the floor is there a training center at the teller line? Can somebody please help us understand that? 

Speaker 6  (04:35)
And sort of where do these questions originate from? 

Speaker 1  (04:39)
This one's coming from Jeremy Bernardo one of our architects. 

Speaker 6  (04:44)
So okay. So we may need, I think, directionally, we can answer some of these, but I think we'll need Partners support to nail down on some of these. Okay, like that, we worked through this like so dimi's on our team, she would have I'm just trying to remember who would have an intake would have been submitted for this. 

Speaker 7  (05:13)
Yeah, we already have one. 

Speaker 6  (05:15)
Okay, an intake into cbb retail, yeah. Oh, okay. So as part of that intake, partner resources are assigned That we can pull and answer these questions. 

Speaker 6  (05:26)
So yeah, we don't really own training or first day type activities, so that's what we'll only tell somebody else. 

Speaker 7  (05:33)
Do you have a name, Eric that we can maybe add to the index that can help us. 

Speaker 6  (05:39)
Now, dimi will have the name. She's just on PTO right now, okay? Yeah, so it should be the technically the lead here in terms of that type of working activity. 

Speaker 6  (05:48)
So she'll corral the cpb resources or just go and get the information. And then so, but it's just so I understand the bigger objective here. Maybe be able to sleep at that, so what I'll feel at yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (06:12)
I can. I could feel as a bigger picture. Yeah We have just so many so many different scenarios, and when we talk about The ubique, the UB itself. 

Speaker 2  (06:26)
Yeah, right. So this identity, how do we? How do we establish, you know, this key as belonging to the To that person and what those flows look like, and we've described, you know, many times at a high level. 

Speaker 2  (06:41)
About about these keys, and when you get rate down into the details, there's things like, okay, do we ship that key to the branch, and then the branch, you know, someone at the branch, give it to the user, for instance right, or you know what, there are too many different scenarios where that just doesn't cut it, so we need to ship that key directly to the user before their first day. Yeah, so we're so we get we get into, we get into these and so, so then we've also learned scenarios where The employee may actually start It's 4 before they're in the system. 

Speaker 2  (07:27)
Like, before Which sounds really weird to me, but apparently this can be a thing, right? We're all we're all used to a corporate world where your date is, you know, whatever 15 days 30 days ahead and all the processes get to work properly, but we understand that's not always the case, and sometimes those lead times aren't there? Right, so in that perfect world where hey, there's lots of time and we can send that person that The ubiquitates at their home address, and then they, you know, arrive for wherever their first day is. 

Speaker 2  (08:05)
That may not always work, so if that doesn't work, how do we account for that and yeah. 

Speaker 5  (08:12)
So Jonathan just, yeah, and sorry, Eric for piping in here. This is where we get into operational policy and procedure and outside of lnd. That, you know, Trish Rossi Victoria Harris team would want to pipe in and influence this Oh, the second part Jonathan is I think you know the question is valid, but we want to step back up a level and basically say, okay. 

Speaker 5  (08:50)
If somebody loses their key Do they have to wait for somebody to ship it? Or does the branch have a supply of them that they can assign to an individual? And And in that particular case, it eliminates all of those other use cases of having to ship a USB key to the individual before they actually start, because the branch is provisioned with them. 

Speaker 5  (09:20)
And then it becomes more of a question of okay, if we provision the branch day, one with so many. Then what do we do day 2, how do they request more? What's the shipping time? 

Speaker 5  (09:35)
Is there a cost? Who's responsible for ordering them and making sure that they're available in inventory to be supplied, what is the tool available to reassign? That USB you know, if someone quits or leaves or moves positions, and they leave their USB key at the branch, can it be reused, can it be a reassigned to somebody, how does the branch keep track of the USB keys? 

Speaker 5  (10:03)
And who's assigned to what those are? The, you know, the questions that start to influence the use cases and the solutions as opposed to the specific questions. 

Speaker 2  (10:16)
Yeah, you got it and every single thing you said there were talking about. 

Speaker 6  (10:22)
Yeah, so I'm wondering if yeah, in a couple of things, one being I think cause I don't remember where we parked the car and I know like we did talk about the UB last time. I think I had some questions about like what the work back looked like to get to end of job on this is a solution because I assume there's some gates in there, right? That involve I'm going to say us, but I'd even say more. 

Speaker 6  (10:48)
So John and Chris on this team, too. But anyways, like how we're getting from a to Z on. Yep, it's ub, and all the right Nope, say executives agree on the solution, and this is probably part of that, but it 'd be helpful for me to understand how we're going from a to Z and then to this laundry list of questions, I think what's going to very quickly happen is these 4 questions are going to turn into 40 questions as soon as we start talking. 

Speaker 6  (11:16)
So if there is a opportunity to even share these over and again, I'm going to point to demean, he will be back next week to share these over, and then I think we could set up a series with the expectation that this is what we're going to work through right, like the onboarding experience if that's what the topic is here or you know, being blown out if there's more to it, but at Brian's point I think you've got multiple Partners that are coming to the table on. The operationalization of this one, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (11:47)
Yeah, for the workpack workback aspect, certainly that Alta Andrew, for all of you know, these little details, these, it's probably hundreds of them at the end of the day, but for the onboarding for the recovery, the different scenarios. Yeah, where we've got, we've got way too many of them and You know, we want to simplify. Ultimately what I expect what I expect we will arrive at are really two different kind of flows. 

Speaker 2  (12:23)
One where there's a self-service self service flows like a self-service recovery which covers off all of those scenarios I forgot it, I lost it, you know, it's broken right, they all end up falling into the same bucket and you end up with, well, I can that employee can fully recover themselves. You know, when we put a new key in their hand and then a flow that would involve some sort of assistance. All right, I wish I could tell you exactly what that some sort of assistance looks like, but it's still still tons of work to do there to figure out all of those details. 

Speaker 2  (13:03)
So, you know, we're mapping all of this out the different scenarios, the different options around them, and just there's just a lot that goes that could go into it and it needs to be simple. 

Speaker 6  (13:19)
Yeah, yeah, and I think you'll get a lot of support out of out of the cpb folks in terms of how to and what works best, because we all know we've got stuff like this or parallel to this. So I think if the topic here is, I'm just gonna call it. Operationalization of an additional peripheral I think we can move forward with that. 

Speaker 6  (13:43)
So we just we just need the heads up and kind of the topic to make sure that because the teams are just kind of engaged now, I don't know that anybody's been on boarded to bring folks into a call, tell them what's going on and start to talk about some of this type of stuff. Is it like, just, I guess back to my question. The 2 might be overlapping really, but like Is there a do you guys have the work back on the U? 

Speaker 6  (14:10)
B? Like, yeah, part of it is a time based question, but part of it is me going. Who is the decision maker on You know, this extra piece of hardware. 

Speaker 6  (14:22)
That, you know, yeah, has tons of benefits, but we all know, brings tons of complexity in terms of oversight. 

Speaker 1  (14:35)
So I guess 2 questions. Eric, the first one is, do you have work back now? We only have Q2 fi 27 as the prop that date. 

Speaker 1  (14:45)
Who is the decision maker on the hardware? I think that would probably be in play enablement. Charlotte and Mike curtains. 

Speaker 6  (14:51)
Okay, so I'm on there. 

Speaker 2  (14:58)
It would be quite enable me, and I mean, we're certainly making the recommendation of the hardware security key at this point in time, right with a high confidence level. This is what the industry has moved. Move, you know, very widely for this type of scenario, right? 

Speaker 2  (15:18)
And also even the like the vendor you know, the vendor that we've chosen is well industry leader. So, you know, I feel good about what What we're proposing at that high level, you know, the details is where we're going to have to really work things out, and in all of our discussions with Yubuka, it's pretty clear that That all companies have their unique Scenarios in situations, and at the end of the day, everybody has Kind of their own custom way of doing everything. And a lot of it comes down to workflows, business processes and everybody's different, so it ends up being a custom solution under the covers. 

Speaker 2  (16:06)
Yeah 

Speaker 6  (16:09)
And so is there Like, is there a VP? Or somebody that is Approving the final. Decision, or how does that shake down? 

Speaker 6  (16:22)
And it's not going to be challenging this to me, try to wrap my head around the governance of How does that? Let me just say 

Speaker 2  (16:30)
Oh, yeah, I'll leave that one day, Andrew. Okay, those questions. I'm sorry, Andrew. 

Speaker 1  (16:37)
Yeah, the B.P would be Teresa. Since Celtic or cincillato and Mike, who's, who's you, technically? Your VP? 

Speaker 1  (16:45)
This is between cloud I am at yam, right? 

Speaker 7  (16:49)
So Eric this comes from enterprise protect, so it's a it's for compliance right so that we're addressing a finding, and we have a due date to complete that. So it is a continuity of windows look for business which was one solution for laptop. And now this team is looking at the other solution. 

Speaker 7  (17:10)
For the other devices so we can close the gap we have in terms of security. And it's 

Speaker 6  (17:17)
I get that part. I just mean, like the solution to closing that gap. Like that? 

Speaker 6  (17:22)
That's kind of what's asking like, who's the authority that says, yeah, you've got the right solution. 

Speaker 7  (17:26)
Well, I think the team is looking at the solution right now and engaging with you to see if it's to validate, if it's the right solution. So that's why we're trying to understand what's your process and having those imp. 

Speaker 6  (17:38)
Yeah 

Speaker 8  (17:39)
I guess Eric we have solutions that will meet the findings but the strategy that we want here is a solution and process that's going to really work for you without interrupting business or potentially improving it. Yeah 

Speaker 6  (17:55)
Okay. Can you Andrew? Can you ping me those names just so I have them, and I can I can sort of make sense, so I get I get what you guys are saying, we'll help with the process the technology like, if I flip this around the other way to say like you, it just feels like you guys. 

Speaker 6  (18:12)
Are wanna pull out a few requirements from us and I get that and then if I was going to follow that path through then a solution, those requirements should be recommended, but we're obviously backing into this one for all the right reasons because, you know we don't have any requirements. But So yeah, I just just so didn't understand like who said that, yes, ub is right? That's kind of the main question, and then we'll figure out all the processed stuff. 

Speaker 6  (18:40)
And don't expect that Lang at this point because there's no I don't think there's any challenge that way it's just more understanding. Or another way of asking the same question, does this project have like an executive oversight? 

Speaker 8  (18:59)
Yeah, so there's several portions of this so Jane, you're owning this from the YM remediation finding, and then from the technology side Jim based out, is your is your sponsoring executive, okay? 

Speaker 6  (19:26)
And then I don't know where we left this one, but like, did you guys? Were you guys able to share over specifics on the ubq? Like to myself, Brian John, Chris like actual model, I think at some point, it'd be good for us to get our hands-on kind of like even when we start talking about size, you know, feasibility of maneuvering in and out of ports like just kind of that sort of stuff has that been shared over like the actual model specs when we anticipate getting our hands-on 

Speaker 9  (19:58)
No, we haven't seen it. We haven't seen it yet. I don't know, Jonathan if you have any kind of documentation you could send us, but 

Speaker 2  (20:05)
Oh, I have so much documentation. Yeah, ubique's pretty pretty good that way, but only in the chat here I'll just put the That link to their page and And so it's going to be the 5 series Model 5 series, I should say. Let's drop that in here. 

Speaker 2  (20:33)
And so the 5 I'm the 5. It's VNF C. I've been fc singing here. 

Speaker 2  (20:52)
They've all cut, they have all kinds. So even just that In the chat there, you see, like six different ones in their in their 5 series. So we'd be looking at that second one so that first that first one is the USB C sorry USB a and the second one is USB C so we'd be looking at usbc, unless you just didn't have a uspc porta. 

Speaker 2  (21:22)
In available, but that would really be the preferred model. It's one of those first 2 

Speaker 9  (21:27)
So it's this is something you gotta plug into the desktop, right? 

Speaker 2  (21:35)
We've been talking about NFC tap, but it comes near the port. Yeah, so so yeah, let the meat 

Speaker 9  (21:43)
So 

Speaker 4  (21:47)
Or as the top extended off like 

Speaker 2  (21:50)
There's a reader that's right. 

Speaker 4  (21:54)
It's like, is it like the little Y on that key? 

Speaker 2  (21:58)
Yeah, well, yeah, let me let me start. We've always talked about a reader. Okay, so yes, a reader that needs needs the that needs a USB. 

Speaker 2  (22:10)
Okay, the key itself, this is NFC tap, but all of these NFC tap keys. They're also insertable. Okay, but world is multifunction. 

Speaker 9  (22:23)
Okay, where's the reader? 

Speaker 2  (22:26)
The reader needs to be attached to the yeah. 

Speaker 9  (22:29)
No, no I mean, where's the picture of the reader? 

Speaker 2  (22:32)
The whole picture of the reader, okay? Yeah, I can. I can show you one of those as well. 

Speaker 2  (22:42)
Yeah, sorry about all 

Speaker 9  (22:45)
The reason I'm saying that is I don't think anybody's going to be reaching in behind the monitor to plug it up it. 

Speaker 2  (22:49)
I said, no. 

Speaker 9  (23:21)
I'm also assuming that that reader needs some sort of or either or needs some sort of software installed on the desktop. 

Speaker 2  (23:27)
No, it doesn't actually, oh really? Yeah? So it's good that way, it's using standards. 

Speaker 2  (23:35)
Yeah, I mean, which was one of our requirements actually? 

Speaker 4  (23:40)
Okay, so it's met the requirements so it doesn't contain any storage or anything, so it's not blocked by the USB port. 

Speaker 2  (23:47)
No, it's just powered by the perfect power. Yeah, powered by it. Yeah, there were you know when we looked at different authenticators, right? 

Speaker 2  (23:58)
There were numerous in the industry that require us to install software or even make changes. To the credential provider, which is a big deal Yeah, we didn't. We didn't want any of that, so you know, solutions that are just integrated directly into the operation system plug and play is what we were after. 

Speaker 6  (24:23)
So what it makes sense, would it make sense for us to get? I've been just gonna say one of these, but a couple of these in the lab, because I'm even looking at the ub. Yeah, the actual key itself, right, and yeah, a couple of things you guys prior to thought about this. 

Speaker 6  (24:38)
Right, like, where does a colleague actually keep this does the fact that it's USB C so I get why that's an advantage, but I could think about that. Sticking out and getting in the way, I guess anyways look and feel all that good stuff does that make sense for us to get a couple of these in our lot. 

Speaker 2  (25:00)
So yes. Yes, I mean, that's, that's always, that's always been the attent. You know, Ben ben Cassidy does have a couple. 

Speaker 6  (25:15)
So John Chris yeah. 

Speaker 9  (25:17)
Yeah, we should have We'd like to get at least 2 But you say, Ben has it and ben's been testing it, or you just does he just have it? 

Speaker 2  (25:29)
He just has it and he's done a basic done a basic test. All right, girn. You know, did it work? 

Speaker 2  (25:35)
Yes, type type thing. But it's not like we've established test cases to go through Okay? Right? 

Speaker 2  (25:47)
It was verify functionality, so as far as we've gotten at this point. 

Speaker 9  (25:53)
So let me back up a minute, I think we need at least one So hopefully too, but We'd also, we'd also need to figure out how we're going to Attach this or set this up on the workstation. So that's why we kind of really want it, and then to test it. 

Speaker 2  (26:11)
Yeah, and then keys as well. 

Speaker 9  (26:13)
Yeah, and then keys as well. But yeah, but the first thing we're going to see is, can we even plug it in and where would we plug it in? Yeah, is it AUS bc? 

Speaker 9  (26:21)
Or is it usba, or is it either or 

Speaker 2  (26:25)
Add the one reader's a** was A Yeah 

Speaker 4  (26:31)
That's what the model shows it doesn't, and on the shows, usba or the Pfizer, 23 reader, I was already looking through it. It doesn't give a different, it's a meter and a 1 cable. 

Speaker 2  (26:42)
Yeah, and then and then There's other so that one that I showed you there that's from hid, global, okay, that is that is what we've been looking at now that specific model that 5023, that one is the multi protocol. And I've talked about this before with the ubs themselves, they're also multiprotocult, even though the only we only need 2 protocols, we need phyto, and we need support for one time password for the mainframe use case so that that NFC reader, that 5023, it also supports multiple protocols, and we may end up with a different model version, I think we likely would I can't tell you what that model version is, but it's like If we're not going to use eight different protocols, why would we get a reader that supports eight different protocols? 

Speaker 2  (27:46)
Okay, so it was, it was basically, you know, get a reader that we could do a functional test with Had unlikely to be the actual reader that we would end up with. But for the purposes of A can I get a reader with, you know, cable that's a meter and a 1 long and see how it's going to sit on the desk. It would, you know, be fine for that. 

Speaker 4  (28:14)
It just adds up, it's 330 A few of us have a meeting with the vendor so 

Speaker 1  (28:26)
Okay, we're at time, so it sounds like we need to separate workshop with other business stakeholders to go through the questions. The original questions that our architect was Jeremy was interested in saw work would give me to schedule that otherwise we just use this series as a general pulse, check weekly sancting. Any other question? 

Speaker 6  (28:54)
No, just I've been kind of dancing around this one today, but yet, the more that can be shared like visually in terms of Ah, cemented workbacks, right? So if we're talking about people buying stuff like it, just, it's, it's going to help us a ton it's gonna help us help each other, that would be appreciated, right? So anything that we do have even notionally or draft in place. 

Speaker 6  (29:18)
Like, we're making decisions by the state, we're, you know, signing the agreements by the state we're buying by the state. It's also good, because the one thing I don't want to do there will be gates on our end socialization. You know, lots of questions about this one. 

Speaker 6  (29:32)
I don't necessarily want to be behind. I guess when I'm driving at 

Speaker 7  (29:36)
Yeah, yeah, so thanks. Are yeah, and I think that's why we're engaging right now, you know, we're almost, like 6 months ahead of when we're planning to roll out. So we're not, you know, last minute like windows will look for business, but yeah, for sure, for sure, we want to work together, proactively. 

Speaker 6  (29:52)
In the core there being anything that you guys can write down like an actual write down would be helpful. Yeah, but yes, definitely do appreciate that. 

Speaker 7  (30:01)
All right. Thank you 

Speaker 6  (30:03)
Bixby 
