
Speaker 1  (00:00)
That's the meeting one. That's one of the meeting notes. So at 1. 

Speaker 1  (00:04)
This one. Is sharing something? 

Speaker 2  (00:07)
No, I'm saying. 

Speaker 3  (00:09)
You know, just what isn't this great? 

Speaker 2  (00:11)
Well, there's on the shad folders, there's Z messaging, there's DSP, because security doesn't, and then there's, I think, dspm, so I'm asking, just clarify which one I'm granted. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
ESPN, ESPN, sorry, all right, that's All right. Thank you and then 

Speaker 2  (00:26)
Team, if we have Before Dan gets into the science sphere around Now an SCR or E messaging, or anything along that line, can we You can Dave defer to Daniel or Ata or anyone just, but I want to make sure one of my homework assignments. I don't have filled out so I'd appreciate input that everything we've done to date with my Dan Wheeler is in your Pat space. This configuration set up, we even have some domains added and testing. 

Speaker 2  (01:06)
But I wanted to confirm with you that somebody on your team, I think Daniel is setting up your production instance when they have the appropriate access, and you're able to do the import and The Domain sink, and all that stuff I have that still pending. 

Speaker 1  (01:23)
It is pending still pending our way focused on focus on the test environment, what we call Pat. 

Speaker 2  (01:29)
I understood, yeah, rob you still yeah, you're still pending, and then the only thing left on top of that that I was trying to explain to my team, but I might have butchered is well. I think I have it is we're waiting for your team to get to sign off on the design of male routing still, and that way we need Dan, will to help advise around the overall hardware replacement that we were working on, we're waiting to kind of certify that And that's still pending as well, correct, correct? All right, cool, so that that's AI just wanted to make sure I had that right. 

Speaker 2  (02:04)
I wasn't Miss, you know, misunderstanding anything, but that that's part of my internal email update to my team and questions team proof point, let me know otherwise back to you guys. Thank you. 

Speaker 4  (02:19)
Okay. Hi, I'm assuming most of the people that need to be here are here. 

Speaker 1  (02:26)
Yeah, yes, Jeff, I don't think so. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (02:29)
If there's nothing, is there any questions from anybody else because I know I'm gonna probably take app a lot of time, because I need to try to figure out how to configure the on prime servers. 

Speaker 1  (02:44)
Well over to Egypt. 

Speaker 4  (02:46)
Okay, I guess I'll meet alright so then I sent you an email earlier this today. So the configuration, yeah, so what we're having a problem with is None of the cables are connected to the embedded necks. And it looks like the The Initial configuration automatically pick the embedded Okay, so either we physically change it, or we kind of you know, change the the The next binding. 

Speaker 3  (03:33)
Yeah, we can do that. Why would you not use the embedded neck? Is there a reason that you went right before the pci card? 

Speaker 4  (03:40)
We never really specified which Nick, but originally, when we had another vendor they had that we used the integrated, because it actually had a 10 gig copper So yeah, we weren't even thinking about that. But Yeah, it automatically selected the integrated. I tried to disable the embedded on the bios. 

Speaker 4  (04:10)
But even after rebooting, it didn't switch over so automatically or anything. 

Speaker 3  (04:15)
That's yeah, it's probably all based on the Linux operation system. And it's not like windows, where it has, you know, driver auto, detect and stuff like that, I would say, let's get Let's get Do you turn a cable into the embedded? Nick? 

Speaker 3  (04:34)
And just make sure that we 're not plugging into the isloport because that islo port should be completely separate. 

Speaker 4  (04:42)
We've got eyelass set up already, so it's okay, it's not an issue there. 

Speaker 3  (04:47)
Awesome. Yeah, let's definitely get a cable clock in. 

Speaker 4  (04:54)
The new recommendation is a physical cable rather than configuring the the OSI guess yes. 

Speaker 1  (05:03)
So we have to go sit out and get some more Kazan, what that means is that we have to Get contractors back in there to To physically change those You know, 27 boxes. Two different locations. 

Speaker 3  (05:22)
27 or 18. 

Speaker 1  (05:27)
Okay. 

Speaker 3  (05:28)
Yeah, I would definitely start out with that. I know that the proof point OS can be pretty picky about what interfaces it has and anything beyond 3 interfaces. It doesn 't even seem to my knowledge, I'm still trying to track down if we have a Dell hardware guide for that, but I would recommend checking out the help setting from the network interface page. 

Speaker 3  (05:56)
If you are able to log into 

Speaker 4  (05:59)
Okay, I think you're scaring me because we're planning to use fournix, right? 

Speaker 3  (06:05)
Okay. 

Speaker 4  (06:06)
Yeah, and you're saying he is the Mac. 

Speaker 3  (06:09)
So yeah, anything above 3 isn't gonna work. 

Speaker 4  (06:13)
Is that like a westing, or is an app thing? 

Speaker 3  (06:17)
It's no west thing 

Speaker 1  (06:21)
So we would have country good, we've set up 4 of them. 

Speaker 2  (06:26)
Yeah, 4 feet below. Why do you need 4 for 

Speaker 4  (06:31)
No, so 2 is for total salt tolerance, right? So there's actually going to be only one idea signed, but that there's 4 nicks, right? 

Speaker 1  (06:40)
I'm sorry, we're, you know, we got a box with 4 and cleaning was possible, so we 

Speaker 4  (06:48)
I mean, that's what we're 

Speaker 1  (06:49)
We know our judgment that the fifth could put forward and use for yeah Okay, all right, continue to add. Let me see if I find 

Speaker 4  (07:05)
Well, if we need to do the cabling, instead of Ended up more, find the oest. There's not much for me to do at this point. 

Speaker 1  (07:13)
Okay. All right, let's spend the time here and get that sort of well, exactly we need to do Cos. I may 

Speaker 4  (07:20)
Oh, you know what, we need to set app a second mind anyway, so if you can help us do that that we could. Yeah, of course. Okay, so let me share that. 

Speaker 4  (07:38)
So here's the Do you see my share? Yes, I do. Okay, so this is the Kama, prompt, yep. 

Speaker 3  (07:54)
Go ahead and hit enter. Take exit. Why did it not go back to the menu? 

Speaker 4  (08:07)
Let's try again. That's a good match. 

Speaker 3  (08:14)
Option one. Yeah, that's not it. What is option? 

Speaker 3  (08:23)
What's back under option free? There should be a networking configuration. 

Speaker 4  (08:29)
That's the only thing. So what I've been able to gather is that any network settings in terms of binding needs to be done through The OS, maybe the cli type thing 

Speaker 3  (08:45)
There should be a network interface under option one, assuming those knicks are actually active on On the hardware level 

Speaker 4  (09:02)
I think I know what you want it. I think the return to main menu. 

Speaker 3  (09:07)
There we go. You know, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (09:11)
So you can't configure anything as far as I can tell you, just get to see what 

Speaker 3  (09:16)
Let's hear, yeah, there should be a network configuration menu in there somewhere. There are 2 eggs, and please sure. Yeah, let me check with somebody right now. 

Speaker 3  (09:50)
All right, so I've just asked something in our pre-sales engineering chat. Hopefully somebody there knows of where that documentation lies and I'm also currently looking on our internal articles. 

Speaker 3  (10:37)
All right, what do we have here? 

Speaker 3  (10:59)
Which specific hardware models do you have? The 1990M890E 

Speaker 1  (11:08)
No, I think we're at P690 and P 6000 okay, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (11:49)
I'm just going to talk to the portal here and we'll see if it likes, do we have any other questions while I'm looking for the hardware guides for this Or is this what we're waiting on at the moment? 

Speaker 4  (12:09)
This is the more important one where we need to be able Bigger and set up the unpre. We got the firewall in place, but I'm not able to connect to it because it's not connected. 

Speaker 3  (12:22)
Roger, that thank you. 

Speaker 3  (13:33)
Can you go to the command prompt? And try if can take just type that out, and let's see what we get. All right, so it sees the 3 Interfaces and eye track 

Speaker 4  (13:53)
It shouldn't be able to see the eye track. 

Speaker 3  (13:56)
Oh, yeah, no one to virtual then. 

Speaker 4  (14:03)
The TMI and the bond 10 and then 

Speaker 3  (14:08)
The other two are the actual individuals. 

Speaker 4  (14:10)
And when the background yep. 

Speaker 3  (14:20)
I don't know why it It doesn't see those individual necks. 

Speaker 4  (14:28)
It does they're so mad for it. 

Speaker 3  (14:31)
Gather. 

Speaker 4  (14:32)
I just don't remember which one it was, I think it was B. R. Show, maybe. 

Speaker 4  (14:39)
Or something like that? 

Speaker 3  (14:42)
You can try IP - H. 

Speaker 4  (14:55)
Oh, link - link. I think. So I mean 

Speaker 3  (15:09)
What is just I Pash, link? 

Speaker 4  (15:13)
It just pulls up that thing, I think 

Speaker 3  (15:18)
What about IP space link -, show? No - in front of the link. 

Speaker 4  (15:25)
Yeah, so There it is. 

Speaker 3  (15:33)
So no dashes, alright. 

Speaker 3  (15:51)
I know I had asked this previously. Let me see if I can find the previous conversation. 

Speaker 4  (16:00)
Yeah, because the only thing I can dig up is that I need to mod. By the I don't think files. 

Speaker 3  (16:09)
Okay? So We did have somebody answer when I asked about the network teaming. But the application, the proof point protection server can only see Ethernet 0 and 1 also known as GB one and GB 2. 

Speaker 3  (16:26)
If you already have those teamed, then we just have one IP address for this appliance. 

Speaker 4  (16:42)
Okay, and that's going to be a big issue. Because we originally asked whether we can have 2 and And we're told it's okay, so we thought and found an outbound, same as the original thinking. And so we have 4 nicks, 2 IPS, one for inbound, and one for outbound type logic. 

Speaker 3  (17:06)
Let's revisit that for a second. What was the purpose of trying to segregate inbound and outbound traffic? 

Speaker 4  (17:15)
There it's more of a logical, because then one Nick will be for Internal communication with td and the other one will be more for Everything else that's the internet. 

Speaker 3  (17:31)
Okay, I don't recommend having that segregated at the network level. It makes much more sense to do that based on The Domain within the actual Per point application or the Admin console itself and the big reason for that is at the end of the day, there is no inbound, an outbound, it is all domains that are on your inbound mail table and domains that are not in other words, every incoming email, whether it's going to a domain on your inbound mail table or something on the internet is received by the filtering dam, and then every outgoing email is sent by the send mail server. 

Speaker 4  (18:15)
I understand that. Looking at the cloud that makes complete sense wasn't sure about the entrepre. Devices, and that's where you guys came in, right? 

Speaker 4  (18:30)
And you said you guys said it was okay. 

Speaker 3  (18:35)
I may have my spoke, it's been a while since I've worked with the on prime physical appliances, but the general recommendation is to not try to segregate traffic for what is considered inbound and outbound, because at some point you will get an email that breaks that paradigm. I eat something that you consider outbound may end up on the quote. ", inbound, Nick or vice versa. 

Speaker 4  (19:01)
Yeah, the reckoning is going to be a big change because all our requests for firewall. All network setup have been in the thought that we're going to have 2 knicks that are working 

Speaker 3  (19:13)
You can't have tunics, they just will not be full tolerant, at that point. And keep in mind the whole system is fall tolerant as a cluster, so even if there is a let's just say that the onboard Nick goes bad on one of the cluster members, if something tries going into that mail cue, and there's a network error it will be shifted over to one of the other agents. 

Speaker 1  (19:37)
So we have load balancing there. 

Speaker 3  (19:40)
At the cluster level, not at the Nick level. Yes 

Speaker 4  (19:46)
Yeah, but that's going to be a complete change in design that we're going to need to submit new firewall requests and everything they 

Speaker 1  (19:56)
Okay, okay, something we need to sit down with. Architecture team and We don't have Cristiano carno. 

Speaker 4  (20:08)
I don't think he's there really But all of the information I've been able to gather, we should be able to get at least 2 bound To balance the 2 teams 

Speaker 3  (20:24)
They'll be seen by the OSI don't know if it would be seen by the proof point software at that point. 

Speaker 4  (20:31)
Okay. Yeah, that's going to be a major change. Unfortunately. 

Speaker 1  (20:42)
So in addition, I was used for that. In addition to us, we We can't get blame, so because we're just 

Speaker 4  (20:49)
We don't need to recap, but we'll still have the extra IPS. We can just not use them. The biggest thing, though, is We were setting up gnats, and some of the firewall requests were based on 2 IPS were The expectation was that the second bound was going to be the one that's committed him with the internet. 

Speaker 4  (21:15)
And the The united was the external netting for the communication was gonna be going to the external neck. So potentially, if we restart everything, we can just maybe use the external, but still need to do requests for let's say the IMF order and everything to the external Nick. So we don't need new IPS, we'll just start using wad. 

Speaker 4  (21:47)
But we're going to have to resubmit all these firewall requests, and all that 

Speaker 3  (21:53)
I wonder if you could just do a blanket, you know, hey, consolidate each one for each of these IP addresses or something like that. I sorry, I don't know how picky your networking team is. Very big. 

Speaker 3  (22:05)
Yeah, I'm sure that's kind of universal. 

Speaker 1  (22:09)
This is new for us and them as well then. So I think My approach is okay, the standard we need here. What are you recommending? 

Speaker 1  (22:16)
Let's see what we need first and then see how they already with that. 

Speaker 4  (22:20)
Oh, wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on. We are already signed IP so if we're doing this, we're gonna have to switch the certain IPS to the the embedded Nick. The external It really depends on how we're going to do it. 

Speaker 4  (22:40)
It might be better just to keep the original IPS, which is the one we sat on the servers already and And I were thinking of moving 2 of the cables, the Nick, one type thing, Nick, one and Nick, 2 to the embedded, and then for the For the narrowing walls just have to get them. To change the IPS, or something like that. 

Speaker 1  (23:08)
Investors plan it out The score to their minds and the Sky it done Have a good we're going to do all this in the bad test environment. First, before we go to the other two. 

Speaker 3  (23:22)
What's the split that we're looking at for a number of appliances for production and number of appliances for Pat? 

Speaker 4  (23:32)
They're pretty much the same. It's just that the For production, there'll be a duplicate one, meaning there'll be a murder set, so 1 master 2 scanners or agents in each side. 

Speaker 3  (23:46)
And for 27, that's 9 total. So, then 

Speaker 4  (23:53)
No, we have three different services, right? So that ticks up the 9 for a Pat, right? So we use 9 for Pat, and then there'll be 9 for 1 site and then 9 for another site. 

Speaker 3  (24:06)
Okay. That should be fine. Keep in mind that each can figmaster, has its own can fig? 

Speaker 3  (24:16)
And its own Admin page, so if you want to share the exact same settings across all of those that will be manually updated each can figmaster, yeah, yeah We know all right. Just wanted to bring that out. I didn't know if you wanted to have a single confate master and multiple agents spread across data centers. 

Speaker 3  (24:40)
I didn't know if you had the ability to do V land stretching across data centers. 

Speaker 4  (24:54)
We could, but Yeah, I'm not sure if we really want to do that. Because Configuration anyways with the other vendor has 2 data set control centers or the masters. And we're not expecting to have to do as much configuration in the first place, because a lot of things are being migrated to the cloud. 

Speaker 4  (25:21)
All right So yeah, it should be more of a set of forget. 

Speaker 3  (25:25)
Almost right, your user based stuff yep. 

Speaker 4  (25:29)
Yeah 

Speaker 4  (25:57)
So is this still worthwhile? To try to configure a second bound or 

Speaker 3  (26:03)
We can try, I just I am not at all familiar with the the Linux command line commands for network teaming. Let me see if I can. 

Speaker 4  (26:14)
We have a is there. 

Speaker 3  (26:16)
I can access. I've already put the ask out to pre-sales to see if that's something they know. 

Speaker 3  (27:06)
All right, I've reached out to the principal architect to see who he knows. Maybe we can get somebody on our next call. 

Speaker 4  (27:14)
Okay. I guess that's it for me for now. Deeply answered any questions. 

Speaker 4  (27:35)
Naomi, I'm good, by the way. 

Speaker 1  (27:37)
I can feel like that's it today, jad, okay, so let's say, jet, let's regoop sometime tomorrow to figure out what we're gonna be asking yes at a data center for 2, yeah, cause they're picking me back already. So What Newton knew? Knowledge further details. 

Speaker 1  (27:53)
So let's get back to the table. Yeah, we can get Chris in there as well. Architect. 

Speaker 4  (28:02)
Okay, yeah, I think we can continue on with I think what our original time was is just to move the Nick 1 and 2 over to the embedded, and then your husband 3 and 4 up, and even if we don't end up using it. 

Speaker 1  (28:24)
I can leave the case yesterday. 

Speaker 4  (28:26)
Somebody had some changes to, you know yeah. 

Speaker 3  (28:28)
But at the end of the day, the worst is that you're occupying a port on a switch somewhere. 

Speaker 4  (28:33)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (28:34)
And a cabinet is full in weight, and so there's nothing else for you can connect to it. 

Speaker 3  (28:39)
So nice. 

Speaker 1  (28:41)
Yeah, you have a problem, really. All right. You're moving at, you guys know jet. 

Speaker 4  (28:47)
All right, things are 

Speaker 1  (28:49)
Connect tomorrow. Okay, thanks everyone. 

Speaker 3  (28:50)
Thank you all 

Speaker 5  (30:26)
You're trying to draw back the same as front door and CM profiles. Businesses 

Speaker 6  (30:50)
I guess. 

Speaker 5  (34:40)
I didn't try to park down on now. It says orge whistle name is that webout contosa 102. Tonight, this last part right here, the basics path for the front door let's see your 

Speaker 6  (35:18)
Now during the creation, they had, you added the first one, right? But the origin 

Speaker 5  (35:28)
So like up here, good at this They're both of them. And then 

Speaker 6  (35:43)
Okay, sorry, I said, okay. You're into the so you're just not betting as the front door right? Correct. 

Speaker 6  (35:49)
Okay. Yeah, you're gonna go with the first apple now. Okay, you bet thanks for check, appreciate that timer. 

Speaker 4  (37:57)
Wait, book is somebody 
