
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Hopefully, there's no dependency here. They're married to each other, so 

Speaker 2  (00:07)
So let's do this, let's, let's let's go back to the detector let's point it for the detector pointed to something else, right? 

Speaker 1  (00:15)
Like we did last time. Yeah? 

Speaker 2  (00:17)
Yeah, but that would allow us to get rid of that and eventually well major title, which is where we tried to grow enough, the unfriendly natural detector that you see these settings, kind of security providers now Okay, but we do need a sticker for this. So where are you making the reference here to the EDM? I think you have to certainly break the track, which is 

Speaker 3  (00:40)
Yeah, it's they're both EDM, so can you just put something like generic here? 

Speaker 1  (00:47)
I am, yeah, working on there. 

Speaker 2  (00:51)
Yeah, I grabbed like a dictionary and wanted to do one of the examples like, yeah, yeah, it's like 

Speaker 1  (00:59)
I can tell you 

Speaker 2  (01:00)
Dish like a smart idea or something, or do you do you 

Speaker 1  (01:03)
I've already changed the thing. Okay, then cool Okay, so that should let In a test Interesting enough. Why am I still referencing this detector? 

Speaker 2  (01:20)
She says, you, I don't think it doesn't update. I noticed that too. 

Speaker 1  (01:24)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (01:26)
Yeah, I've been dead enough. You got that, so I did for my perfect Next, I'm gonna provide you that 

Speaker 3  (01:45)
Okay, so I assume these are not being referenced to any rules or anything. 

Speaker 1  (01:51)
Now directly we do the party through our detector. 

Speaker 2  (01:59)
So the guy attempted ear 

Speaker 3  (02:02)
You said you wait, you said you did have in a detector. 

Speaker 1  (02:06)
Not anymore, but that's a that's the way we're referencing them, right? We create the idm, and then create a detector and then reference use the detector and policy. Yeah, he's embroiled. 

Speaker 3  (02:18)
Factor that we just deleted or replaced that had all 3 of them in there. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (02:22)
Yeah, correct. We just use that one that or 3 other okay. This one. 

Speaker 1  (02:30)
I'll do what I can do this one / 2day, okay? 

Speaker 3  (02:37)
That should be fine, just let us know in the EDM. One is gone, and we'll rerun the script. 

Speaker 2  (02:45)
Understand so you can only delete from the backend. 

Speaker 1  (02:48)
Yeah, you can only delete it using the tool. However Their idea EDM tool that is on the server. 

Speaker 2  (02:57)
Okay, we need AI think I get. Well, we'll submit that later. Okay, so perfect. 

Speaker 2  (03:04)
We're good to hear religion. Oh, Hiers, once this is done. But is there any other issue with your poster stuff or 

Speaker 1  (03:14)
Not personally other than that one that I brought up, I just saw that the error message I did sent you an email in regards to the add integration, but we can actually So we did this early today. Harry's I didn't have a chance to talk to you on Tuesday. I think it was We finally did the connection of the identity only piece. 

Speaker 1  (03:45)
Yeah. 

Speaker 3  (03:50)
The twerking. 

Speaker 1  (03:53)
Well. So I we were kind of I was kind of lost to be quite Frank. So because doesn't talk about anything, where can I be you? 

Speaker 1  (04:04)
And there's no documentation around this piece right? So I was like and nowhere to read. 

Speaker 3  (04:11)
So the documentation piece is yeah, it's it's called the data catalog. So it's not called like ad. But if you I'll show you where you can view, if it's if it's working. 

Speaker 3  (04:23)
So go to the end point, go to the endpoint, drop down here and go to realms. I believe you have it turned on already, I think we turned it on initially, but edit this and go to advance settings. There's a you'll see data user catalog here, so go down. 

Speaker 3  (04:41)
It's in this first processing. Yeah, user catalog integration. Turn this on. 

Speaker 1  (04:45)
I went to 

Speaker 3  (04:48)
All right, and then save this. 

Speaker 1  (04:52)
I cook that this was off. That's interesting. 

Speaker 3  (04:57)
Yeah, I'm not sure why I know we talked about it, but you guys left it off until you made a decision on how you were going to connect it. 

Speaker 1  (05:05)
Okay. 

Speaker 3  (05:08)
Okay, uh, so that that will initiate the sink. I'm not sure how long it'll take, but I'll show you where to check to see all the groups so yeah, just go to a rule prevention or detection rules. 

Speaker 1  (05:21)
So what is this group coming from that, I guess the ag? 

Speaker 3  (05:29)
Well, yeah, that's just probably just like a cause. It'll feel scanned, like the local or like the whatever groups that endpoint is a part of but okay. 

Speaker 1  (05:39)
Because I went here, I went to use her catalog. 

Speaker 3  (05:42)
Okay, did it 

Speaker 1  (05:44)
And it said, endpoint, directory 

Speaker 3  (05:47)
Yeah, you'll see like an Avenue, 65 like button, okay, okay. 

Speaker 1  (05:55)
So if we hope Okay, my God. So if we're getting Telemetry, from the endpoint, so you see as endpoint directory, and that's when we thought if this was part of the because this is one of the domains right? 

Speaker 3  (06:13)
Yeah, I mean you probably have like a do you have one of your machines that are out there that are part of these groups. 

Speaker 1  (06:20)
For all of them 

Speaker 3  (06:22)
Yeah, so that's why they're already observed right? Under that endpoint directory, you'll see a like M365 button appear like once to start. 

Speaker 1  (06:31)
Okay, so the way you need to do the wind even need that integration, then if we're getting telemetry from the endpoint. 

Speaker 2  (06:39)
We need it because we also need to target usage based on the usage, right? But I just want to clarify something like Paris, you just mentioned, like a dose, mentioning part of this group like a there's intentional recession to target users. No machines users want to make sure that this actually works with users. 

Speaker 2  (07:02)
Right? You know, another machines. 

Speaker 3  (07:05)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like you're talking about the user group. 

Speaker 1  (07:08)
User opi. 

Speaker 2  (07:09)
Yeah, that's funny. Make sure because you said machines. And like the kind of brakes up little 

Speaker 3  (07:14)
Yeah, sorry, change, no group. You can use your group so 

Speaker 1  (07:18)
Okay, so we hope 

Speaker 3  (07:20)
You've got on the ad side right, so, you know, users get added in, but like I mentioned the sink here will only update the membership once a day, so yeah, just keep that time frame in mind as you build your rules out if you need someone in the rule like immediately or you need them, you need to put them in itm, like, if you guys end up using that portion, you can add their username directly into a rule or into A Into an agent policy, but typically the sink is once a day. I believe you can open a support ticket and have them crease. 

Speaker 3  (07:57)
The frequency of I don't think it'll be like every hour but I've seen them put into like once every 12 hours or once every 8 hour. 

Speaker 1  (08:06)
It's basically once every 24 hours. Then And in object will appear down here, the second 365 directory. I guess 

Speaker 3  (08:21)
Yeah, so in the rule, what you would let's see if it appears so cancel out of here, you're actually in just the Group A. So click group name here. It might already be on since we talked about yeah, and then go to user and new groups from catalog. 

Speaker 3  (08:38)
Yeah, okay. And then select values. And let's see if it's your no okay. 

Speaker 3  (08:45)
Yeah, there will be like an M365 that appears 

Speaker 1  (08:50)
So this is the only way to check, there's no other way to check this like per se that you have a dedicated user group or our directory link, because I haven't seen that so, but I just wanted to confirm with you. 

Speaker 3  (09:08)
There you just see it within the rules or whatever reference, a group you'll see it. 

Speaker 1  (09:13)
So because we just enable this, and there's no way to I guess confirm that the sink is happening from the polo perspective. 

Speaker 3  (09:23)
No, there's not unfortunately, but you have that. As long as that connection is shown, green, like, you should be fine. When it I think it should once we toggle it on it should. 

Speaker 3  (09:37)
Like, I would assume, it's gonna force a sink like, as soon as it detects that we turn that on. But yeah, I'm not sure if it's like working on some time cycle as well. 

Speaker 1  (09:51)
Privileges, wait 24 hours and hope for the best 

Speaker 3  (09:55)
Um yeah, I would say just check it periodically throughout the day and And see if it appears here, but that's there's nothing else that you would need to do here. As long as this s***'s John Green and its identity only should be fun. This is more on the cloud side. 

Speaker 3  (10:15)
But Yeah, on the cloud dop portion. 

Speaker 1  (10:25)
Okay, anything you have for another? Yeah, no Okay, that was definitely home. 

Speaker 2  (10:32)
For the desert now, you might go into I mean, that the point that come I just want to go Oh, we're gonna, I'm going to see situations that are run into this weekend. I didn't want to reply to the email I just want to, you know, make sure everybody understood, what was the issue here? It was a there was an era for nap and Oh, I mean, wait, wait, wait, wait. 

Speaker 3  (10:56)
What other point on the group guys is that, on the email side, there is like a separate user import. It's not covered by the same. Identity, only that we just did. 

Speaker 1  (11:09)
Yeah, we figure is you have three different products, three different integrations. It's not a unified type of integration. Yeah, I see. 

Speaker 1  (11:19)
I've seen that with other vendors. It's just a way that the cookie crumbles. When you go, you go through acquisitions. 

Speaker 2  (11:28)
I'm gonna go to search. 

Speaker 1  (11:33)
To do okay. 

Speaker 2  (11:37)
You know, I should just look for any email sand by me this week. So And we'll send there because, however That's now. Do you have to do my whole last name chant ych AN 

Speaker 4  (11:55)
Now you can display Howard. 

Speaker 2  (12:01)
I perfect. Do the last 3 days. But last today, something like that Sometimes it works. 

Speaker 2  (12:11)
Memory, I will need to trim my screen. Oh, sorry, brilliant's me. I probably had this swimming all the way, yeah, so it was my screen. 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
Okay, which so which you mother, you want me to? Take a look at? 

Speaker 2  (12:34)
I don't know if he was like a minute. I still don't see the whole screen on your side. I don't know why. 

Speaker 2  (12:43)
I don't know your monitor no I don't want to see a specific email. I just want to see the I wanted to see the bigger picture, right? So if she scrolled down a little bit, so we can see the not 

Speaker 1  (12:57)
I'll stop sharing our reshare, Howard. 

Speaker 2  (13:00)
Maybe actually give us a give a second. Let me probably let me just share my screen, because I'm okay, we do guys right? So that's for a second. 

Speaker 2  (13:10)
I made the performer counts, are I just It's gonna be a second. I chair my 3 work. I'm a material work just because that issue was bugging me. 

Speaker 2  (13:29)
I'm sorry, just kind of 1 second. This is what I'm trying to figure it out, like man. I sailed and getters next doesn't want to work today. 

Speaker 2  (13:39)
Okay, there we go. It's not the cooker, it's my eyes. Okay, finish my screen mozak. 

Speaker 2  (14:11)
Hey, if you guys can smash great ray. Yeah, okay, so let me show you this. 

Speaker 2  (14:28)
Sacrifice, so this is going back to me. Testing a condition at adception with the with the secure, right? I had an email, I had same attachment this attachment here. 

Speaker 2  (14:48)
Since again, that's the Lex right? This attachment was in all my earbels, when I said them, all of them, right? And we noticed that when we send an email. 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
Without a keyword, I only had like a like ATD secure, that was funny, because it triggered by just having a word that wasn't going to be in the system. Right? What I noticed is that he basically triggered an encryption, and I'm going to show you what it did. 

Speaker 2  (15:21)
Sorry, I forget to log into look. Hey, so you see everything that I sang here right? And I shot how like I should trigger it should trigger it should trigger, so all of them mechanically, aside from one of the last one is just the It shows the same fire that I keep testing right, the cna. 

Speaker 2  (15:48)
That's one, right? I send this email repeatedly. You know, 20 4K 20 4K 20 4K. 

Speaker 2  (15:57)
What and you can see here how this is working, I suspect it right like it's here in the quarantine this y'all, and it's going to the VCR VCI then I just, I just did the secure process, so just my keyword. And then he So this game is sick, and what will happen? I triggered it insecure, and then it doesn't show me that it actually went All right, so show me the trigger my policy. 

Speaker 2  (16:39)
He basically triggered TV secure before he went to dop, right. And then when I sit there in The Pass into a warehub right is something totally different. And there is no attachment, and you will see that probably here. 

Speaker 2  (16:58)
Let's see that. There was no exclusion, sorry I had no exclusion at that point like that there was nothing secure condition of all my on my dalty role, right. It did trigger the insecure setup for whatever reasons I think, and this is probably a bit rather that I was referring to. 

Speaker 2  (17:18)
And then, when I look at the scenario of what I actually trigger, it triggered a different policy, they had set up, that was looking also Maggie. But the interesting part is that there was no attachment not to get away, so maybe I was explaining correct on the email, but this is what I saw. If I just look at my earbud, it seems this is what I got. 

Speaker 2  (17:43)
You see is do we email secure, even though I did so I heard that not our encrypt. 

Speaker 4  (17:51)
So it's that like 

Speaker 1  (17:53)
Yes 

Speaker 2  (17:55)
Yes, right. So yeah, I understand that so what I'm trying to say is that we have a routing issue right now, right? That's why I didn't get and Daniel to the extent to the tread, right. 

Speaker 2  (18:15)
I just want to make sure we identify this at this stage. 

Speaker 4  (18:19)
Yeah, one thing I used to Howard, sorry, interrupt, go back to that rule it'd be helpful for troubleshooting, if we just added not just the scarve, but also the scard in the quarantine so we can have a sample of the message. And someone that triggers the dpen layer 6 rule. Yeah, that one So that way we just showed little sample message. 

Speaker 2  (18:50)
Yeah, I could do that. But I know why I trigger him like this one trigger against on my email right like this is just me, testing something, and that's why I trigger, right? But in a regular situation, this role will trigger it with just the message was just be allowed to go through, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (19:10)
All right, this is just because I had a policy that looks specific receipting, because I cannot test the receipting, I just decided to use by domain right and that's why I trigger. But we just want to make sure that you know, I understand the sobratomy issue. I still don't know why it actually removed the dashboard. 

Speaker 2  (19:34)
Honestly, but I guess we'll have to figure out once the What's the the broader issue? 

Speaker 4  (19:43)
Yeah, Daniel's back weeks week right? Because you know it'd be helpful. Look at the headers, but I think leaning Daniel took it with us. 

Speaker 4  (19:51)
Is jedi? 

Speaker 2  (19:53)
No, no, who's not one of this girl? So yeah, this disrupting issue, I just wanted to show you this, because this is what I was getting, I was sending stuff, and I didn't have any condition on my role and any exception, and I was kind of just in like something yourself here and I want to make sure we catch this. And we update any type of you know, debt rules or whatever or type rules are that we have to modify before we get to collection because I want to make sure you know this is being tested. 

Speaker 2  (20:26)
And you know, it's kind of unaware of this problem right? 

Speaker 1  (20:30)
Question from beyond the console, can we send? Can we see where the email went to 

Speaker 2  (20:37)
I cannot see it. I don't see it, that that's the thing the only thing I can see where that is okay. 

Speaker 4  (20:42)
Yeah, the message I was delivered 

Speaker 1  (20:46)
Is it the one that caused the 

Speaker 4  (20:47)
Carol was finding it, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (20:51)
That went to TV secure and no attachment value. I guess 

Speaker 4  (20:56)
Of that, we have to look her nose. 

Speaker 1  (20:58)
To go to the train, go to the trace. 

Speaker 2  (21:04)
That's what I said. 

Speaker 4  (21:05)
Right? But I was saying, if you copy a messaging quarantine, we can get the received headers, so we can eat some troubleshooting, so that it wouldn't hurt to quarantine the coffee, especially if we can replicate it at well. 

Speaker 1  (21:20)
But you said you said we could see it. 

Speaker 4  (21:24)
Navy, well, there are 3 parts. If the message was received by the proof point, we can quarantine a copy, and we click the receipt headers, if the message is relate like, you know where there's like that arrow on their trace. You can look at the MT locks. 

Speaker 4  (21:40)
In this case, there was no mta locks because it was sent locally, but like one of that was delivered. Yeah, it be traced and it'll be vmt, locks, you see, it says not available. 

Speaker 2  (21:51)
So black, this was a blood condition. Yeah, you know, you can only see things like that when you have an action that basically comp 

Speaker 1  (22:01)
Sets continue. 

Speaker 2  (22:06)
It's a blog, so 

Speaker 4  (22:07)
Yeah, that's why having some of the quarantine vest hits, we can see, like the hot step led to the message. It led to the proof point going backwards. Okay, we know the source IP, but we don't know like Number one strings down. 

Speaker 2  (22:25)
Or 12 down from the abountables. Okay, so that will stay at a quick question that I had, that's all that happened, you know, like the help that it gave me, actually worse, I was hoped to actually put the condition based on the pro, like it's not in here, and that was fine, I just had to use this key, or so, it doesn't go to that secure system traveling, so yeah. A quick question. 

Speaker 2  (22:58)
I mean, a little bit, I should put it earlier this week, we just mentioned that there was something in the back end that was missing. Was that fix also made to the pattern production tenant, or what we have to do to make the happen? 

Speaker 3  (23:13)
Yeah, there was a there was a deal setting that needed to be tongued on so that doesn't actually affect the functionality on like the agent or on email just within the console, like the way that scanning tool works is what we need the toggle for but yeah, I mean I'll turn it on in. All your tenants for now, we just turn it on. And the one we were testing with. 

Speaker 3  (23:37)
But that can be like done today, I'll put in the ticket and they'll do it 

Speaker 1  (23:41)
Yeah, let's make sure we get across all the The Italians running run. 

Speaker 2  (23:47)
Go. 

Speaker 3  (23:48)
It was actually we were doing everything right? I don't know if you saw my email with if you look at the dictionary. Now it's actually just one attribute, so yeah, we didn't need to actually have all that stuff in there, it was just that we weren't scanning the metadata so that that was the issue. 

Speaker 2  (24:06)
So When I went to go to Sr I Paul gr. 

Speaker 3  (24:09)
Yeah, I'll turn it on and 

Speaker 2  (24:11)
It just makes our life a little bit. 

Speaker 1  (24:13)
Yes, please. 

Speaker 2  (24:16)
I know the queer externally, I think this is the second time with running into a situation where something is not enabled in the back end between, I'm not saying the specifically to ESP, but also, ESPN is the only way we can actually get into session, where we actually compare all these values and gold requests, all the flags in the backend. Just make sure when I'm missing anything that is important for us. Um. 

Speaker 2  (24:44)
4 quote, 1 versus 22. 

Speaker 3  (24:47)
We can try Howard, but typically those toggles aren't like made public other customers that ask for that. The only reason this wasn't on is because matazeta scanning just was released. So yeah, the way it changes the way the scanning like fundamentally works. 

Speaker 3  (25:06)
That's why we haven't turned it on for all the tenants, but we don't really have a list of toggles that are like human readable that we can just share out right? You guys aren't the first people to ask for that, but yeah, we'll keep an eye out and you know, if there's anything else that needs to be enabled, this is kind of why we're going through the testing right, so we can definitely put it through, but I don't you. Know, I don't think we're going to get much reaction with that, to be honest with you. 

Speaker 2  (25:35)
So it's this policy, and you know, I wish the answer was different, right? Like a girl we got like I give an example, a proof point, basically, it's not proof point. Let's go up actually have sessions quidos quickly, and we actually get any new flag that has been able. 

Speaker 2  (25:52)
We actually look into that and basically bringing it up to us based on the new upgrades with platforms. Hey, we have this new functionality, right, then you want us to double this song for you right. And even this is not something that the guests want to share with us, because it's now customer, really, how you guys don't want to share whatever song is, I think there should be some sort of script that says, okay, based on the services we should ensure that all these flags are nable. 

Speaker 4  (26:21)
Yeah, I think to your request from like when we add new features, though, and it'll be available on the flag or it'll be available on the lts agent or an agent that's, you know, available for based for specific use cases, we can have a process to share like, you know. What's latest and greatest? 

Speaker 2  (26:41)
But. 

Speaker 4  (26:44)
Yeah, I think we can do something very similar to. Let's go going forward. But like as for like About the specific flags on how we deal with it, we typically in PS we just 

Speaker 3  (27:01)
Yeah, it's unfortunately. It kind of passes on like a case-by-case. Basis, right? 

Speaker 3  (27:08)
I mean, dysfunctionality is not something that would affect the agent behavior right. That's the toggle that's visible within the I was, you know, within the age of realm settings. I'm not sure why this specific toggle wasn't enabled. 

Speaker 3  (27:26)
They said, because it's released, they were just going through the custom, but it'll be user configurable by the end of this month. So again, like when new features come out, there's always some delay in, you know, they'll go. In beta mode for a bit, sometimes you'll see the field there, but like the toggle to make it actually work is not enabled. 

Speaker 3  (27:46)
It's only available upon request so we kind of just deal with it. Case-by-case, but yeah, I think we can. We can beat internally and talk about maybe a plan to get td some more like updated info. 

Speaker 2  (28:04)
Anything that can help us help grip a bit the solution, and that we don't, you know, spend hours and hours to recognize something, and they realize that it's a back instead of that needs to be total. 

Speaker 3  (28:16)
No, I mean, II completely agree with you Howard, I mean, it's, it's kind of frustrated for us too, but because we're not always told on our like PS level like what is what actually needs to have a toggle enabled. So yeah, no I agree, we definitely need to improve that process. Absolutely. 

Speaker 2  (28:35)
Yeah, thank you, I have a question because I guess to the laughs. And so as you guys know, I see that you guys have these now unifies set up where there seems to be way more integration on the DSP and ESPN and ESP. The question that I have, so let's say if we go through our scans, right, then this may be a happy question, but just because it shares the same infrastructure, right. 

Speaker 2  (28:59)
So while we go through a scan, and we look at the data that we detecting, right, like a files, you know, it's going to come up with stuff, and then sleep is going to show stuff here and user and whatever, right? Did you know if this information integrates today with the data security war base that where we can actually come here and say, okay, show me, you know, these files that were picked up by ESPN, and who are the owners like a Korean exploration based on the ESPN data so, you know, if that's possible. 

Speaker 2  (29:33)
It's coming. 

Speaker 3  (29:35)
I don't think it's possible today, just because if you look at the data sources, ESPN is not one of them. Right now, I would assume it's probably coming, because they have added slowly, like the different data sources into this unified alerting platform. So my assumption would be that probably will come. 

Speaker 3  (29:53)
At some point. But I don't have like an exact date for you or anything. 

Speaker 2  (29:59)
Okay, what is the chances that if we are open our I free today that it could be done before we go live next year? 

Speaker 4  (30:09)
And I think you should do it anyways, but we have a call scheduled to schedule a call with the PM. Well, we bring you up in that session too. 

Speaker 2  (30:24)
Technical appreciate it, yeah, because I was sure. So because a week ago with goalkeepers team, we were going all with teams, explorations and the dangers were there and the light they built this. And since I saw the integration, I assumed that that could be possible, but it's not so but if this is something available for ESPN in the future they will poet. 

Speaker 2  (30:49)
I can tell you, that's good. 

Speaker 4  (30:54)
I mean, that's obviously direction I wouldn't refer to vmc when you meet with them to discuss China like 

Speaker 2  (31:04)
That will be great, a second that I personally don't have any questions or issues. Let me go with my list Harris, do you have a chance to look at the language for the Steve ads talking about a couple of years ago? 

Speaker 3  (31:21)
I think it's, I mean, I didn't see any limits like documented, but I was testing it. And it looked like, I mean, at least from that test that I did that, it was like around 30. Yeah, I'll follow-up to see if there's like an official limit. 

Speaker 3  (31:40)
But like I had like, I think, like 70 email addresses and it only displayed 30 of them. So yeah, maybe it's 30, but I'll have to double-check on that as well. 

Speaker 2  (31:53)
Okay. Okay, yeah, most of the stuff that I have in my late shore for this week was like, I email stuff related, and I really had the answer. Do you guys tell me? 

Speaker 2  (32:07)
Do you have any questions regarding your the detector do you want to go over some of the stuff right now? 

Speaker 3  (32:16)
So this is only an hour call. 

Speaker 2  (32:18)
Oh, yes, it's 12, my apologies sorry. 

Speaker 3  (32:22)
Smarter and I got no worries, Don and Jason, if you had something really quick here. 

Speaker 5  (32:29)
Thanks at Paris. I was my quite, I saved it for the end and it's mostly I think I've been communing with nav, we opened up. One of our internal processes is getting standard technical implementation guidelines created in-house per solution, so we provided a description of each of these like DSP, dspm and email protection, but That people were looking for more meat to like, be able to design that so I did email nav a team, just following up, have to see if how that's going, and because basically, until we get that it kind of stalls the process, so that's what I was following over. 

Speaker 4  (33:21)
Yeah, I gotta understand so, so Harris, maybe cop, we backed internally. I got to him checking internally. I figured like if this come up with other ps consultants they're looking at sake. 

Speaker 4  (33:32)
So this is kind of like, I guess an internal document on how they can harden to best practices of using the tool. Don I explain it the best that's correct? I'm not aware of such a document. 

Speaker 2  (33:44)
And sort of connected 

Speaker 5  (33:45)
So you don't have to do a stick dock, you don't have to like have a just do you have something that talks about dspm, and what it does? And what the controls are instead of just like not so much of a high level marketing documents also kind of I guess the say, like an Admin guide, which you can't get off like, I try going to help and documentation that that's just like inside the app. 

Speaker 2  (34:13)
It's interesting. So it doesn't need to get this true Jo. 

Speaker 4  (34:17)
Okay, so you're looking more 

Speaker 5  (34:19)
You don't have to give us a stick, you just need to give us something that describes dspm, as these controls is what we're trying to achieve is the architecture, such as stuff like that. 

Speaker 4  (34:31)
So if you're looking for like 

Speaker 6  (34:33)
For G spm, you're saying, just 

Speaker 5  (34:35)
So for me, yeah, all 3 

Speaker 6  (34:40)
Yes, I really think that a vizette could give me, I looked internally, I don't have like a anything that isn't call it sort of sales related like from seismic or something like that, but would that be kind of product would it be? 

Speaker 4  (34:59)
Yeah, yeah, maybe doesn't misunderstand the requirement, Don. I was thinking it was more like going through all the configurations and like. 

Speaker 5  (35:05)
Yeah, you don't have to, they just want to do what they would be doing something like that. They're not asking you to provide sticks, they just want to know aside, they don't want to marketing dock, that says, hey, we do this, and that they want a little bit more meat saying, these are the components of the product. This is what it does is how it tries to achieve it. 

Speaker 4  (35:27)
Okay, some more detail of like capabilities, document. 

Speaker 2  (35:31)
Yeah 

Speaker 5  (35:32)
I'm almost wondering if an Admin guide would like fill that, so the only my only issue with that is that we wouldn't be pursuing probably all of the the features in the product. Like, for instance, we wouldn't be doing isolation, so I would have to tell them that. 

Speaker 2  (35:50)
Don't don't 

Speaker 5  (35:51)
Cover isolation. 

Speaker 6  (35:53)
Yeah, you have to like when a line item market out or something. And No, I don't want to touch a file that that I mean, just in my mind now I mean, I could, I've tried on a couple different fronts so it's a control, it sounds like a control guy, at least that's what it sounds like you're describing to me. You wouldn't have an example by any chance of one that you've had for a platform that maybe that sounds silly, but even if I could see what something looks like, I can articulate the question better that 

Speaker 4  (36:31)
Yeah, Don. If he has me, you could share that give us like the right level of detail, I think Tim and I were obviously overthinking it. So 

Speaker 5  (36:38)
Yeah, like you could. Yeah, let's recircle back like. I don't think I can't wait. 

Speaker 5  (36:43)
I think maybe we're all overthinking. It is just something that's not marketing. Do you have a PDF or cbn dice for each of these products? 

Speaker 4  (36:54)
Products we do for email, let's see if we can get one for dspn, and at endpoint, those are usually all online, but if we could start with ending guidance that I'll pick it out, that would be it's the easiest for both of us right? I don't know. So 

Speaker 1  (37:10)
It hangs up. 

Speaker 5  (37:11)
Chevron gave me the Arab men guided for the 3 products, so I think that would be a good start, or and maybe that's all we need. 

Speaker 4  (37:21)
Okay, okay, let's take that vacuum. 

Speaker 5  (37:24)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (37:25)
Sex. 

Speaker 1  (37:26)
Hey guys, just a quick update. I've seen Harris already dropped off. If you can 10 more on a bin, can you just keep him an update that he can go ahead and run the screen at how D The EDM from the porto and the detector or any reference hacking against that 

Speaker 6  (37:48)
Like that doesn't seem, that was open Howard, I can ping him. What was that you said? Just tell Harris, he's good to go. 

Speaker 1  (37:56)
Yeah, to run the script have deleted a reference for evm out of the portal. 

Speaker 6  (38:05)
All right now I will ask him to confirm. Hey, I'm running it and B I'm done okay. 

Speaker 6  (38:23)
Okay, thank you. I got I just paying them now. So 

Speaker 1  (38:26)
All right. Thank you phone. 
