
Speaker 1  (00:11)
Is it just me? Are you cut out there Danielle? Yeah, Dan, you cut out right at the key moment. 

Speaker 2  (00:17)
I was going to say, is that my on you or why was it 

Speaker 1  (00:20)
It was like that moment in was the spring coming out of 

Speaker 3  (00:23)
Encrypted emails from the users. 

Speaker 1  (00:26)
Daniel push. You keep cutting out or you want a headset. Hey, Dave ping him internally on a calm. 

Speaker 1  (00:36)
Maybe let them know we're not here. We're gonna I'm doing that. You heard that Daniel, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (00:46)
One second. Sorry. I just I typed it to look at the app Daniel. 

Speaker 1  (00:53)
Hey, we weren't hearing 

Speaker 2  (00:54)
The things from a minute ag. 

Speaker 1  (00:56)
Yeah, write it right when you started. You cut out, I don't know if you're on a headset. See, he might have cut out again. 

Speaker 2  (01:08)
Oh, cutting out that much is much more of an internet connection than a headset. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
I think yeah, probably yeah. 

Speaker 3  (01:16)
Sorry, what's happening is it just 

Speaker 1  (01:18)
Yeah, it sounds like a chew. Cause, we're up with you're cotton in and out of Daniel. 

Speaker 4  (01:27)
And everybody here Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
Baby, you went in that, drop your drop out and come back in. 

Speaker 4  (01:39)
I think he's still getting cut off. 

Speaker 1  (01:41)
Yeah, let's talk well, give him a second. What we said at the beginning right before everyone joined is we don't think it'll be a full hour. Then he had a question for Dan I might add, I would might even recommend if he can't connect. 

Speaker 1  (01:55)
Maybe he might not hear him, but he could type. Maybe that would make it easier. 

Speaker 4  (02:29)
So while we're waiting for Danielle to come back, I just texted him to perhaps try logging out and come back in. See if that fixes the issue. Can you guys hear me? 

Speaker 4  (02:43)
Yes, no. Yeah, so I can't speak up the whole Ic rather subject, but in terms of the subsection of you know, encryption, we're still waiting for the subdomain to be created. There's a lengthy process going through that. 

Speaker 4  (03:03)
And 

Speaker 3  (03:09)
Do you hear me now? 

Speaker 1  (03:10)
Yeah, I don't mind your 

Speaker 3  (03:14)
I don't know what happened. 

Speaker 2  (03:18)
Playing Microsoft, always the easiest way. 

Speaker 4  (03:21)
Exactly. 

Speaker 3  (03:22)
So did you hear my question or not? 

Speaker 1  (03:24)
We didn't can you hold on? So we could just okay, tammel for 1 second I think for children at least on the question. Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (03:32)
Actually 

Speaker 4  (03:33)
I was just saying that, you know, Sr is a bigger Object for me to talk about, but the section for encryption, we're waiting for the subdomain to be allowed for us to create, and once that is set up and the dns record is created, we will provide those information for you guys, so we could all set it up, and then we will start testing Now, how long that will definitely take? It's kind of a problem for me because kind of first time I'm going through this process so I'm not sure how long it will take for the subdomain to be created. 

Speaker 4  (04:14)
But I'm hoping within next week, I should be able to get some results because I've been waiting already for about a week. 

Speaker 2  (04:23)
Of course, and keep in mind that the subdomain is arbitrary, it can be anything you want it to be the important part here is the certificate. The certificate is going to let external recipients know that the website belongs to TV bank. 

Speaker 4  (04:39)
Perfect. That's great to know yeah? There's also a site discussion about which still me and Danielle Franco and Phil have to discuss probably even jet that whether we want two separate portals for our customers, you know, one for apps and one for user traffic, or do we want to combine and merge them? 

Speaker 4  (05:06)
I think we will discuss that tomorrow. In our team meeting so and come up with some unified 

Speaker 5  (05:13)
And certainly, since we were mentioning that, did you guys have any problems with I guess application traffic throwing flowing through the the seg I guess. 

Speaker 2  (05:27)
Now for the encryption portal, if the goal is to have a single portal, we'll overlook any rules area Gray area there for that. 

Speaker 4  (05:39)
Okay. Could Daniel, please go ahead? Okay, I had a question. 

Speaker 3  (05:46)
Yeah, I have a question of the for mfa, right? I would like to have a clear understanding from proof point where is mfa, employed devices on Prem devices versus, you know, a mean portal Vs specifically for encrypted email, the user portal that we were trying to set up 

Speaker 2  (06:09)
Yep, so for unprem and the Admin portals, it's going to be mfa, is going to be tied to your idp. Basically, your identity provider is allowing the initial login anyway, so you can tie an mfa into that idp, i.e., in addition to typing your password, you have to you know, type a pattern from a token, or click a UK or something like that for end users logging into the encryption portal. There is no mfa, because all of those users would have to be registered with an mfa before being allowed access, and that's just not possible. 

Speaker 3  (06:50)
Okay, that makes sense. So the user, okay? 

Speaker 2  (06:57)
External encryption users, there is no mfa. Everybody else mfa, is through your identity provider. 

Speaker 3  (07:09)
I didn't think about that for sure, but then it's right like how would you register unless you do it at the time of the registration? Couldn't you do it then at the time of the registration like whenever you whenever your user is being created on The portal can also tie to something that will be made there. 

Speaker 5  (07:34)
Our abuse potentially create one during that time. Because 

Speaker 2  (07:39)
No, because that M fa still has to go through your ID. P. So unless you're putting every external recipient as a contact in your Azure, system, there is no mfa at the time of the registration, there's the confirmation email that goes out, which requires a code to be put in. 

Speaker 3  (08:00)
Okay, so maybe that's good enough. For sure than we have sat the date. 

Speaker 4  (08:08)
Yes, echo works sorry. I missed the question, but echo works does have mfa solution for the external customers. 

Speaker 3  (08:18)
Do you know how that works? 

Speaker 4  (08:24)
I do have a documentation from echo works, explaining all that I could share that with you. 

Speaker 3  (08:31)
Yeah, if you don't mind, I would like to understand the difference absolutely, because probably they have their own solution for this, because they're not using right now. A cord so well. Don't forget. 

Speaker 4  (08:46)
Yeah, they're only it's a company that only concentrates on encryption. Nothing else, right, so obviously you know. They have more time too. 

Speaker 5  (08:58)
If you're creating a database for the users anyway, right? I'm thinking if they're They can, potentially, if they have their own mfa, they can do something like that. 

Speaker 3  (09:10)
Yeah, but they thought They're probably, and that correct me, probably you're just picking back in on the identity, that it's sure for mfa, right, correct? You don't have your own Gears or processes behind the scene that will do the mfa, you're just picking back onto the existing Azure, identity. Correct. 

Speaker 3  (09:36)
And try the ok. Yeah, so that's the difference, because echoes right now, it's doing has its own process for it, but its own mechanism behind the scene that does all of that, right? Because of course, it's not integrated with the edge, right? 

Speaker 3  (09:54)
No, it's no, no, no, it's not. Yeah, okay, so that's that's what the difference is. Okay, the reason why we're asking that is because we have a finding On our end, on the TV side for MFA onto the user porto, right So that's, that's, that's the reason for partially. 

Speaker 3  (10:17)
That's the reason for my question. 

Speaker 2  (10:20)
I feel like for the user that makes sense. 

Speaker 6  (10:22)
Yeah, but for the user portal, because we have WW hon college windows for hello, they will have it because it's already integrated. It'll be integrated with entreas, so you have a kind of novel. 

Speaker 5  (10:36)
No, no, no, we're talking about the customers. 

Speaker 6  (10:40)
Oh, external customers? Yeah, that's 

Speaker 2  (10:43)
@gmail.com, who receives an encrypted message from exactly Bang. 

Speaker 6  (10:48)
So internally it's covered, so again externally, that's a different thing, and that's probably an enhancement that's required. 

Speaker 2  (10:57)
Yeah, internally, there's what is called decrypticist, where responses from those external recipients. I eat boba, gmail.com, gets an encrypted email from you when he clicks reply that email is in the proofpoint portal, and then we just deliver it through normal channels to your outlook, clients. So your users will receive the the email and they won't have to log into the encryption board. 

Speaker 3  (11:29)
Yeah, no, no I get that. Yeah, you're right. So maybe from our end, we have to rephrase that finding for shadding to maybe we split into internal and external, because putting internal users as Ania mentioned, we do have that this is going to be part of it is just the external users. 

Speaker 3  (11:46)
Are going to be? They're not going to have the top shot, right? Which they might be okay with that. 

Speaker 4  (11:55)
Well, I'm sure external users will be cause we haven't had any requests so far in all these years from an external user. Or is your MFA right? 

Speaker 3  (12:04)
Glide, no, no, I'm just wondering from the standpoint of security things from our to get them off. Our back from the security standpoint, right if we break that into say into 2, and we say, yeah, for internal, it's going to work just fine, we do have mfa by entra, but for external, we do not. There might be okay with that, because it's it's external, it's their job to figure out, okay. 

Speaker 3  (12:31)
Okay, so that was my question. Then that's that's, that's what I have. 

Speaker 2  (12:38)
I know it's been put in as an RFE before the hard part is figuring out all right, where does the source database for that MFA live? Because yeah, at that point you would have to get the those external users to be using something like Google authenticator. Yeah, and I know that we have Google authenticator tie into the product coming up for local administrator accounts on proof point systems. 

Speaker 2  (13:06)
I.e. you'll be able to set up a Google authenticator tie it in for mfa for the pod Admin account. I don't know if that's going to be extended to the encryption users, though Yeah 

Speaker 7  (13:18)
Dan, let me show my experience, I had a customer I had let's request but they have a Siam, so we can do great with their Siam. So that way you get suicidal, maybe there are already onboard with the reportal most I am support like social logians. So if that becomes requirement, the only gotcha is that we only support one idp, so your administration should also be able to authenticate against the cyam. 

Speaker 2  (13:48)
Which is not ideal? 

Speaker 3  (13:53)
And how would he work with Cheryl boxes? Or not share milburgh, but okay with accounts that are being accessed by multiple users. So a company received the problem. 

Speaker 3  (14:06)
Yeah, yeah, you know what I mean, right? Yeah. Okay, so okay, so let's rephrase this into internal and external, and see if that's going to I've been in African And we'll take it from there. 

Speaker 3  (14:26)
Yeah, okay. So I think that that's pretty much all the questions that we have, unless somebody else's questions, as I said, we will probably have more next week. Because we're hoping that the own print devices on prim appliances are going to be, we're going to get access to them. 

Speaker 3  (14:49)
Tomorrow, it's still some firewalls on the TV side, and then we're gonna go with the configuration, and we might have some questions. 

Speaker 2  (15:04)
Yeah, yeah, of course. 

Speaker 1  (15:05)
Again, when we, when we'd be doing low balancing for that, or is that something td would do and just ask your, that's out of what you would advise on, like on the agents and stuff like that. 

Speaker 2  (15:17)
For the ongoing clients is that that's up to TV's 

Speaker 1  (15:21)
Okay. 

Speaker 3  (15:21)
All right, you know yeah, this us 

Speaker 1  (15:24)
So when you, I let me say in another way, cause I'm simple. Daniel, maybe when you set up these appliances, and you said, you might have some questions, the questions coming back for would it be more about email routing and things like that. 

Speaker 3  (15:37)
Yeah, you know, yeah, configuration and stuff like that, not load balancing that, we do it ourselves via fives, pipes and stuff like that. So we take care of that, it might be some. These appliances should not have. 

Speaker 1  (16:13)
So if you To have no preference, let's say the Tuesday or Thursday, or what you may walk into. I'd like to help you make sure so we're ready for it, but if it's pretty 

Speaker 2  (16:25)
Oh, I've directed plenty of times before II don't 

Speaker 1  (16:28)
So that's, I call it. Yeah, I'm just looking out for us. I want to maximize the opportunities Daniel, if you say next week, get be Tuesday or Thursday with Dan Wheeler and we're good to go. 

Speaker 3  (16:39)
Yeah, as I said, most likely would not, it's nothing or shuttering is going to happen and we know exactly what needs to be done, but just in case we run into some issues, at least we can I know we can rest it then. 

Speaker 2  (16:53)
Yeah, I've heard it's 

Speaker 1  (16:54)
Anyway, but yeah, yeah, and for team proof point, what I've been doing is because this is a Dan Wheeler, it's an assigned A project, if you will, whatever we named it And our tool. Daniel, you just Dan G you just say, hey, we're done, we might have a few questions. I could check with Dave Reese, I can sign off with you and say yeah, this has all been completed and I market complete. 

Speaker 1  (17:19)
That's all, I just I just don't want to miss it, because I want to make sure we're focused on where we need to focus primarily emassaging inbound outbound, routing and Sr application traffic wear refresh is more consultary consultation. Thank you appreciated everyone. 

Speaker 3  (17:40)
So, does anybody else from the TV side have any questions for then, or for proof point for them? Now I have anybody 

Speaker 2  (17:51)
That was like if you're okay today. 

Speaker 3  (17:54)
Yeah, yeah, yep, yeah, if not, thank you so much for attendance today and we'll talk next week. 

Speaker 2  (18:01)
Always happy to help cause doctor folks later. Thank you 

Speaker 3  (18:04)
Okay, thank you so much. 
