
Speaker 1  (00:01)
With you, because Prada group to talk about Some upcoming stuff that you're working on with ub ID, and how that possibly plays into our ability to do you know, self-service key registration? Which is kind of one of the places where we were having some potential challenges And I know Shaquille, you asked us to I'll provide our kind of you know flows that we were looking at. And you know, I think that we get this, probably, you know, we were before we started to dive into the flows, we were also looking at a high level at our user stories like what are our use cases? 

Speaker 1  (00:52)
And I don't know that we had flushed them out entirely, but we had flushed out enough of them that we wanted to kind of take a high level pass through. Of the intended flows, I want to note Shaquille, that right now, we're really in design right and so we're gathering requirements and business use cases and kind of drafting out these high level flows mostly from a scratch pad perspective to help inform the design right? Because obviously there's a very large difference from a design perspective between Just shipping people a replacement key from ubico, versus deploying the ubian roll app to all of our managers versus If you're developing and deploying an onboarding portal um that is surfaced externally and available for for security registration purposes, right? 

Speaker 1  (01:54)
Like those are 3 very different paths from a design perspective that have significant impact to, you know, program timeline cost. Development effort, you know etc right? And so part of the reason for us to kind of take a first pass through some intended user flows was to help us identify gaps from a design perspective and figure out what options are available and allow us to kind of bake out what options we need to look at. 

Speaker 1  (02:22)
In order to proceed forward right? Obviously the outset of the design. It's that we'll be continuing to work with our BSA, who's Anthony? 

Speaker 1  (02:36)
To actually, you know detail out You know, more detailed and comprehensive user flows, that will be kind of an output of that work right. So right now what we have is more scratch pad to help us identify gaps that we need to go figure out from a design perspective than, you know, intended target states, right? 

Speaker 2  (03:04)
Yes, understood. And yeah, and that's why I felt. If once you're ready to share what you have That could also help us determine whether there are gaps in any of these It flows that you're currently evugging. 

Speaker 2  (03:29)
And so we can, we can determine, or we can help determine Where they could be optimizations, or you know, if there are areas where we have any types of recommendations, we can also provide those back to you. But yeah, absolutely understand where you are. As far as the stage is concerned as well as the, you know, the timeline. 

Speaker 2  (03:53)
And that we're also considering, and Putting it all together and just trying to identify, you know, what can work where and when and how so fully fully understand now 

Speaker 1  (04:08)
Yeah, it makes sense. So Anthony, I gotta be honest with you. I hate these blackboards. 

Speaker 1  (04:20)
And I hate him. Not because there may not be useful to you, but like for me to go back and look at. Okay, where's our business requirements and our business use cases. 

Speaker 1  (04:33)
We didn't really document them out instead, like we just put a bunch of sticky notes like like you started doing this whiteboard and put a bunch of sticky notes, and then you started making whiteboards per session. So now there's just a bunch of hodgepodge information all over the place. And I don't have like A consistent place to go back to where I can say, here's our retail use cases that we're trying to base against. 

Speaker 3  (04:54)
No, well, we do have it, I've been here, I've been documenting this. You see this. And I've been putting our notes as we gather them. 

Speaker 1  (05:12)
Yeah, but this is just a bunch of different stuff kind of put together, and you've got stuff like emotions in here, like I don't understand why. 

Speaker 3  (05:19)
No, they have to be the stories are right here at the top. 

Speaker 4  (05:27)
And the shipping low yeah, you 

Speaker 1  (05:29)
I think guidelines and cleanup and governance guardrails and stuff and like that's not use, that's not a use case, that's a decision. 

Speaker 3  (05:38)
I told you you are an actor this can be easy compared to the. I can give you this thing, use cases immediately from this. Also, it's everything is in there somehow or the other But we need to know exactly how you want it. 

Speaker 3  (05:56)
Do you want it as an Excel sheet? Do you you know? Initially, we started with an Excel sheet, and it started getting all messy, all colorful and everywhere all over the place. 

Speaker 1  (06:07)
Yeah, no I you know. Again, if we just look at industry standard requirements gathering, right? We have high level. 

Speaker 1  (06:16)
We have use cases, and we have high level requirements. And we have detailed requirements, right? I think you From a use case perspective, right? 

Speaker 1  (06:28)
There's obviously functional and non-functional use cases. Obviously the we started document that out in a page and confluence right like I captured some functional requirements and also some non-functional requirements right you were right there on the prior page. 

Speaker 3  (06:44)
I don't know. I'll just show you something I'm doing for the other project. This is how we are actually 

Speaker 1  (06:55)
Going right back to our project. 

Speaker 3  (06:56)
Yeah, so we've been rumbling for a link. I just went back to So here this is what I'm doing this is the way we're capturing Requirements for other projects right now. So we have requirements exactly like this. 

Speaker 3  (07:17)
If we have requirements, we have 

Speaker 1  (07:20)
The use cases or user stories 

Speaker 3  (07:24)
That's where that's where the okay. Let me just take something. Okay, you see this. 

Speaker 3  (07:31)
Yeah, this is our captain business requirement. The functional requirement, the technical requirement, and what is the acceptance criteria that's another busier capturing thing is, you know, different people like it in different ways, some like it. You know, the first few some like it this way, there are. 

Speaker 3  (07:49)
This is how i90% of the time I capture it right now, we mean scratch, predicting everything. So I've been putting it in a way that I can keep up with and sure enough, I know I can easily convert what you saw to this format easily. That's 

Speaker 1  (08:06)
I think this is what we're going 

Speaker 3  (08:08)
Find the need in this episode. Looking for this, it can easily converted to this also. 

Speaker 4  (08:13)
I'm sorry cause this isn't This is just to acquire its format. Doesn't match user stories, right? So there's three things right? 

Speaker 4  (08:22)
There's functional non-functional Requirements, and then how the story does the requirements for how the stories would proceed. Succeed or the stories drive those requirements based on how they work, right? They're not, they're not the same thing for the doctor. 

Speaker 4  (08:40)
Two different things. The require What's been the stories right? Or no? 

Speaker 3  (08:44)
I see, I'm sure I assure you another way, I'll show you another way there's another, but just 1 second. Let me see, because we got every, you know, every some people expect it in a in a particular format, some people expect it in, I just assure you another one. And we have got One second. 

Speaker 3  (09:29)
It's like a we can even go that given when then format. So if you look at this You see the 

Speaker 1  (09:40)
Hey hey hey I was second to Anthony. 

Speaker 3  (09:44)
You killed. 

Speaker 1  (09:45)
For the purpose of today's conversation, we're working with our BSA to kind of Pulled together some information, we will end up working on more life cycle. Use cases at some point and may not even get to that in today's call, I just want to make sure that we're not wasting your time, uh uh Understood. Yeah, so there's there's plenty to talk about with you. 

Speaker 1  (10:11)
But I don't also don't want you to sit through the internal minutiae of us. Formatting, our requirements. 

Speaker 2  (10:21)
I mean, I have this time blocked. I can certainly hang out if that's okay. 

Speaker 1  (10:25)
Yeah, yeah, okay. Just I didn't, I wanted to just ensure that If you need it or wanted to cut loose, I don't know what value being on this particular call would be. That's all Sorry, Anthony. 

Speaker 3  (10:46)
No, so this is another way, so we actually put in given when there's stuff kind of thing. So is that? 

Speaker 1  (10:55)
No, I don't think that that's that's 

Speaker 3  (11:01)
You know? 

Speaker 1  (11:04)
I don't think that that's what we need for this. I think, from a user's story perspective. Our user stories are things like, and I started to capture that in confluence, when we started to go through They need to sign into a shared retail device for the first time they're issued a laptop, but also need to sign into a shared desktop, they forget or lose their Fido key, they're working at another location for the day and didn't bring their key. 

Speaker 1  (11:31)
They're terminated and need to return the key they They're accessing A An application from their mobile device that requires 

Speaker 3  (11:43)
If you wanted there as single breakdown in steps that can also be done, it's all there, anything else. How granular do you want these stories? 

Speaker 4  (11:54)
These use cases I guess they kind of are business requirements and then function they drive functional requirements and then everything's subject to sort of the non-functional whatever requirements. 

Speaker 1  (12:07)
Right, we were, we were basing these off of user stories, and we had started to capture user stories in the whiteboard, Anthony, but now it's not in the whiteboard anymore. 

Speaker 3  (12:19)
It means if you look at this our whiteboards have is it? It's They were there in blue stickers, 1 second. Yeah, because we've been doing that. 

Speaker 1  (12:41)
I see. Am I seeing there was 

Speaker 3  (12:43)
The rain, they're all there, they're all there. So you see here we do have we did, because everything was being done scratch pad. I was trying to, and I put them all into an Excel, which I can understand where they are right now, but how granular should these stories be? 

Speaker 3  (12:57)
Like the way you spoke, you literally broke it down into, very, very granular steps. Do we need high levels, or do we need to capture each and every action over there? Like you said, a person needs to His first day in a person loses key person needs to log in person needs to Get a test, stated, something like, do you need all of that in Very granular. 

Speaker 3  (13:34)
Because then we'll have to I can do that. Also, that's not a problem. It's all there. 

Speaker 3  (13:39)
The thing is, how granular do you want it to be? The information is there. It's just a matter of How how deep are we going to? 

Speaker 3  (13:55)
How granalized are we going to make it 

Speaker 1  (13:59)
I was granular, as we need to Anthony, so 

Speaker 3  (14:03)
If I can go very well on the 

Speaker 1  (14:06)
These are stories, right? Right now you have them in Fun, little blue. 

Speaker 3  (14:13)
Yeah, I have them improved, but yeah. 

Speaker 1  (14:16)
But the reality is that we're going to have to make those more efficient, right? And then those stories are, what's driving out Our requirements right. So we made the decision to take the stories and break them down into our Our use cases right so for this use case, here's how it could flow. 

Speaker 1  (14:39)
We decided to break into that rather than just define specific requirements, because we felt that that would help us define specific requirements, right? So if we look at our options for the use case of a user, losing their Fido key, depending on what option we go with from a design perspective that also helps us drive out requires, and I realize it's a little bit backwards, there are some requirements that That are irregardless of the solution being picked, but then there are requirements that also get driven by whatever option we decide that we want to go with as well, right? 

Speaker 3  (15:12)
Yeah, because because then it'll get a mix of everything we won't know whether this is an option story or is it like, you know, some sort of grouping will have to be done I guess at some stage. Because if you just if I just keep on listing every action we actually spoke of it's going to be quite lengthy. 

Speaker 1  (15:39)
Well, from a user's story perspective, we should be capturing All actions, right, but there's there's non. Well I don't know if I would consider These are that non-functional, I was thinking about, there's non-functional type requirements, like, for example, if we use a spare key, and we need to issue a replacement for the spare stock, right like that's a requirement. 

Speaker 3  (16:02)
No paid. But it's not not for change. This is not a law for 

Speaker 1  (16:07)
It's right. The use case is the user loses their key, and they need a replacement from the spare pool. 

Speaker 4  (16:14)
Right right, the non-functional requirements constrain the use cases, and then the use cases or constrain the user story, how we respond to the user's stories, and then the user's stories. Given the strains Drive the technical, I guess, technical or whatever functional requirements right like a like. We need to have an internet facing mobile friendly user portal to let users self register. 

Speaker 4  (16:45)
The key or something, but that's that's driven from the user story, and but then that it's non-functional requirements that'll affect parameters of that, like, users need to be, you know. I did any verification in order to be able to self registry their key hearing self register their to register their ub by a self-service or something. I guess that's kind of where I'm thinking about. 

Speaker 4  (17:10)
How do that makes sense, right? That's kind of a non the nonfunction, I think a non-functional. Margaret is mostly being constrained. 

Speaker 4  (17:19)
The functional requirements is being we need to do to fulfill the user stories. But maybe we call business requirements aside one thing Anthony, if yours, the user store stories were summarized as business requirements and the technical requirements kind of fell out of that. 

Speaker 3  (17:38)
Yeah, that's what if you had to Let's just take a simple example. Okay, so if I were to write a story, user writes a little without a usable fireball, because it's lost, then do we need another one because it's stolen? 

Speaker 4  (17:57)
Local spare decision, another column, another difference 

Speaker 3  (18:01)
What is that? That's not like story that's a yeah, so this is a like, say, this is the grouping now do we need two separate 1 story for A A story for we need to send the key to someone or the person comes into the office and gets it from the spare pool. 

Speaker 4  (18:22)
I just felt this formatively mixed. 

Speaker 3  (18:24)
No, no, this is what I didn't see. I know this for methane mold makes sense to you, but if I break this down into the way. Jeremy's asking yeah, every action will require like laws will require one stolen will require one broken will require one. 

Speaker 3  (18:42)
Whether it's shipped will require one whether 

Speaker 4  (18:45)
Bixby when why would they require? I guess right? That's why we have if we determine lost stolen broken or that yeah. 

Speaker 4  (18:54)
We have to tell the story and figure out if our response is different. And if the response is the same, then they don't have to be different stories. 

Speaker 3  (19:02)
Yeah, but do we take that decision before I write or after we write? 

Speaker 4  (19:09)
I thought we were doing that as we walked through all of the walks through the use case. I 

Speaker 3  (19:14)
I don't, yeah, so According to me, according to our discussion laws, broken and forgotten all is just one story, just different actions. 

Speaker 4  (19:30)
Loss. Stalin, broken and We're unusable, are all the same story. I thought 

Speaker 3  (19:38)
Yeah, but the way Germany saying we also needed to be a little bit more granular. 

Speaker 4  (19:44)
But we needed more granular, in terms of what does that actually mean, not? Who 

Speaker 3  (19:49)
Do we need to not breathe like that as like, if I've been doing yes, same team actually, so, but if I if I were to, look at it stolen? And broke and broken are two different things stolen may require a different action. It may require you contacting a global security. 

Speaker 3  (20:09)
Someone came and stole my key, someone broke into the branch and stole keys. It's not the same as broken in this case, because then broken, I actually know that it's broken. It's in my hand. 

Speaker 3  (20:24)
So it's a different action. 

Speaker 4  (20:26)
Care that we need to ask whether the process is different, but in practice right either of those keys should be unregistered from the users, but it's stolen might be more sensitive so yeah. 

Speaker 3  (20:36)
Yeah, you know, there are different risk levels. There's a different risk level, then shipping do I-ship? 

Speaker 4  (20:46)
I guess you're convincing me that we do need to do me more. Granular, kind of like Jeremy was saying, right? All of these things need to be separate flows. 

Speaker 3  (20:53)
And we could say, you use, yeah, then somebody, if you're sure I write it first, and then we say, is it groupable, or is it purely individualistic? Or is it purely? 

Speaker 4  (21:04)
Yeah, what are we doing about? 

Speaker 3  (21:06)
Yeah, what I'll be doing about it is. Does it take us slightly different path or does it just follow the same path? You know, it's for me to write it down. 

Speaker 3  (21:18)
Yes, but The grouping will have to come after I write it down. Like we're not shipping even shipping as an issue. Even shipping do I-ship only the key or do I-ship it with the password or do I-ship it and the person comes in gets his password from the manager. 

Speaker 3  (21:41)
See there are 3, you know, it just keeps on creeping up. 

Speaker 4  (21:48)
I don't know how we deal with that without answering all of those questions. 

Speaker 3  (21:53)
So do we do we have just one story for shipping, or do we have three separate stories for shipping? 

Speaker 4  (22:00)
Decisions are should. Decisions are part of the user story. It might be different depending on the situation. 

Speaker 4  (22:07)
Sorry, that's that's a decision that's not a different use case. That's a decision to make in each of the use case. 

Speaker 3  (22:13)
Yeah, so do we do I capture it as As a user story, and then we break out the acceptance story, we break it down the user experience 

Speaker 4  (22:24)
Doing historians that they lost their key and whether the ship and ships to them Vs local is a decision within each of the stories. And that's what I was saying with one of your earlier sheets, right? Like you have use your stories. 

Speaker 3  (22:39)
Oh, yes, yes. 

Speaker 4  (22:40)
Besides each of those stories 

Speaker 3  (22:41)
So if I were to okay, let's just take the story of the shipping. Ship the key, this story is about shipping. The key. 

Speaker 3  (22:48)
Now, what 

Speaker 4  (22:48)
There's a story about shipping the key, there's a story about the user lost their key. What do we ship it? Do we ship them a replacement, or do they take a local spare? 

Speaker 4  (22:58)
It's not a story, it's a it's A 

Speaker 3  (23:01)
It's a floor it's a floor here now. We moved from stories to a flow. 

Speaker 4  (23:08)
Right, it's a flow within each of the stories. It's not a story on its own. 

Speaker 3  (23:13)
No, but we need a decision right, lost the key. Okay, what does he do? What is the acceptance criteria for this to close the story? 

Speaker 3  (23:25)
If he's lost the 3 Does he have to contact somebody, or does he have to go to the spare? 

Speaker 4  (23:33)
That's why sorry, that's why we're writing up the user story, so we can define those things. 

Speaker 3  (23:37)
Yeah, so I'll have to go very granular. I'll have to go very, very granular, for each of them, and then we put an acceptance criteria for each of them. Some may have the same acceptance criteria, and then we can group them 

Speaker 4  (23:55)
Acceptance criteria for what 

Speaker 3  (23:58)
For what do you do when your key is lost? Yes Yes, forget the shipping part. Just what do you do in the keys lost? 

Speaker 3  (24:11)
What is the acceptance of the stadium? What is the acceptance criteria for that particular story? 

Speaker 4  (24:18)
You have a new key, and you can sign at your computer with it. 

Speaker 3  (24:21)
Yeah, but where do you take a new flow? Now we need another story. Now we need another story here where do you take away key from? 

Speaker 3  (24:29)
Does it come ship to you or do you go to your spare Pooh? 

Speaker 4  (24:33)
That's not an acceptance criteria. 

Speaker 3  (24:35)
No, yeah, but if we had put that as an acceptance criteria, then we need another story. 

Speaker 4  (24:42)
What do you mean as an acceptance criteria? But what is 

Speaker 3  (24:44)
So so I have lost my tea, I have sex reluctance criteria, get another key, you know, it'll trigger another story. Get another key from here. 

Speaker 4  (24:58)
Right, the big thing, in other story, what do you mean? It's part? It's part of the 

Speaker 3  (25:03)
We just created another action. It'll create another action. That's what how granular do we want our stories? 

Speaker 4  (25:11)
But we have to know all of the steps I guess we need to trace back like we were doing in the previous calls and to trace back to every step that might be required. 

Speaker 3  (25:22)
Right, so let me remember. Okay, let me go back to let me 

Speaker 4  (25:24)
Okay, generally the story that we 

Speaker 3  (25:27)
Let me take him out and let me take you to steps. Is this what we are looking for? Employee begins onboarding in workday. 

Speaker 3  (25:35)
Outka, a new higher identity is available for it. But I sail point detects the new high through birth recognitioning the user is evaluated from is this the type of story stuff that we need? If you're going to go the steps, then you're going to have to do steps like this. 

Speaker 4  (25:53)
And that's what we were already doing. And this is an interesting diagram, though it's not very detailed. 

Speaker 3  (25:59)
No, that's what I'm going to do this week. I've just been going into high levels, hoping that then I can write the stories for each of these boxes. Each of these blocks will require stories. 

Speaker 3  (26:16)
It's not the story. It's the block It's the let's put it in our in TV terminology, it's our epic So do we want to go? If you're going steps, you'll have to go like this. 

Speaker 3  (26:34)
This is a very high level. Of course. But if you want, if you want to go in steps, you'll have to go this way. 

Speaker 4  (26:42)
This doesn't tell us anything about how any of this is done. So this is irregard. 

Speaker 3  (26:48)
I got put into details, this is high level stuff. This is very high level. This is high levels. 

Speaker 4  (26:52)
But if we don't have a way to fulfill it, we can't put it in as a high level, I guess that's why we were getting into the details on the earlier calls, because if we don't Know us. Any of this is possible, then writing out a flow. It's a little bit like 

Speaker 3  (27:05)
Yeah, because if you need to know the details, we'll have to go with business functional technical And acceptance criteria. This is how we love to do it. We need to know how we're doing it. 

Speaker 3  (27:22)
Provide news with control mechanisms to manually trigger outborn, email encryption. I still remember whatever you need to support power, so what does it need to support? It needs to support subject based stuff outlook plugins. 

Speaker 3  (27:37)
Preserve the encryption, how do we do it? We configure in proof point or something like that, the acceptance criteria emails, we'll have to do it like this. If we'll have to take a business requirement, what you're looking for is a business requirement, shipping, that's the business requirement, what are the consumers? 

Speaker 4  (27:58)
I'm saying, does this? What do you mean that shipping isn't a business requirement? I mean, I was super at a business requirement. 

Speaker 3  (28:06)
And you have to ship the key, right? That's not a technical job, that's a manual task. Somebody's going to have to do it. 

Speaker 3  (28:14)
Now it's a it's our technical, it's not a technical requirement. 

Speaker 4  (28:23)
Right? But it's a it's a requirement to support the business requirement of the user who has lost gold. On whatever their key needs to get a replacement key, right? 

Speaker 4  (28:34)
And then there's decisions along that path. So as to how they get the replacement key, which may entail shipping or not. But that's not I don't know. 

Speaker 4  (28:44)
It's, I guess it's it's a fair question. What level of granularity do the business requirements need to be? 

Speaker 3  (28:50)
Yeah, yeah, that's the that's the biggest problem. And if we could go into a rabbit hole, if we go to granular. 

Speaker 4  (28:57)
But we need to be able to get to exactly how this is being done, so that we know what the solution components are. 

Speaker 3  (29:03)
Because even if you do write a stories, there are some stories that we may not be able to write the acceptance criteria for it'll have to be written by somebody else, because we don't do it. 

Speaker 4  (29:13)
Who else would write? 

Speaker 3  (29:15)
The retail will have to write them, maybe even ep may have to write them, maybe even global security may have to write them because these are physical stuff, this is physical stuff. Stolen becomes global security thing. 

Speaker 4  (29:34)
They just define the non-functional requirements, not how we define it. 

Speaker 3  (29:37)
Address it no, but they'll have. They'll have a they'll have a kind of what it trigger point, right? He stole and immediately called this number. 

Speaker 4  (29:49)
Right? That's a non-functional requirement for our solution. 

Speaker 3  (29:52)
In our case, it's a law functional requirement, but for somebody who we are, the branch manager is not going to act on something that's stolen, nor is the, nor are we, we are not going to be able to control anything sitting at a desktop or a laptop. All right, go for it. 

Speaker 4  (30:14)
But we need to define what's done, and that's it's 

Speaker 3  (30:17)
Yeah, in that case, and it's beyond our scope to define that, because it's a physical asset. 

Speaker 4  (30:24)
I don't know why would it be beyond our sco? 

Speaker 3  (30:27)
I give it to a story, and it's stolen, right? I mean, like, you know, if someone breaks and steals a laptop. What I've known a person who lost his laptop here in td, and he had to go through all that gsd stuff, where do you leave it? 

Speaker 3  (30:44)
In some cases, I think it even becomes a police complaint. 

Speaker 4  (30:49)
But that what we do about it from a from the system that is providing the right that is Driving the replacement key and the person needs to interface with to. Yeah, it' Get their replacements key so that they can continue doing their work. 

Speaker 3  (31:07)
Yeah, so Aaron, that's what I'm saying. So if you need a business requirement, then we need to break it down into functional stuff, then, technically what we are going to do with it, and what should be the outcome of it? 

Speaker 1  (31:23)
Okay? So Let's, let's What are the challenges here? Anthony? 

Speaker 1  (31:29)
I think, is just that Some of this stuff has just turned into word salad 

Speaker 3  (31:35)
Yeah, it's going to be that's what we're going to go into a rabbit hole. And we're just going to end up with smithing it. 

Speaker 1  (31:41)
Yeah, so like you get stuff all over the place here, and I'm just trying to figure out how we pull this back to the basics of what we need from an output perspective, right? Okay, so if we take it back to the basics, right, we started with a few key user personas, right? So we wanted to identify Who are the users right like? 

Speaker 1  (32:02)
What are the personas who are the workers? What are the personas that we have for retail? We had started to document that. 

Speaker 1  (32:08)
And at that time you had to add that in Excel, right? And I think you put it in here into the scratch pad, right? And then we basically wanted to break out. 

Speaker 1  (32:18)
What are the use cases? What are the user stories for these personas, right? They're coming in new for the first time and there's a few variants of that they're losing or forgetting or having their keys stolen. 

Speaker 1  (32:30)
And there's a variant of that right. They are transferring to another location, they are being terminated. They are moving to another roll, right? 

Speaker 1  (32:41)
So those in my mind are our user stories, right? At the end of the day, I want those in something better than a sticky note on a whitebo. 

Speaker 3  (32:52)
Look, yeah, that's what this is all scratch pad stuff that's what I was saying, I've been trying to capture them grouping them in this Excel sheet of wine as to what we are speaking so that I had an understanding of what's going on back and then I showed you it 

Speaker 1  (33:08)
Stuff that you've shown me so far hasn't been some concise list of user stories. It's been 

Speaker 3  (33:13)
It's been just, I'm not sure anywhere. I'm not showing you any user stories right now, I'm not showing you any story user stories right now, I've just been capturing them as they've come in in the best way that I think I can right now. 

Speaker 1  (33:26)
These are requirements, okay. 

Speaker 3  (33:28)
Yeah, do we want them? Do we want them in the form of this way? 

Speaker 1  (33:34)
No, I think that we did want to output requirements. I think the exercise that we've been taking on. The front-end of this on these calls has been we identified the user personas, and the stories, and the purpose of identifying the user's stories was to help us define out some initial options for high level design, because we weren't even sure where to go with high level design, right? 

Speaker 1  (33:58)
So from a high level design perspective, there are several different options that we've been discussing for how to replace a stolen key, for example, right? Or a lost or broken or stolen key, right? And we talked about 

Speaker 3  (34:15)
Yeah, but we have captured everything we've lost. We have not differentiated between loss broken and stolen. We have just said, we don't 

Speaker 1  (34:23)
We don't need to right just like if someone loses their personal laptop, that's not relevant to this use case and I don't care or loses their TD laptop. That is, there's already a business process for that I don't care. In July, we want to focus on the the phyto key specific use cases, and how they're leveraged, right? 

Speaker 1  (34:51)
So what we wanted to make sure is that we captured all of our user stories so that we understood how these keys and what flavors of usage we needed to solve for right? We need to solve for how to replace a key we need to resolve for what happens. When someone terminates, we need to solve for a new user coming into the organization. 

Speaker 1  (35:16)
We need to look at other business use cases like transfer. We need to understand the nuance between A teller that only works on shared devices and a manager that only has their own laptop, right? You know, those those types of business stories are the ones that are, you know, user stories are the ones that we wanted to understand because that then helps us drive out the requirements that we have, and the flows that we need to to 

Speaker 3  (35:45)
Defined, so basically, we also need to convert our questions into stories. 

Speaker 1  (35:53)
Well, once we have answers to the questions, they either align with the story, or they create a new story. Yes 

Speaker 3  (35:58)
No, that's okay. Yeah, so that's why we have to do many of these questions, we don't even have the answer. So the stories will have to be find out what's going on as simple as that. 

Speaker 4  (36:15)
Hey there, what's going on with what 

Speaker 3  (36:17)
Like, how do people start in the first day? Which that becomes a story in our case? 

Speaker 1  (36:22)
That's correct. And so we have a couple of high level. First day stories, right? 

Speaker 1  (36:27)
So our 2 stories are the 2 ones on the left, in the blue right, a new user getting set up in advance of their higher date, and they're getting set up after They're higher late right now. But there's there's more there's more nuance than that right like, and as those are the other 

Speaker 3  (36:46)
The new function are written, but what we call is there's more functionality to it than just two things. There's most 

Speaker 1  (36:54)
Oh, I agree. And so that the point of us identifying the personas, and the high level stories is that I knew that it would generate questions about the specific user stories that we needed to get from our retail divisions, and that's exactly what it did, right. It generated a bunch of questions well, how do they get set up in advance of their heartache. 

Speaker 1  (37:12)
What happens when they walk into the door the first day are they going to a training center? Are they going to a training branch? Are they going to a lab or are they going into the store? 

Speaker 1  (37:20)
Are they starting in the back room? Are they starting on the teleline? Are they shadowing someone? 

Speaker 1  (37:25)
When do they log into their machine for the first time, right? Those are the answers that we need, and that helps us drive out that user story. 

Speaker 3  (37:31)
So is that is so are they one user story, or are they one user story, or they multiply? 

Speaker 1  (37:40)
It'll, it'll likely break into multiple user stories, and the user stories will be a flavor right. So it'll be the high level story is someone starts on their first day, right? The breakdown of those stories, right? 

Speaker 1  (37:54)
Where we break down into the user stories themselves, or the use cases right is I'm a user that's starting in a training center, I'm a user that's starting at on a teleline, I'm a user that's starting on a spare laptop in the branch. I'm a user, that's starting on a service device, right? Those are our user stories, and then we have to look at from a design perspective. 

Speaker 1  (38:15)
How do we handle each one of those stories? How do you log it? So this is the device you're starting from, how are you logging it? 

Speaker 3  (38:22)
Yeah, they will. That's what I'm saying. Yeah, we are, we're actually going to, we are going very granular, so it's going to be a very long list. 

Speaker 1  (38:31)
Yes, this is a very complicated exercise, and there's a lot of there's a lot of moving parts that we have to account for. In order to make this solution viable 

Speaker 3  (38:40)
Yeah, so we are going back to what I said in the right at the beginning. If you look at this, we are going to break we're going to have a story 1 for lost one for broken one. For this, we're going to have for shipping. 

Speaker 3  (38:52)
We're going to have shipping through Korea shipping through something else. Pick it up, something of that sort, so everything that we 

Speaker 4  (39:02)
Even part of the use case, it's not its own 

Speaker 3  (39:05)
No, but according to Jeremy, it's its own thing. 

Speaker 1  (39:09)
That is not what I said. 

Speaker 3  (39:11)
You said we need a design for each of that step. 

Speaker 1  (39:17)
I'm not asking you to create a design for that stuff. 

Speaker 3  (39:19)
No, no, I'm not finding desire or not. 

Speaker 1  (39:23)
So like the shipping Vs local spare decision. Yes, that is a decision, but that's not something that we capture in a user story. That's a design item that's down. 

Speaker 1  (39:34)
That's a decision that we make from a design perspective based on the user stories that we have, and the flows that we define for those user stories. Okay, the whether or not Whether or not we decide to ship a replacement or drop ship a key or whatever is relevant to the user story, the user's story is I lost my key. Right? 

Speaker 1  (40:02)
The how we decide to resolve that is a completely different thing that does not need to be captured as part of the user's story. Now the decision that we make on design might drive requirements, so if we decide that we want to ship a replacement key to a user, then we might have requirements around where we ship that key, that is based on the user's stories, right? We might decide that we need to ship it only to the person's home. 

Speaker 1  (40:30)
We might decide that based on retail requirements, where they say you can't ship it to the home because it requires a signature and the play won't be there, right? Then, maybe we can't trip it to the Hull, right? We might decide to ship to the location well, okay, which location is always going to be the a location that's in HR do they need to be able to specify a location right? 

Speaker 1  (40:50)
Okay, and that's going to lead to fund on by the user's story I eat, where are they, when this happens, right? And so if they say that an employee may not always be at their HR job location and they might be flound, then a requirement for us might be that in the request portal. To ship a replacement key 

Speaker 3  (41:12)
May I have to be able to no, let's start go beyond a story right now? Do we need a story? For let's the second part. 

Speaker 3  (41:22)
To ship a replacement, they have to select. Do we need a story for that? Do we need a story or user has to decide whether to select the location to ship or is it auto generated for it? 

Speaker 3  (41:38)
Do we need a story for that? Or are we going to do that at the next stage after we have evaluated what we're going to take? So is that a story? 

Speaker 3  (41:50)
The user has to decide whether to To submit Brad's location home or It's auto generated. It's an auto generated location for help. We are a design decision, or is that a story 

Speaker 1  (42:17)
I'm sorry which item again, Anthony. 

Speaker 3  (42:19)
The one which you said about shipping 

Speaker 1  (42:24)
That is clearly a design item, and it is not related to a story at all, but there is relation to a story. But that is not what we're trying to capture right now, what we're trying to capture right now is What we're trying to ensure right now is that we have a full capture of user stories. And so here's where we're at, we had started to capture user stories, which we had in spreadsheet format that you moved into these blue sticky notes, right? 

Speaker 1  (42:48)
And there was several there, I think that there's more if you scroll over, I think there was a few more as well, we identified, like I don't know 10 or so, right I don't know if yeah, so there's 10 stories that we had identified so far. Okay, we know that there are going to be more stories or variants of these stories, so we'll have to reformat these a little bit right, like we have a story right now where users getting set up in advance of their higher dates, or users are getting set up after their high date. 

Speaker 1  (43:16)
It may not be that simple, it might be able to keep it at that level, or we might have to break it down a little bit further, depending on the answers that we get from retail, as to what their actual user stories are right. For a new YouTube So we might have a story that's like, and you usually starts at a training center, because that's going to be inherently different now, from a design perspective, we can come back we can look into what are options for those different user stories, and we can decide once we get through, like a high level design. 

Speaker 1  (43:46)
On this, that it's the same answer for several of the stories and we can consolidate them at that time. But for now, we don't have the design right? We're still working through that, so we don't have that information, so we should break down the user's stories to the level that we think we need to, in order to inform the design that's the point, right? 

Speaker 1  (44:06)
So we're trying to get, so there's a few accident items that are happening right now. Andrew met with retail, I forwarded to do that. Meeting advice. 

Speaker 1  (44:12)
I don't know if you made it. I missed it yesterday because I had a call with Microsoft that I couldn't. 

Speaker 3  (44:17)
Yeah, no, we were talking about it about that same meeting just as you joined, you know, I made it for the heat. 

Speaker 1  (44:24)
Yeah, so so I missed that call, but I just got a note from Andrew saying that he's scheduling up a dedicated meeting, they identified a resource to talk to to go through the user stories, but so we will meet with that retail resource for Canadian retail, we're going to have to do the same thing with US retail and we'll, we'll we need these blue stories in a format that we could. That's not a sticky note that we can review with retail. 

Speaker 3  (44:57)
That's why I can wear now. I can give you this level stories quite easily. The blue sticky note level. 

Speaker 1  (45:03)
So and and we can, yeah, so all we all we need to just have that defined, is 

Speaker 3  (45:08)
If you want the blue level, sticky dough type of notes, yeah 

Speaker 1  (45:12)
No, I don't have to after the I've mentioned this. 

Speaker 5  (45:15)
So first up, I'm not a hater, but I despise this whiteboard, like 

Speaker 4  (45:21)
It bothers hell. 

Speaker 3  (45:22)
The thing is, that Excel sheet makes it even worse. Yeah, you remember the first Excel sheet, we were writing all over the place. I couldn't remember I couldn't see nor could he all see anything what I was writing. 

Speaker 4  (45:34)
Let's talk about audience for a second, because I But that sometimes helps to focus the discussion, because Jeremy, you said something, which is I think helpful that if we think about how are we going to, who are we representing this? To forward review? Are we going to like? 

Speaker 4  (45:52)
What level of detail is? Bright level of detail for A But the user's story is insufficient, right? As presented here is certainly insufficient detail for retail, to say, this sounds good to us, the level of detail that we went for the 1 or 2 use cases that we've managed to go through so far is perhaps too much detail. 

Speaker 4  (46:17)
I don't are they going to want to know, but step-by-step, do they want to know exactly what someone's going to have to do, and how long it's going to take, maybe we do need to get to that level of detail with them. 

Speaker 1  (46:27)
Retail is absolutely going to care very much about the options that we decide on, and how long and how complicated those things are. They will 1000% care about that. 

Speaker 5  (46:41)
Yeah, and until yesterday sergey, the meaning that you couldn't make so you know, one thing like, I think it I mean, Chris nobes doesn't matter where, you know, one of the one of them spoke up, and he rattled off. 

Speaker 4  (46:56)
I think it was like stickster, 8 

Speaker 5  (46:59)
Different little scenarios I said, we've talked about all of them Right? So yeah, they absolutely absolutely care. 

Speaker 1  (47:08)
Yeah, and so we want to show them that we are capturing their functional use cases, their user stories, and we want to make sure that they don't have other user stories of their sleeve that we didn't even think of right. And so, we've got a bunch of questions for them, but we want to be able to show them in a format. And so Anthony scroll over on the left campaign. 

Speaker 1  (47:33)
And then click on Fido, key requirements right below ubiko, yat whiteboard, so I had started to kind of like document some stuff while we were talking to retail, and if you look at the one that says functional, use cases, right that loosely aligns with your stickiness. Ignore the description notes, right? But like, essentially, we want something that's like a more formalized version of that that we can review, and it can be complex doesn't matter that we can review with retail, with all the other stuff that we put on the page, right? 

Speaker 1  (48:07)
So we need something in sort of this format that we can add some flavor to in the conversation with retail, and that we can confirm with retail that these actually are their use cases. 

Speaker 3  (48:20)
Right? These are the at the like, like ball supported up. These are at the level of the blue sticky Doge. 

Speaker 3  (48:27)
I agree. Yes, if somebody's the level of detail you're looking for fine with me. And that's 

Speaker 1  (48:35)
Conversation with retail yes, will we 

Speaker 3  (48:37)
That's that's right. That's that's, that's his leader. That's his leader, because remember, we started with that level of a little lesser in. 

Speaker 3  (48:47)
Let me open that accent sheet. I don't remember by the helitas, imagining. Remember, this was the Excel sheet that we started with 1 second. 

Speaker 3  (49:16)
Oh, it's hesitant twice enough of an opening 

Speaker 4  (49:30)
I believe I'm with the initially bunch of ch. 

Speaker 3  (49:33)
See use case. And then we support a small description. This is what we had started with. 

Speaker 3  (49:38)
Then remember then we went. So if we wanted to do this, this type of stuff like you have done in your conference site. Yeah, that's usually done, but we don't have details. 

Speaker 3  (49:51)
We won't have details. Remember that. 

Speaker 1  (49:53)
We don't need the details for the conversation with Rachel right now we're just trying to make sure that we have their user stories and that we understand their use cases. That's the key. 

Speaker 3  (50:02)
That's what I can bring it down to just this level. This is just the use case column part of things, forget description notes, okay, because that's what we started with that's what we started with, and then we went into all the detail. 

Speaker 1  (50:16)
Keep in mind well, keep in mind anything that we're working on a bunch of things in parallel. And that's why things might be getting a little bit confusing, right? 

Speaker 3  (50:22)
Yeah, and I can try to just gather it so that I can keep a track of it, but it's not being shared it just 

Speaker 1  (50:28)
The the the so so The history of how this happened, right is that we knew that we had questions for retail, that we hadn't yet answered. So we knew we couldn't finish these functional use cases. So we decided, hey, some of these functional use cases. 

Speaker 1  (50:44)
We know like lost stolen key, right? We know that that is a valid use case we know that is going to happen. That is a binary users will lose their key, or it will get lost or broken or stolen right? 

Speaker 1  (50:57)
We know that that is a thing, so let's talk about our options for how that flow would work. So let's brainstorm that in the interim of getting the additional data from retail, we're gonna have to do that work either way, and that's what that's what drove the life cycle. Flows that we started working on Now some of the answers from retail will help augment those flows, or potentially even change those flows, or help us decide which blow we can actually choose, because right now we're defining multiple options for those flows. 

Speaker 1  (51:29)
And there's a series of reasons why we might choose one flow Vs another. It might be because it's not viable from a business perspective. It might be because it's not viable from a technical perspective, except 

Speaker 3  (51:43)
Okay, and nope, if let me just do this so that others will end up with the words meeting everything and falling into rabbit h***, so I'll get it down to this level. I will share it with you by tomorrow, okay, let me work on it today. 

Speaker 1  (51:58)
Yeah, no worries. I don't think we have the families. 

Speaker 3  (52:00)
Yeah, green tail, yeah. Yeah. For me, I know where I've captured this, it's actually just my first line over here this row will give us all the cases that you are looking for the others are all details based on, but we don't want to go into details with retail, so I'm just going to keep it to this level of stuff, and I'm quite sure I'll be able to get everything in a room. 

Speaker 3  (52:24)
Okay, yeah, it doesn't have to be because I'm not going to put anybody to put 

Speaker 1  (52:30)
Yes, we want it to be like a typical user's story, right? 

Speaker 3  (52:33)
And I'll tell you, you guys 

Speaker 1  (52:33)
He's a new retail worker. I'm signing into the first time like that kind of thing, right? 

Speaker 3  (52:37)
Yeah, correct. That's it. I'm just going to keep it at the blue, sticky level thing. 

Speaker 3  (52:42)
But we'll have, because we're keeping it at the blue, sticky level thing. It'll be a little lengthy list and we'll have to. Anyway, we'll have to be, we'll have to read it out as we discuss it with the retail. 

Speaker 1  (52:56)
Yeah, that's fine. So we'll review it before we'll make sure that we're good with the word against stuff. The big thing is that we just want. 

Speaker 3  (53:02)
It just requires, you know, it's to Romeo and retail, we'll just have to pull out the beats, because it will be quite lengthy, because we're breaking into, because we are taking it down to the blue, sticky level, so it'll be a little lengthy. Okay. Well, I think I can easily do that without any problems. 

Speaker 3  (53:23)
Remember, we had done it in the Excel sheet, but then we started getting into details and it became really ugly. 

Speaker 4  (53:29)
The problem with the Excel sheet is it mixed like five different types of things, right? Like it was not, it just it was called use cases, but they Excel, she didn't really cover use cases. It covered a bunch of solution components. 

Speaker 3  (53:42)
Yeah, the thing is, yeah, you were discussing everything at the same time. We were discussing everything at the same time. 

Speaker 4  (53:50)
I purpose, I think the main issue would be that she is that lots of everything on it was valid, but it wasn't really use cases, it was mixing use cases with a bunch of stuff that was that were more like solution constraints, non-functional requirements, technology deliverables, all in the same sheet. So we need to segment more like what To some extent, what Jeremy's doing here, right? Which is breaking things into categories. 

Speaker 4  (54:16)
So it's clear which things are sort of. And independence, or what? 

Speaker 3  (54:21)
Okay, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (54:22)
Anthony I'll be. I will be on the call tomorrow. 

Speaker 3  (54:27)
Yeah, because it'll just have to it just have to, you know, we'll have to weed out the we'll have to weed it out a bit, before we share it with everybody. Okay, folks 
