
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Mediate, a finding, I'll speak finding in a nutshell. Okay, yeah, it's enterprise reporter from quest. 

Speaker 2  (00:11)
It, uh yeah, that would have been, you need to know that but just enterprise reporting, I don't know, that could mean anything. 

Speaker 1  (00:18)
I guess that's why there's this kickoff yeah. 

Speaker 2  (00:25)
Well, that's helped greatly. Thank you, Richard. 

Speaker 1  (00:27)
No problem. 

Speaker 3  (00:33)
So nature, it will be under irides or idr, because we had a problem last time, right? When We are the observers, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (00:42)
Yeah, sure and be under AD. D. Yes, ADS specific to the ad infrastructure. 

Speaker 2  (00:47)
Yeah, I don't have this, so you do a halfpipe. Resumer, new tech new app, correct, yeah. Okay, if we played with this yet, Richard like is 

Speaker 1  (00:58)
P'r seed, it yep, there was a piece there was that 

Speaker 2  (01:03)
Okay, we didn't do an NTA though by sounds of that right. 

Speaker 1  (01:06)
Why isn't the NTI done after the fact? 

Speaker 2  (01:10)
No NTA. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
LNTA I'm not aware of that no, all right. 

Speaker 2  (01:21)
I'm less of an essay and more of an architecture, a governance cop. I'll need this jacket. 

Speaker 1  (01:30)
So I guess the nta falls, it's A 

Speaker 2  (01:33)
I want I tease you, drink first and then actually NTI needs to they won't touch it until we have A 

Speaker 1  (01:40)
Afterwards. 

Speaker 2  (01:41)
I now won record, right? So we'll need to do that before they do anything. 

Speaker 1  (01:46)
Yeah, I haven't gone through that process. Rnt and ta. 

Speaker 2  (01:50)
I've never dealt with it. 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
It will be a first Cause, we'll have another product also from quest that we'll come in to replace AGP M so 

Speaker 2  (02:09)
Replacing, what? 

Speaker 1  (02:11)
Age of PM advance. We're policy manager. 

Speaker 2  (02:17)
Also, from quest. 

Speaker 1  (02:19)
All right, gather replacement is from quest just because Microsoft appreciated that product 

Speaker 4  (02:25)
Hey well. 

Speaker 5  (02:29)
And it's walking about star late Okay, so I'm glad I'll wait back all of your bridge. So just before we gotta start everyone to know who's doing what, no, the steps we will cut out right, so just for all of you to know. So Antony is from our esa team who will be acting as our business analyst basically to document all the Venice requirements, including functional and unfunctional requirements, so we have the Umer here is our diesel resource primary, we'll be focusing on lexitoring the country gap and nervous documents, so Dave visa was a solution architect, we'll walk out let's say the blueprint, the architectural blueprint, then we have a demand bra, he is our design. 

Speaker 5  (03:32)
We'll continue with lexipaid with the ibomb approval with the Dr. So these are the teams basically more folks on the route employment until the design approval. So from the I'm team, so we have Lane links our PO so here's the PO for our part directories, Richard, you all know, it's the engineer, Jason is also the I'm Engineers will be assisting provider, basically, the technical Details, you know, Alice is also an engineer. 

Speaker 5  (04:09)
So basically referred, Jason and Alister has all the technical details we'll be providing so Edward and oloop, our card coordinators who will be helping us to coordinate all the activities. So all will be the primary is the backup, so this is pretty much all of our teams But to get us started, I think, because all of you will need the same information as reason. I got all of you together. 

Speaker 5  (04:38)
This is more introductory. I think the process will be starting for our Antony to dedu. At the time of the dark information we're feeding, let's say, um, and a day for the design documents and eventually the mandra will take on all the design activities to get approved for the ER and Idaho. 

Speaker 5  (05:03)
So that's the whole process there, do any of us question before we dig deep into the technical discussion. 

Speaker 3  (05:13)
Hi, William, good morning, so I think they should be under adds and not idi as right because when we go to dinner last time it was then we had to change it to an ads. So If you want to change the malco or yeah. 

Speaker 1  (05:28)
This has nothing to do with 

Speaker 5  (05:30)
And this is a little bit complicated. Now 

Speaker 4  (05:32)
Hello? 

Speaker 2  (05:33)
Yes, okay. It's A 

Speaker 5  (05:34)
You see a different no, it's not. 

Speaker 3  (05:36)
Okay? And it will be another idea, so only 

Speaker 5  (05:42)
So there's electrically complicated acts as a brand new application for now, to create a new application code with takes and time, so this will be put into the I and the score the ir for now. And here later on decided that a final miracle is being created. 

Speaker 6  (06:03)
Application code is in the process of being created right now. Jason and I have a meeting with relevant teams analyzing the new code. 

Speaker 2  (06:13)
Yeah, I wouldn't move forward with a different existing app code, and then switch it later on that really get that things will get messy, you know, all kinds of things are tagged and tied to the app code to go back and change it. I think it would be a mistake. So lany, and you've been already on the app code sort of drafted, I mean, that's all it needs to be development mode, right? 

Speaker 2  (06:39)
It doesn't need to be in production mode, it, just as long as you. What's the app, what is the app code, by the way? 

Speaker 6  (06:46)
A Dq ER. 

Speaker 2  (06:50)
It's like that Happ. 80QDR. 

Speaker 6  (06:54)
Q. E! R. 

Speaker 5  (07:00)
All right, smoke antipress reported, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (07:03)
Yeah, I don't see it like, is it? It's not a development mode that yet I'm looking 

Speaker 6  (07:11)
I'm not sure what faces in, but this is still a for approval. So no progress as of the last time I raised this 

Speaker 2  (07:25)
Okay. Yeah, I think yeah, but I mean, it shouldn't take too long to get it. Just in a state where, you know, the terror hasn't been done yet or whatever, and it's still just in, like, the life cycle mode would be just development or whatever, where it's you're just, you're still You know, it's still, it's still in development. 

Speaker 2  (07:45)
It's funny I don't I thought I would see it right away in development status but I don't see it in Tita right now. 

Speaker 5  (07:57)
Exactly. Are you spending right to tax your trip? Starting off the mail code we know is called the add QR, because we cannot see it right, but we don't want to pick this. 

Speaker 5  (08:11)
Because a shoe is stopper, I mean, if they stand it's a weak proceed with adq. Yeah, let's do it. But if there is something we have to have I underscored, there is a temporary one if we have to use, but if we don't have to use, we'd rather use the ad Q year. 

Speaker 5  (08:30)
That's the approach we want, we just don't want, because it is hold up to the whole process. Texas. 

Speaker 2  (08:39)
Yeah, I just don't know what you 

Speaker 5  (08:40)
So for any other documents, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (08:42)
I just don't know what you would, what would what you'd need an app code for that. I don't know what steps you would go through with a with a temporary interimap code. It doesn't make sense to me, but anyways. 

Speaker 5  (08:57)
So yeah, so if any documents we don't have to put the system to pass through, that's used at edq. Ur. But if we somehow we blocked and it's because the show stopper, we need to go the temporary use, I and the squad here, I hope we don't have to especially for send documentations right, so we can just use the add Q as the male cone unless it has to be entered the system, so let's use the ad Q year until we really cannot. 

Speaker 5  (09:28)
Let's do it that way that way, okay? But I think it won't stop us to get an introductory, then let's plan the activities, especially for some requirement, the package documentation, or some initial questions here, that's the purpose, and let's get a story. Okay, so if that's the case, then I'm more thinking is give some background, so can these adjacent arbitrary providers and background why this tool? 

Speaker 5  (09:55)
What is that? So all the teams has the understanding of that? 

Speaker 4  (10:01)
Yep, for sure, which would be a minor jump in on that. So essentially, this is a standalone application that Can be used to pull data from active directory and other endpoints, but we 're looking at specifically the active directory piece for this purpose. Purpose pulls data from 

Speaker 5  (10:26)
Her stop. Sorry, this, because I think most of us over here, I don't want to repeat in the future do any of you feel there's a benefit less recording. It would that help you? 

Speaker 5  (10:39)
I think there is a recording it probably. You can reference in the future makes sense to help you. If we are consensus 

Speaker 2  (10:48)
It's time to sign by me here. 

Speaker 5  (10:50)
Yeah, okay. Okay, great, so let's get the recording back. Thanks. 

Speaker 5  (10:55)
Sorry about that, Jason yeah, please. Yeah, result. 

Speaker 4  (10:58)
Okay, yeah, for sure, I'll start 

Speaker 5  (11:08)
Yep, the recording started. Yeah, please press seeing 

Speaker 2  (11:14)
Yeah, it's got to come off. Mute, accept the Transcript. 

Speaker 4  (11:17)
Yeah, I have to exec. The Terms & Conditions Which is new? I don't know when that though was at it. 

Speaker 4  (11:25)
But anyway Anyway, yeah, so quest center hards, reporter is a standalone application that in this use case will integrate with active directory and pull group and membership information, and it will store it in a database SQL database that will allow generation of reports using that data, and those reports are specifically targeted for the purposes of this finding towards nested group memberships in active directory and that is groups as members within other groups. And the tool has 3 main components. 

Speaker 4  (12:06)
There is the discovery manager, which is the tool that integrates with active directory to read the data. Database component, which is where the data gets stored and the report manager component, which generates the reports from data in the database The tool can be installed either on one server which is how we had it in the poc. But obviously that's not ideal for load and Performance purposes, so we were recommended by quest to We have the servers individualized, basically have a server for the The discovery manager, which is Performing the queries against actor directory and Closter, it Nodes for each server in The fridge domain in that forest, so I'll use tdbgs. 

Speaker 4  (13:06)
As an example, the primary discovery manager tool will be installed in dtbfg or similar, and then we will have a node. Note server running a node instance of enterprise reporter in D2 Arn or sorry, an arnet and td securities. So that would be similar configuration in the bk and mmi domain. 

Speaker 4  (13:35)
Now that gives us the best performance for running those queries, the longest part of the application processes the queries against active directory due to the volume of data. All the groups and all membership data is pulled, including user members and stored in the database in the sequel database after which the connection to active directory is no longer running, and all actions can be performed against the SQL database using the report man. Ginger tool and the report manager tool basically just performs sequel queries against the database using. 

Speaker 4  (14:12)
I Out of the box, as well as custom queries to generate reports in various formats that can be packaged and used for reporting on nested structures remediation of the finding, for example, and various other things we have worked with quests to define those queries to meet our needs as best as possible, creating Structured trees for nested groups and that sort of query would run on either a client like so we could run it on a tool server in our environment external to the quest enterprise reporter servers, or it can also run locally as a schedule job to the quest enterprise reporter servers, so we're flexible in that respect. 

Speaker 4  (15:00)
But to for a general estimate, when we were discussing this with quest, we wanted to have essentially 5 servers. 5 primary servers in each environment 34, the td global forest, one for bk and G and one for mmi, and then Variation of Dr. ser servers in each environment depending on the risk associated with that environment. 

Speaker 4  (15:31)
So that was kind of our estimate and Yeah, I think Richard, I think the last account we kind of landed on 18, so 6 per, and the reason for that is the Dr. Kind of only really needs to capture. The database is the is the is where all the information is stored, the enterprise reporter tool how it works is the database is portable in that if for whatever reason the server that hosts the discovery manager or the report manager becomes unusable, you can link another version or another install of the report manager or the discovery manager to an existing database via an encryption key So that key gets saved at time of installation somewhere and And you can use it to link a new instance if you lose connection, or the server goes down for whatever reason. 

Speaker 4  (16:29)
So the database is accessible by by any instance, as long as you have that key And that's kind of it's it, in a nutshell use of the tool is pretty straightforward, but I don't think would require any sort of like specific, architectural or design philosophies. 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
So chasing, you don't have a picture, do you? It wouldn't be cool to have a picture of this. 

Speaker 4  (16:56)
A picture of 

Speaker 2  (16:57)
Well, just yeah, just the check architecture, it sounds like so there's a sort of a discovery type server that needs to be in each domain, and then you've got obviously a SQL database and then the reporting a separate reporting server that goes against the database is that 

Speaker 4  (17:17)
Yeah, so it doesn't need to be in each domain. It can link as long as there is a trust available which we have so in our poc, we had everything on one server in D2 GDB for example, and it was able to pull data from D2 Tb 2 Arnaut. Securities, as well ASD to Bang G and D to TDI. 

Speaker 2  (17:38)
Because of the trial game so it can use the trust, but you're saying for till for low distribution and performance reasons. You guys have sort of Figured it needs to be broken down by what was it the keyboard to the TD global, whatever that force trusted an MMI and BK and G 

Speaker 4  (17:59)
Yeah, exactly, we wanted to break it down into Basically if the forest had multiple domains within it, then it would be a the primary would be located on like tdbg, for example, and then your nodes would exist on the other two domains in that forest Arna and td securities that sort of clustering would only have to be present in The the td global forest because bkg and mmi only have one domain within them so they can run sort of standalone Ok, is that all of them? 

Speaker 2  (18:33)
Sorry, I just say how many discovery servers? Then why do you think you need? 

Speaker 4  (18:39)
What yeah, that the other pieces? So all of the the discovery server would exist in TD global or TDB for example, the nodes would exist in all the other domains. Aren't it? 

Speaker 4  (18:53)
It is serendipities, Ben, G and I'm on the venue. 

Speaker 2  (18:55)
I thought those nodes, I was calling them a discovery server, because they're the ones that actually are connecting to the I would take to the to add and doing the queries, but yeah. 

Speaker 4  (19:05)
The nodes do that, the nodes do that as part of the clustering, so the the The main, the primary cluster would exist, and it would connect up with all the nodes to have them do work in their own domains. And by 2 work, I mean, get queries from their own domains and the information would then be packaged and sent to the To the database through the primary server. Let me see if I can just pull up the installed dock in that 

Speaker 2  (19:32)
Clarifies, so videos, you gotta. You have one discovery server in the What td global, whatever we call? And then plus a node in TDB FG Arnett. 

Speaker 2  (19:48)
Mmi. 

Speaker 4  (19:50)
Yb K yeah, yeah, exactly 

Speaker 2  (19:53)
So 5 servers. 

Speaker 4  (19:55)
Yep, and I 

Speaker 2  (19:57)
And plus a database and then plus the reporting server is separate. Then right now right now 

Speaker 4  (20:05)
Yes, the reporting server would be can either be local and run as a schedule drug because once the discovery is done, the performance is not impacted whatsoever by that tool, it's completely offline. There are no additional discoveries done until a next discovery is run, but that's not a real-time thing. 

Speaker 2  (20:26)
Oh, isn't this? But what is discovery running every day once a week? 

Speaker 4  (20:30)
It can be scheduled to be on demand or it can be scheduled to To yeah, to some sort of schedule, but the reason we don't want it to be running constantly is because the time to run it in D2 twfg, and sorry, in Dev. So all 5 domains in Dev, it took 12 to 15 hours to run. Yeah, off one server. 

Speaker 4  (20:51)
Now obviously that would come down quite a bit with the node and the clustering format that we would use, but yeah, it would. It's not really great to have it running every single day, we wouldn't need it to anyway, I think we were discussing monthly Vs weekly. 

Speaker 2  (21:12)
Okay, so there's the for each environment, let's just mark this out in prad, you've got these 5 servers that are involved in the discovery query component, it feeds the database, so it's another server. And then is there not a separate server that does the reporting? 

Speaker 4  (21:33)
So yeah, it's 

Speaker 2  (21:34)
You're just going to use one of the discovery servers. 

Speaker 4  (21:37)
It can exist on a discovery server and and it can also be running on sale person's local machine, something like that, it's essentially a client, it just requests the data from the database and in a specific format or package it doesn't, yeah, but let me write anything it doesn't perform. Any, it's just a read, like a front-end tool for it can run on a laptop or 

Speaker 2  (22:02)
Yeah, then I don't think permission wise are going to be happy about people's laptops connecting directly to a sequel server in the data zone like I know it's, I don't know what the data classification is, but I doubt that's gon. 

Speaker 4  (22:15)
It's the exact same data that's in active directory. Right now I could I could, and we did test this before we purchased the server. We tested running our own scripts against hack trajectory, the data is available to literally anyone in the bank like you could you could query power shell with your own Account and get the exact same information, no new information is stored there. 

Speaker 4  (22:36)
We don't install employee numbers or anything like that. It's whatever's an act of directory. Is there in the database? 

Speaker 4  (22:43)
Just get hackaged in a way that makes it more access. 

Speaker 2  (22:47)
So I again, I'm not even sure what we classify what the 10th kind of classification is for 80 I got to go look that up again. 

Speaker 4  (22:56)
But I think, maybe umari, do you do do you remember that she 

Speaker 2  (23:01)
Probably still confidential. Honestly 

Speaker 4  (23:03)
It's either eternal or confidential. I'm not a 100% sure, but yeah, you're right, it's gonna be the same classification. 

Speaker 2  (23:09)
Status for you right, yeah, but I still I still think they'll poop the idea of like the desktop connecting directly to the database. It's usually like I thought there would be some precanned reporting, and some sexy UI into the reporting, like it's, it seems strange that you just like, hey, go at the But it'd be like a web-based UI that would give you all the funky reporting, and stuff like seemed strange that it would be We'd run that video stuff 

Speaker 4  (23:41)
Port manager essentially functions like that. It's a fit client, but so it's installed on a server or locally on your machine, and you can query the data, and then it will output it in A Fat of your choosing, whether it's like a data file or And actually, hmm report or a PDF, what have you? But the idea is that we would export data Data in a data format that can be invested into an actual web-based dashboard of some sort like powerbi or a home brew thing, something like that was kind of the end goal, depending on teams and teams' needs for the data, right? 

Speaker 4  (24:18)
Because a lot of this data is not going to be utilized by us. It's going to be utilized by the other teams enterprises Employee enablement, I am amh. So it's it's really, you know, and we have already in discussions with them, to for them, to just use to get the raw data as ingest into their systems, and they can use it, how they see fit, sort of thing. 

Speaker 3  (24:43)
With a classification for leds is restricted Really? Yeah? On data. 

Speaker 2  (24:55)
Thank you, it's good to think about what, but that's probably because it's got the the hashed credentials or passwords and stuff like that. But that's certainly not something we' re going to extract into the database, I wouldn't think, right. 

Speaker 4  (25:07)
No, it does not access to that. The only thing it would put in there are groups and group members 

Speaker 2  (25:15)
Yeah, so hopefully when you go. Yeah, so that's kind of important. That's why I'd like to when you go through the the new app code and get the terror rate that we do it correctly right? 

Speaker 2  (25:24)
Because I wouldn't want this to end up with the same data classification as restricted. That's that's, that's going to be quite well, give. 

Speaker 7  (25:32)
Yeah, so basically as alright, so basically, if you have group and group members, so you should write these, then that would be most likely to be ACF 2 ids, or that would become a confidential data. 

Speaker 2  (25:43)
Yeah, I think you're going to end up, I'm guessing confidential as well, and I think it's only restricted. Now, because you've got the credentials, even though they're hashed, the actual credentials are an ad, so that's why that got restricted, but if you're not pulling that over, then we shouldn't adapt. We shouldn't inherit a restricted category. 

Speaker 2  (26:03)
And you don't want, you don't want that, that'll make them be a pain in the but. 

Speaker 7  (26:06)
Yeah, yeah, specific categories means you have to protect extra controls, and that would be a different ball game then, so you don't want that. 

Speaker 1  (26:17)
And just to add to that, Jason. 

Speaker 4  (26:20)
Correct, and I'm wr. 

Speaker 1  (26:22)
The report that is required for the the finding It does not include all members of the groups. It's specific to group nesting. 

Speaker 4  (26:33)
Correct? Yeah, so whatever. 

Speaker 1  (26:35)
Every report will be published or wherever, like Jason mentioned power BI or whatever it is, it will only contain group nesting. It does not tell you which uses are in one 

Speaker 4  (26:49)
Correct. Yeah, it would be a limited set of the data, and the access to the database would be completely restricted to any individual user would have to be through. Do you manage your tool? 

Speaker 4  (27:02)
The report manager tool 

Speaker 1  (27:04)
And to be honest, we're not, we're not publishing any information that's not already accessible by users, the havocant. So anyway, as soon as you have an account, you have access to this data through ars through 

Speaker 4  (27:17)
You know aldaquer, queries. 

Speaker 1  (27:21)
So we're not actually introducing any additional access specific access to this data number. 

Speaker 2  (27:28)
Okay, it's okay. 

Speaker 3  (27:29)
So I need to drop off, but I have one question Jason jason, is it physical or it will be on the vmc too? What will be the platform? 

Speaker 4  (27:40)
I would imagine it would be Yeah, yes, that was it. 

Speaker 2  (27:45)
I'm going to really acquire, Mr. B Yeah, healthcare, I would really hope so. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (27:50)
Thank you very much after the documentary. Yeah, everybody has time. I can still share. 

Speaker 2  (27:55)
Well, the one, yeah, the one thing I wanted to know, like mentioned at the top of the meeting was like, we're going to need to nta this tool, right, it's technology that we've got to adapt, so we have to go through our new technology process. So who's the tech owner? Who's going to be the owner of the product? 

Speaker 4  (28:14)
I believe it would be lane and then Myself and Richard as delegates corre. 

Speaker 2  (28:21)
Okay. Wrongly, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I can draft quickly draft up an NTA template, send it over for you guys to kind of populate, but you've done the yet you've done a poc already, right, so we can, hopefully you've got the, you know, some results or some test cases. 

Speaker 2  (28:36)
That you could include in the in the nta, so it can combine the 2 steps 

Speaker 4  (28:42)
Yep, I have a report and an overall summary of that that I can provide. Okay everyone Yeah, so this is kind of a just a rough overview of one particular installation design. We. 

Speaker 4  (29:09)
So our thought was originally to have these 3 components, the report manager ER server and configuration manager on a single server. I wouldn't. 

Speaker 2  (29:19)
But I'm not knowing that as well. Yeah 

Speaker 4  (29:22)
Yeah, and that is, these nodes would be running on the other servers per domain. 

Speaker 2  (29:28)
And they be joined in those domains too, just to make things easier or to stay work across the trust. 

Speaker 4  (29:36)
It would They would be installed on the the I mean, like a server within that domain, so the server would be domain joint. Yes Okay, so that would be ideal. I mean we can. 

Speaker 4  (29:49)
It can work across the trust. It doesn't matter. I mean, I guess it's probably easier from a management perspective. 

Speaker 4  (29:55)
Could not have servers under, you know. Bkg, for example, be owned by A Non am CB entity were not 

Speaker 2  (30:03)
Yeah, I let my kids are wonky. Yeah, I never felt like yeah. 

Speaker 4  (30:06)
So it can work across us, not a problem, as long as they're separate to preserve performance. Then we're fine 

Speaker 2  (30:14)
Right? Okay, so where is this? Can you share the stock or share the link? 

Speaker 4  (30:20)
Yeah, I can share this after the call. This is the installation guide and there's also a user guide that I can share. Gives details on ports to open things like that. 

Speaker 4  (30:30)
Yeah, so I can pass this over. 

Speaker 2  (30:32)
Yeah, we're just put it in the chat window, and that 

Speaker 4  (30:35)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, that worked. 

Speaker 2  (30:37)
And then And at the top of the hour or 20, she Richard sluffs, Richard mentioned something about like, bringing this in because Microsoft's depreting, something they're advanced group policy or something, but was it 

Speaker 4  (30:52)
No, no, that was a different that was a different product. The advanced group policy management tool, so hpf that is being deprecated, so there's another tool we're buying from quest called GPO admino Admin express, I don't know if it's like the actual express But we're buying another product that basically replaces hpm. 

Speaker 2  (31:17)
Okay, so ignore that has nothing to do with ad QE R okay, right? Yeah, okay. And then so what is the there's a finding that 80 QR is being brought in because of a finding, what's the finding number? 

Speaker 4  (31:32)
Yep, the finding number is, let's see here. 

Speaker 2  (31:36)
Or you can pick that in the group shot too 

Speaker 4  (31:38)
Yeah, I'll put it in the chat. But yes, there's a large finding, not just 80 nesting. It's there's a lot of components R back is there? 

Speaker 2  (31:49)
Network share, this is going to tackle a couple of them. 

Speaker 4  (31:52)
Nope, this will only so we are only responsible for a small A portion of the finding there are many pieces to the finding, and other teams are working on amh is working on wim. Bunch of different teams But I'll put the number in the the chat 

Speaker 2  (32:11)
Yeah, yeah, and if you have any you know, is there, like a one sentence description of the finding to be him hilarious 5 night, oh, that's a lot of nines. 

Speaker 4  (32:20)
Yeah, and the This one is what our commitment is for this particular purpose. So for requests, enterprise reporter That's the commitment for this particular item. Again, there are 9 pieces for the overall finding. 

Speaker 4  (32:44)
I can put all of them in if you want in the chat. This is the entire finding as far as I have it from my most recent update. 

Speaker 2  (32:54)
And 

Speaker 4  (32:55)
Yeah, so there's 9 pieces very. Our team is only looking at was only looking at. 6 and 7 on this list. 

Speaker 4  (33:11)
Okay. So yeah, so we've already done 67 ISIS what we're working on now, and then I'll put the documents in here as well. 

Speaker 2  (33:22)
The link the link to it like that's a that's just a link off of quest website. I guess. 

Speaker 4  (33:27)
Nope, that was, there were raw P. D. F. 

Speaker 4  (33:31)
There as well. Yeah, in order to download them, you need to have questions. The counts, unfortunately for these 2, uh U. 

Speaker 2  (33:40)
Okay, I'd like to thank you. 

Speaker 4  (33:56)
Yeah, so that's basically it. It's fairly straightforward. I think the most difficult pieces are going to be There's the what was difficult for us previously, which was ports and things with network, because there are quite a few that we would want open for this. 

Speaker 4  (34:21)
Set up, but we can discuss those fine details as we 

Speaker 2  (34:25)
Buffalo, it's all those Goofy. Microsoft ad ports, I imagine right 

Speaker 4  (34:33)
Yeah, because he's ran it all on one server. We didn't have the issues of porting. For our plc, but we will add it for sure. 

Speaker 4  (34:44)
So we'll have to make sure we cover it up. Yeah, it's all of those those odd, not only the Microsoft ones, but also the sequel ports and We'll have to open the correct ports that are specific to this app so that the nodes can talk to the cluster primary, so that's all detailed in that install guide so that that shouldn't be too difficult to go through, and we can just determine which The subset of ports will require 

Speaker 2  (35:16)
Okay, all right, well, my takeaway here is I'll draft the nta template and send it to you and lany, and Just help fill out. And then we'll Because that's going to be required to create an L1 entry, and in ServiceNow in the IPS, I mean, for tracking all this stuff, and that's you'll need that to do nti like nti, will But you can't start it unless you have an L1 ID. So If that makes sense, okay? 

Speaker 2  (36:01)
And then what's the timeline on this as anyone else? Like yesterday or like as her, I see something about July 2027 is that you've got a year to fix this, is that what I'm saying? 

Speaker 4  (36:17)
That's the commitment end day for the finding, and that is delivering the evidence that we have all of these pieces in place, and not just the reporting, but also A Let me bring up the actual verbiage there. Sustainability updated and maintenance of existing groups. So there 'S.A. 

Speaker 4  (36:43)
lot of moving pieces to that we' re not the only team involved, we' re also working with wim on that, but yeah, essentially, July 2027 is our end date but we're looking to have ER stood up. And I believe the lower environments, much sooner before year's end for sure. 

Speaker 2  (37:04)
If I get it, then all right, well, that's the reason. Nothing like And nothing like we need this next week or something 

Speaker 4  (37:12)
No, no, no, no, no obviously sooner. The better for sure. But yeah, we're not. 

Speaker 4  (37:19)
We're not rushing, and we don't want to rush in this case because it does pertain to a flat tick, so Stay here. Just to clarify, the nta is what we have to provide for right 

Speaker 2  (37:40)
Yeah, new technology assessment right? Just the standard process for Approving technology. The nti is certifying the technology, so it's very different when it's okay, just like approving. 

Speaker 2  (37:58)
Yeah, we need this technology, it makes sense. It's the right tool. I don't know if there's any comparative similar tools out there to this quest to Enterprise reporting reporting. 

Speaker 2  (38:18)
There isn't any other vendors. 

Speaker 4  (38:21)
Yeah, so we primarily looked at this tool because of our already ongoing engagements with quest for things like ARS and qrm, so and it does allow integrations with those systems. So that was part of the reason why we went with it. Because we could use utilize existing apps. 

Speaker 4  (38:42)
Hopes to give us more reporting and more data So that was the primary reason we couldn't find any Like standalone applications, we found details about custom like bespoke. It's third party like, you know, consulting written scripts or applications that were that were not vendor sold or approved, so we didn't want to go with those yeah, yeah, we even tried to do some in-house, but the performance was not. Was not working, of course, we could have easily just built all of this similar structure. 

Speaker 4  (39:19)
Read all of the data from ad dump it in a database. Yes, the first run would be massive. But afterwards It's curing, the database would be relatively fast, but Again, the integrations with ARS and all these other systems And also, the fact that it comes with vendor support and Professional services just made the most sense, especially as it pertains to a finding, we didn 't want to have to, you know, internally, support a custom built tool. 

Speaker 4  (39:51)
I mean, we already kind of had that issue with 80 lab portal, whereas a custom built tool. And now We 're fighting with various teams internally because it doesn' T Mine booth Torres, it doesn't align with the code review, and all these different. You know, mcrs that are required for it because it's an internally built app that doesn't meet any sort of standards from like 1520 years ago it was built, so we didn't want to, we didn't want to give future us a bigger problem. 

Speaker 4  (40:24)
Yeah, it's no more questions, I mean, I guess that's pretty much it I see. Will's already dropped. Most people have dropped already. 

Speaker 2  (40:31)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think we're good, I think I got a general idea. We'll start with the nta and then And yeah, we'll go from there. Oh, and if we're going to create an architecture design or an architecture blueprint, does anyone have? 

Speaker 2  (40:46)
Do you guys have a share, not a share point? A confluence site that we can use 

Speaker 4  (40:54)
We do. Yes, I'll get you that link. 

Speaker 2  (40:57)
Yeah, is that another one? If you want to just pop it in the 

Speaker 4  (41:02)
I've moved off of confluence, though we use share point now. 

Speaker 2  (41:05)
Yeah, well, unfortunately, the architecture blueprint template is a it's a confluence template, and there's no word option anymore, so have to 

Speaker 4  (41:15)
Let me let me get you the link for that. Because I don't even think we use our own page, but if you could We could probably just create you a link so that you can just throw it there. Alright. 

Speaker 4  (41:27)
Alright, I'll put it in the chat as well. 

Speaker 2  (41:29)
Okay, yeah, well, first step is the nta, and then we'll worry about the blueprint. 

Speaker 4  (41:35)
Okay, can you Put that information in the chat regarding nta because I think ghislaine What will require that? And there's also a little confusion still between that the NT ISO 

Speaker 2  (41:48)
Yeah, it's the 2 part process, so in taste first then nts 

Speaker 4  (41:52)
So we already did the second step. Okay, that's fun. 

Speaker 2  (41:55)
Although you completed the NTI 

Speaker 4  (41:58)
Yeah, she already did the N. T. I. 

Speaker 2  (42:01)
I'm shocked because 

Speaker 4  (42:03)
That's what she was saying. 

Speaker 2  (42:04)
Those guys basically say they need an L1 ID. To do that. I got well, let me thank lady on that, she's left. 

Speaker 2  (42:15)
Okay, I'll ping lady, okay? Perfect, okay, alright. Alright. 

Speaker 2  (42:20)
Yeah, I better roll too much further. 

Speaker 4  (42:23)
All right, thanks to everybody, thanks to ticket. 
